{"candidates": ["Look directly at the headlights of the oncoming vehicle", "Always use your high beams", "Increase your following distance"], "question": "When driving at night you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 0}
{"candidates": ["You must yield to pedestrians", "Pedestrians must yield to you", "Construction workers must yield to you"], "question": "At a crosswalk:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 2}
{"candidates": ["Grip the steering wheel firmly, slow down, and exit from the traffic lanes.", "Pump the brakes rapidly.", "Brake hard and steer toward the right edge of the roadway."], "question": "If, while driving, a tire suddenly blows out, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 3}
{"candidates": ["you yield to all other traffic at the intersection.", "you are traveling on a two-way street and turning onto a two-way street.", "you are traveling on a one-way street and turning onto another one-way street."], "question": "It is legal to make a left turn at a red traffic light after stopping if:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 4}
{"candidates": ["A construction flagger is ahead", "A police office is ahead", "A parking attendant is ahead"], "question": "The sign shown in the picture tells a driver that:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 6}
{"candidates": ["Slow down and get into the lane nearest the centerline.", "Signal and get into the lane nearest the right curb.", "Approach the corner in the lane nearest the right curb, but move over toward the middle of the street before turning."], "question": "The proper way in which to make a right turn is:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 7}
{"candidates": ["Driving 3-5 mph slower than the car behind", "Driving 3-5 mph faster than the car behind", "Keeping a steady speed"], "question": "You can help keep the driver behind you at a safe distance by", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 8}
{"candidates": ["Even over the counter drugs can impair your driving", "Any prescription drug is safe to use if you don't feel drowsy", "Only illegals drugs can impair your driving"], "question": "Which of these statements is true about drugs and driving is true", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 10}
{"candidates": ["Slowing down.", "Moving over a lane if there is no on next to you.", "Maintain your speed and position."], "question": "Make room for cars entering freeways by:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 12}
{"candidates": ["Wait until the pedestrian crosses the street before proceeding", "Proceed if you have the right of way", "Proceed if the pedestrian is not in your lane"], "question": "A pedestrian starts to cross the street after the \"Don't walk\" signal begins to flash. The pedestrian is in the middle of the street when your signal light changes to green. You should", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 14}
{"candidates": ["yield to the vehicle to your right", "yield to the vehicle to your left", "wait until there are no vehicles at the intersection"], "question": "For right-of-way at an intersection where signs or signals are not used, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 23}
{"candidates": ["Set the parking brake", "Check mirrors for traffic", "Place your foot on the accelerator"], "question": "Before stopping your vehicle on the roadway:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 30}
{"candidates": ["Increase your speed", "You can go through the intersection at a reasonable and safe speed if it is clear to do so", "Adjust your mirrors"], "question": "A steady green traffic light means:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 31}
{"candidates": ["Windshield wipers cannot keep the windshield clear of rain", "Tires lose contact with the road surface", "Spray from large trucks reduce visibility"], "question": "When a vehicle is hydroplaning the", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 32}
{"candidates": ["They do not have the same physical reflexes as an adult", "Both. They are smaller and more difficult to see and they do not have the same physical reflexes as an adult", "They are smaller and more difficult to see"], "question": "Children on bicycles should be given even more space by motor vehicle operators because:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 33}
{"candidates": ["Check traffic in all directions", "Always move to the left lane", "Increase your speed"], "question": "What is an important step in turning?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 34}
{"candidates": ["Put your lights on high beam", "Put your lights on low beam", "Put your emergency flashers on"], "question": "It is very foggy. You should slow down and:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 35}
{"candidates": ["Get rest or change drivers", "Drink coffee", "Open a window"], "question": "The best thing to do if you become tired or sleepy while driving is:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 36}
{"candidates": ["Missing an exit", "Falling asleep behind the wheel and crashing", "Being late for an appointment"], "question": "Fatigue increases the risk of:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 37}
{"candidates": ["Your tires do not have as much traction, so you must drive slower.", "Your tires can grip the road better than on pavement.", "Visibility is better."], "question": "When driving on gravel or dirt roads:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 38}
{"candidates": ["Over the counter medications cannot impair driving ability if taken in the recommended dosages", "Most cold medications can make a person drowsy", "Medications are safe to take at any time if prescribed by a doctor"], "question": "Which of these statements is true about driving and taking medications", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 40}
{"candidates": ["Roads in shady areas", "Hilly open roads", "Concrete rather than asphalt roads"], "question": "Which area is more likely to be slippery after snow or rain during freezing weather?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 41}
{"candidates": ["Before you start driving", "Before you get into the car", "Whenever you need to use them"], "question": "Adjust your rearview and side mirrors:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 43}
{"candidates": ["red", "yellow", "orange"], "question": "The basic color for various traffic control devices used in construction and maintenance work areas is:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 44}
{"candidates": ["They cut through all lanes", "They wait on the side of the road", "They may use the left lane"], "question": "When a bicyclist is making a left hand turn:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 45}
{"candidates": ["when you can see the front of the vehicle or the vehicle's headlights in your rearview mirror", "when you can no longer see the vehicle over your right shoulder", "after about three seconds"], "question": "After you have passed a vehicle moving in the same direction, it is safe to move back into the right lane:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 46}
{"candidates": ["Look to the sides of your vehicle to see what is coming.", "Slowly pass vehicles that seem to be stopped for no reason.", "Stop, listen, and proceed cautiously."], "question": "At intersections, crosswalks, and railroad crossings, you should always:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 47}
{"candidates": ["Honk your horn so the pedestrian moves over", "Slow down and let the vehicle pass first", "Keep driving, the oncoming vehicle must stop for you"], "question": "When overtaking a pedestrian who is walking along the roadway and an oncoming vehicle is approaching:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 48}
{"candidates": ["Stop, then proceed when safe.", "Stop before entering the intersection and let all other traffic go first.", "Slow down or stop, only if necessary."], "question": "If a traffic signal light is not working, you must:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 54}
{"candidates": ["Farther behind the truck than you would for a passenger vehicle.", "No more than one car length behind the truck so the driver can see you.", "Closely behind the truck in bad weather because the driver can see farther ahead."], "question": "You may not cross over the center line to pass while doing which of the following?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 59}
{"candidates": ["The crossing is located in a city or town with frequent train traffic", "You transport two or more children in a passenger vehicle", "You don't have room on the other side to completely cross the tracks."], "question": "You must stop at the intersection ahead. Just before the intersection, you have to cross railroad tracks. You should stop before you cross the railroad tracks when:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 62}
{"candidates": ["change lanes in an intersection", "check over your left or right shoulder to check for blind spots", "check for other drivers moving into the same lane"], "question": "When changing lanes, you should never:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 63}
{"candidates": ["Come to a full stop and yield the right-of-way before entering the intersection.", "Drive quickly through the intersection to get out of the way of other vehicles.", "If the intersection is clear, the driver does not need to stop."], "question": "What should a driver do when approaching a traffic control signal that is not in operation?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 64}
{"candidates": ["They are more maneuverable than passenger vehicles", "They all have air brakes which allow them to stop quickly", "They take longer to stop than passenger vehicles"], "question": "Which of these statements is true about large trucks:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 65}
{"candidates": ["One lane of traffic is traveling faster than the other lanes.", "One vehicle is traveling faster or slower than the flow of traffic.", "All vehicles are traveling about the same speed."], "question": "Collisions can happen more often when:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 66}
{"candidates": ["Next to the solid line may pass.", "Next to the broken line may pass.", "In both directions may pass."], "question": "A solid yellow line next to a broken yellow line means that vehicles:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 67}
{"candidates": ["Red, green, yellow", "Green, red, yellow", "Red, yellow, green"], "question": "From top to bottom, the following is the proper order for traffic lights:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 68}
{"candidates": ["watch for multiple trains.", "All the others.", "watch for vehicles that must stop at railroad crossings (school buses, trucks carrying hazardous materials, etc.)"], "question": "You have stopped for a train at a railroad crossing. After the train passes, you must:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 70}
{"candidates": ["Move into the right lane and drive slowly until the vehicle has passed", "Maintain speed and stay in your lane until the vehicle has passed", "Pull over to the curb or edge of the road and stop to allow the emergency vehicle to pass"], "question": "When you hear a siren or see a vehicle approaching with flashing lights:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 72}
{"candidates": ["You can see both its headlights in your rearview mirror.", "You have cleared the front bumper of the passed vehicle.", "You are 50 feet in front of the passed vehicle."], "question": "When passing a vehicle, you should return to your lane when:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 73}
{"candidates": ["under no circumstances", "if you don't feel drowsy", "if it is prescribed by a physician"], "question": "Driving under the influence of any medication which impairs your driving is permitted", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 74}
{"candidates": ["Slow down gradually and use brakes lightly", "Tap or pump the brakes", "Apply the brakes firmly"], "question": "If you experience a tire blowout", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 76}
{"candidates": ["Quickly turn right before the truck or bus does", "Squeeze between the truck or bus and the curb", "Wait until the truck or bus turns before turning right"], "question": "If a truck or bus needs to make a right turn and you are also turning right:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 77}
{"candidates": ["race", "weight", "height"], "question": "Which of the following factors affect an individual's absorption of alcohol:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 80}
{"candidates": ["20 mph", "25 mph", "30 mph"], "question": "Unless otherwise posted the speed limit in a residential area is ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 84}
{"candidates": ["18 years old.", "12 years old.", "16 years old."], "question": "What is the minimum age requirement for obtaining a vessel license in Alabama?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 89}
{"candidates": ["yield the right-of-way to cross traffic close enough to cause conflict", "yield to those vehicles only on your right", "slow down and proceed"], "question": "At intersections with a \"Yield\" sign, you must:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 91}
{"candidates": ["Only is a crossing guard is present", "Only when a guide dog is leading the person across the street", "At all times"], "question": "You must yield to a pedestrian using a white cane or guide dog", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 92}
{"candidates": ["During a heavy downpour.", "The first rain after a dry spell.", "After it has been raining for awhile."], "question": "Roadways are the most slippery:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 93}
{"candidates": ["Brake lightly", "Brake abruptly", "Stay off the brakes"], "question": "If you find yourself in a skid", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 95}
{"candidates": ["Swerve into the lane next to you", "Honk and step on the brake firmly", "Take your foot off the gas"], "question": "A vehicle suddenly \"cuts\" in front of you creating a hazard. Which of these actions should you take first", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 97}
{"candidates": ["Make eye contact and then pass him/her.", "Slow down as you pass him/her.", "Stop and let him/her finish crossing the street."], "question": "There is no crosswalk and you see a pedestrian crossing your lane ahead. You should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 99}
{"candidates": ["Avoid tailgating and keep a safe following distance", "Pass the driver in front of you as soon as you can", "Follow the driver in front of you closely"], "question": "In work zones, you should", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 100}
{"candidates": ["Stop an either get rest or change drivers", "Drink something with caffeine", "Open a window"], "question": "If you are getting tired while driving, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 101}
{"candidates": ["On your right.", "Arrived before you.", "On your left."], "question": "An intersection with stop signs at all four (or more) corners, you must yield the right-of-way to the driver:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 103}
{"candidates": ["Expect the unexpected", "Construction workers must yield to roadway users", "Slightly increase your speed"], "question": "When driving in a construction zone:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 104}
{"candidates": ["Use your low beams", "Use your high beams", "Use your parking lights"], "question": "If weather of light conditions require you to have your lights on:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 105}
{"candidates": ["Unless you have the right of way or a green light", "Unless you entered the intersection on a green light", "Under any circumstances, even if your light is green"], "question": "Blocking an intersection during \"rush hour\" traffic is not permitted", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 106}
{"candidates": ["200 ft.", "300 ft.", "500 ft."], "question": "Within how many ft. must you dim your headlights upon an approaching vehicle?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 118}
{"candidates": ["Repeatedly violate traffic laws.", "Run a red light once.", "Overspeed once."], "question": "Your license may be canceled if ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 119}
{"candidates": ["You must yield the right-of-way to pedestrians", "You have the right-of-way over pedestrians", "Pedestrians must wait for you to cross"], "question": "When you are facing a green light and there are pedestrians in the intersection:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 121}
{"candidates": ["Driving or attempting to drive after consuming alcohol", "Driving or attempting to drive while smoking", "Driving or attempting to drive before midnight"], "question": "All drivers under the age of 21 have a specific restriction prohibiting them from:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 122}
{"candidates": ["the stop arm is retracted", "all students are off the bus", "the stop arm is retracted and the bus resumes motion"], "question": "Vehicles stopped behind a school bus when the red lights are flashing must remain stopped until:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 123}
{"candidates": ["Slow down when driving", "Share a lane with motorcycles", "Make constant visual checks"], "question": "Motorcycles, scooters, and mopeds are not easy to see; therefore, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 124}
{"candidates": ["Stay focused on the center line on the road", "Keep looking briefly to the side of the road", "Flash your high beams"], "question": "To avoid glare from headlights of an approaching car:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 125}
{"candidates": ["when a car is in your blind spot", "quickly and often", "gradually and carefully"], "question": "Changing from one lane to another is best done:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 126}
{"candidates": ["When you are following another vehicle or in heavy traffic", "When you come within about a one-block distance of an oncoming vehicle", "When there are no oncoming vehicles approaching"], "question": "When should you use your high beam headlights?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 127}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "signal your intention before changing lanes", "check your blind spots, mirrors, and look over shoulder toward the rear"], "question": "Before changing lanes or attempting to pass another vehicle, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 128}
{"candidates": ["Within three feet of a private driveway.", "In an unmarked crosswalk", "In a bicycle lane."], "question": "It is illegal to park your vehicle:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 136}
{"candidates": ["No more than one car length behind the truck so the driver can see you.", "Farther behind the truck than you would for a passenger vehicle.", "Closely behind the truck in bad weather because the driver can see farther ahead."], "question": "You are driving on the freeway. The vehicle in front of you is a large truck. You should drive:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 137}
{"candidates": ["Yield to any vehicle, bicycle, or pedestrian in the intersection.", "Yield to pedestrians only in the intersection.", "Wait four seconds before proceeding."], "question": "On a green arrow, you must:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 142}
{"candidates": ["Yes, it is a good defensive driving technique.", "Yes, it is always safer than driving faster than other traffic.", "No, you can block traffic when you drive too slowly."], "question": "Your driver's license may be revoked by the Director of Public Safety if you have ____ reckless driving convictions in ____ months?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 148}
{"candidates": ["You must tell them where to cross the street", "You must always yield the right-of-way", "You must yield the right of way at corners only"], "question": "When a pedestrian is crossing a street guided by a dog or carrying a white cane", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 152}
{"candidates": ["High beams", "Low beams", "Driving lights only"], "question": "When driving in fog, heavy rain or snow, use:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 154}
{"candidates": ["To test the vehicle's shock absorbers.", "To alert drivers to potential tire problems.", "To alert drowsy or inattentive drivers through vibration and sound that their vehicles have left the travel lane or are approaching a stop sign or signal."], "question": "What is the purpose of rumble strips?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 155}
{"candidates": ["Time", "Fresh air.", "Coffee"], "question": "What is the only medically proven method to remove alcohol or other drug combinations from your system?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 156}
{"candidates": ["If it has been raining from one to two hours.", "If it has just begun to rain.", "If it has been raining several hours."], "question": "Highway pavement is particularly treacherous and will be most slippery:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 158}
{"candidates": ["It draws the attention of other drivers as it is an illegal activity", "It causes the driver to be concerned about the cost of the call", "It occupies the driver's hands, eyes, and mind"], "question": "Any use of a cell phone while operating a motor vehicle is considered a distraction because:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 161}
{"candidates": ["honk your horn as you proceed past them.", "carefully drive around them.", "stop until the person is well away from the roadway or path of travel."], "question": "When approaching someone using a white cane or guide dog, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 162}
{"candidates": ["Change lanes and pass cautiously", "Slow to 10 mph", "Stop until the lights stop flashing"], "question": "When a school bus is stopped on your side of the road with its red lights flashing, you must:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 165}
{"candidates": ["Challenge them", "Get out of their way", "Speed up"], "question": "If you encounter an aggressive driver you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 167}
{"candidates": ["Seat belts should be worn behind the back", "Seat belts should still be worn", "Seat belts do not need to be worn"], "question": "If the vehicle is equipped with air bags:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 168}
{"candidates": ["Leaving the scene of an injury accident.", "Driving under the influence of alcohol or other drugs.", "Driving during a heavy downpour."], "question": "Which of the following is not a case in which your license can be revoked?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 177}
{"candidates": ["Look over your right shoulder for a right lane change and your left shoulder for a left lane change", "You only need to turn and look over your right shoulder for lane changes to the right or left", "Vehicles with two outside mirrors do not have blind spots"], "question": "Which of these statements is true about changing lanes", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 181}
{"candidates": ["Stopping", "Turning left", "Debris in roadway"], "question": "The bicyclist is signaling:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 182}
{"candidates": ["Select a safe gap and merge into the lane of traffic", "Always stop before entering the highway", "Merge over two lanes at once and speed up"], "question": "You are merging onto an interstate highway. You should", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 183}
{"candidates": ["Look in the left side mirror.", "Look into the rear-view mirror.", "Look over your shoulder in the direction you plan to move."], "question": "When you change lanes:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 188}
{"candidates": ["immediately upon entering the deceleration lane", "as you approach the deceleration lane", "about halfway through the deceleration lane"], "question": "You are preparing to exit an expressway. When should you start reducing speed?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 189}
{"candidates": ["An intersection.", "A bridge.", "A tunnel."], "question": "Which of the following road surfaces freezes first?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 190}
{"candidates": ["Slow down to watch the workers", "Pass the construction zone carefully and not \u201crubberneck\u201d.", "Decrease your following distance"], "question": "When you drive through a construction zone, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 191}
{"candidates": ["Low beams", "Parking lights", "High beams"], "question": "When following another vehicle you should use:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 192}
{"candidates": ["Other drivers when merging onto a freeway.", "Other drivers when they want to slow down.", "The truck driver to stop the vehicle."], "question": "The extra space in front of a large truck is needed for:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 194}
{"candidates": ["Prevents rear-end collisions", "Improves traffic flow by preventing collisions", "Causes traffic congestion"], "question": "Slowing down just to look at collisions or anything else out of the ordinary:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 195}
{"candidates": ["Directly in front of the car", "At the middle of the road", "Beside, ahead and to the rear of the car"], "question": "A driver should always be looking:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 196}
{"candidates": ["15", "5", "10"], "question": "You just sold your vehicle. You must notify the DMV within ____ days.", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 200}
{"candidates": ["Using your high beam lights in the fog", "Starring at the road ahead of your vehicle", "Checking your rearview mirrors frequently"], "question": "Which of these is a safe driving technique", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 212}
{"candidates": ["Interfere with traffic and receive a ticket", "Demonstrate defensive driving techniques", "Improve traffic flow"], "question": "If you drive slower than the flow of traffic, you will most likely", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 213}
{"candidates": ["Vehicle speed and distance are harder to judge", "The speed limit is increased at night", "There are fewer cars on the roads at night"], "question": "Night driving poses special problems for drivers because:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 215}
{"candidates": ["Time", "Strong coffee", "Cold shower"], "question": "What is the only effective way to remove alcohol from the body?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 217}
{"candidates": ["The inside rearview mirror", "Over your shoulders", "The outside rearview mirror"], "question": "To see vehicles in your blind spot, you should check:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 218}
{"candidates": ["passing is permitted on the side of the broken yellow line", "passing is not permitted in either direction", "passing is permitted on the side of the solid yellow line"], "question": "A broken yellow line beside a solid yellow line indicates:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 219}
{"candidates": ["Flash your headlights once quickly", "Keep your high beam headlights on", "Look in the direction of their vehicle"], "question": "When driving at night and a vehicle comes toward you with their high beam headlights on:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 220}
{"candidates": ["The lane nearest the center of the street", "The lane nearest the right curb.", "The lane nearest the left curb."], "question": "Which lane must you be in before making a left turn from a one-way street?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 224}
{"candidates": ["yield", "warning", "stop"], "question": "A diamond shaped sign means:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 225}
{"candidates": ["Diamond or rectangular with orange and black coloring", "Square or rectangular with white red coloring", "Round of octagon with black and yellow coloring"], "question": "Construction zone signs are generally", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 227}
{"candidates": ["stop only if pedestrians are on the sidewalk area.", "drivers should increase speed to get into the flow of traffic safely.", "stop before driving onto the sidewalk to sidewalk area."], "question": "When leaving alleys or driveways:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 229}
{"candidates": ["A sign permits the turn.", "Traffic on the street moves to the left.", "Traffic on the street moves to the right."], "question": "You are driving on a one-way street. You may turn left onto another one-way street only if:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 234}
{"candidates": ["Anything that causes you to pay more attention to driving", "Anything that takes your attention away from driving", "Anything that causes evasive action while driving"], "question": "A driver distraction is:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 240}
{"candidates": ["Proceed to the next exit where you can re-enter the freeway and return to your proper exit.", "Continue on the freeway and find an alternative route.", "Back up on the road or shoulder."], "question": "If you miss your exit on a freeway, you should NOT:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 241}
{"candidates": ["Drive at the same speed as the vehicle you are passing", "Pass the vehicle as slowly as possible", "Pass the vehicle as safely and as quickly as possible"], "question": "When passing another vehicle:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 242}
{"candidates": ["rate of alcohol consumption (RAC)", "blood alcohol concentration (BAC)", "implied consent (IC)"], "question": "The amount of alcohol in the blood is referred to as:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 243}
{"candidates": ["Use the acceleration lane to blend into the traffic.", "Go down to the bottom of the ramp and stop until it is safe to enter the expressway.", "Go down the ramp and cross over to the traffic lane as soon as possible."], "question": "What is the proper way to enter an expressway from the entrance ramp?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 244}
{"candidates": ["Honk your horn to let them know you are there", "The pedestrian must yield the right-of-way", "You must yield the right-of-way to them"], "question": "If you see a pedestrian using a guide dog or carrying a white cane:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 245}
{"candidates": ["Balance", "Judgment and skills", "Vision"], "question": "The first thing that a drink of alcohol effects is:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 247}
{"candidates": ["You should prepare to stop and give the right of way to oncoming traffic", "You should speed up so you can make the turn before the light changes", "You do not need to signal to turn from that lane"], "question": "A yellow arrow on a traffic signal means:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 248}
{"candidates": ["Turn off your engine until the person crosses the street", "Wait until the person crosses the street", "Tell the pedestrian when to cross the street"], "question": "You want to make a right turn at the corner. A pedestrian with a guide dog is at the corner ready to cross the street in front of you. Before making your right turn, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 250}
{"candidates": ["Will double your chances of having an accident", "Won't affect your driving that much", "Won't have any effect on your driving"], "question": "A blood alcohol of .02", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 251}
{"candidates": ["high beam headlights", "low beam headlights", "parking lights"], "question": "To improve visibility caused by rain or fog, drivers should use:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 252}
{"candidates": ["Always use your high beams", "Increase your following distance", "Look directly at the headlights on the oncoming vehicle"], "question": "When driving at night you should", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 253}
{"candidates": ["Are not affected by vehicle speed", "Increase as vehicle speed increases", "Decrease as vehicle speed increases"], "question": "Stopping distances and severity of crashes", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 254}
{"candidates": ["Speed up", "Slow down", "Maintain a constant speed"], "question": "When being passed by another vehicle:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 255}
{"candidates": ["The road is probably more slippery at night.", "Your reaction time is slower at night.", "You cannot see as far ahead at night."], "question": "It is more dangerous to drive at night than in daytime, because:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 256}
{"candidates": ["it is safe to use your cruise control", "make speed and directional changes more gradually", "drive as you would in normal conditions"], "question": "When driving in snow or ice conditions:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 257}
{"candidates": ["Make sure the pedestrian can see you before proceeding", "Stop and let the pedestrian finish crossing", "cautiously drive around the pedestrian"], "question": "If there is no crosswalk and you see a pedestrian crossing your lane, you should", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 258}
{"candidates": ["Turned to the left (toward the street).", "Turned to the right (away from the street).", "Parallel with the pavement."], "question": "When parking uphill on a two-way street with no curb, your front wheels should be:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 259}
{"candidates": ["Report the accident without delay to the city police or, in unincorporated areas, to the CHP.", "Leave a note on the vehicle.", "Both of the above."], "question": "You have been involved in a minor traffic collision with a parked vehicle and you can`t find the owner. You must:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 263}
{"candidates": ["A speed which matches the flow of traffic.", "The posted speed limit.", "A speed just below the posted speed limit."], "question": "When merging on to the interstate(freeway) you must accelerate to:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 264}
{"candidates": ["Slow down because the lane ends ahead.", "Change lanes and maintain your current speed.", "Be prepared for workers and equipment ahead"], "question": "If you see orange construction signs and cones on a freeway, you must:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 271}
{"candidates": ["In both directions may pass", "Next to the solid line may pass", "Next to the broken line may pass"], "question": "A solid yellow line next to a broken yellow line means that vehicles", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 272}
{"candidates": ["Increase your speed to get through as quickly as possible", "Reduce your speed and be prepared to stop suddenly", "Maintain your speed the while way through the zone"], "question": "In work zones, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 273}
{"candidates": ["Decrease as vehicle speed increases", "Are not affected by vehicle speed", "Increase as vehicle speed increases"], "question": "Stopping distances and severity of crashes:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 274}
{"candidates": ["Areas of the road that cannot be seen even when looking into your mirrors. Check over your shoulders to avoid hitting vehicles that are in your blind spots when you change lanes.", "Spots in your vision when you become fatigued.", "Traffic control devices."], "question": "Blind spots are:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 275}
{"candidates": ["Help you to be a better driver", "Impair your judgment", "Make you feel better"], "question": "Just like alcohol and other drugs, driving while drowsy can:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 277}
{"candidates": ["Spray from large trucks reduce visibility", "Tires lose contact with the road surface", "Windshield wipers cannot keep the windshield clear of rain"], "question": "When a vehicle is hydroplaning the:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 278}
{"candidates": ["Turn left and find another route", "Stay out of the intersection until traffic clears", "Enter the intersection and wait"], "question": "If you have a green light, but the path ahead is blocked, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 280}
{"candidates": ["Another vehicle is in your way", "Another driver makes a mistake", "It may help prevent a collision"], "question": "You should use your horn when:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 281}
{"candidates": ["Speed up to clear traffic.", "Drive slowly until it has passed.", "Pull to the right and stop."], "question": "On an undivided highway when an emergency vehicle approaches with its siren and/or flashing lights on, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 283}
{"candidates": ["consult your doctor about the effects before driving", "keep your window open and drive more slowly", "have someone follow you home"], "question": "When taking any medicine, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 284}
{"candidates": ["75", "100", "50"], "question": "You are about to make a left turn. You must signal continuously during the last ____ feet before the turn.", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 292}
{"candidates": ["Relax and concentrate on driving", "Tailgate the driver in front of you", "Drive above the posted speed limit"], "question": "To prevent yourself from becoming an aggressive driver:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 303}
{"candidates": ["Always, even if the pedestrian is not obeying traffic controls", "Only when the pedestrian is in the crosswalk", "Only if the traffic lights are in the pedestrian's favor"], "question": "You have to yield to a pedestrian:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 306}
{"candidates": ["Press on the brake pedal as hard as you can.", "Rapidly pump the brake pedal several times.", "Slow down gradually and do not brake."], "question": "If you are driving and a tire suddenly goes flat:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 307}
{"candidates": ["The light will reflect back into your eyes.", "Vehicles behind you may follow too closely.", "Approaching vehicles might not see you."], "question": "When driving in fog or mist, never put your headlights on high beam because:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 308}
{"candidates": ["turn your lights on and off", "look toward the right edge of the road", "switch your lights to the high beam"], "question": "When driving at night, if the oncoming lights are blinding you, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 310}
{"candidates": ["the immediate left of the cab", "Both the immediate left of the cab and directly behind the body", "directly behind the body"], "question": "The blind spots where trucks will not be able to see you are:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 311}
{"candidates": ["Do it fast", "Rely only on your rear-view mirror", "Always look through the rear window"], "question": "When you back up:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 312}
{"candidates": ["Pump the brakes", "Use the brakes lightly", "Apply the brakes firmly"], "question": "If you have a sudden tire blow out:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 313}
{"candidates": ["Reserved for passengers pick up or drop off", "No parking or stopping", "Loading zone"], "question": "A curb painted red means:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 316}
{"candidates": ["you wait until the light changes", "you are in the proper lane and the roadway is clear", "you make a complete stop first"], "question": "At a red traffic light with a green arrow, you may proceed in the direction of the arrow if:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 317}
{"candidates": ["Always put one car length between you and the car ahead.", "Look only at the car in front of you while driving.", "Keep your eyes moving to look for possible hazards."], "question": "Which is NOT a feature of an interchange?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 327}
{"candidates": ["Every five hours.", "Every two hours.", "No need to take a rest."], "question": "When going on a long trip, how often should you take rest stops?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 328}
{"candidates": ["Ignore other drivers on the roadway", "Treat others the way you want to be treated", "Drive aggressively"], "question": "The golden rule of driving is to:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 331}
{"candidates": ["0.1", "0.04", "0.08"], "question": "If you are over ____ blood alcohol concentration (BAC), you are in violation of the law.", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 332}
{"candidates": ["Turn off the ignition", "Ease up on the gas pedal", "Brake as hard as possible"], "question": "If your vehicle begins to skid, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 333}
{"candidates": ["Passing is prohibited on both sides", "Passing is permitted on both sides", "Passing is permitted on your side"], "question": "A yellow dashed line on your side of the roadway only means:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 334}
{"candidates": ["Slow down", "Apply the brakes as soon as the car starts to skid", "Keep a constant speed"], "question": "To avoid hydroplaning, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 336}
{"candidates": ["Only when you are slowing down", "Often to see how traffic is moving behind you", "To see if a vehicle is in your blind spot"], "question": "Check your rearview mirrors:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 337}
{"candidates": ["Another name for a 4-way intersection", "The area where pedestrians may cross the roadway", "An area designated for road construction workers"], "question": "What is a crosswalk?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 339}
{"candidates": ["Allow more following distance", "Be ready to use the horn", "Drive more slowly"], "question": "When you are behind a motorcycle, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 341}
{"candidates": ["Keep your eyes moving to look for possible hazards.", "Look only at the car in front of you while driving.", "Always put one car length between you and the car ahead."], "question": "You drive defensively when you:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 342}
{"candidates": ["Left", "Left, right, then left again", "Right"], "question": "Before you enter an intersection, you should look:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 345}
{"candidates": ["Transporting an unrestrained animal inside the vehicle.", "Listening to music through headphones that cover both ears", "Adjusting your outside mirrors."], "question": "All of the following practices are dangerous to do while driving. Which of these is also illegal?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 346}
{"candidates": ["May have to swing wide to complete the right turn.", "May complete its turn in either of the two lanes.", "Must stay in the right lane at all times while turning."], "question": "A large truck is ahead of you and is turning right onto a street with two lanes in each direction. The truck:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 354}
{"candidates": ["reduce you speed and proceed carefully through the intersection", "come to a safe stop", "speed up to beat the red light"], "question": "You are approaching an intersection with a traffic signal indicating a steady yellow light. If you have not already entered the intersection, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 360}
{"candidates": ["At night or if it is raining", "When the roads are slippery", "All the others."], "question": "You should increase your following distance", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 362}
{"candidates": ["Continue driving so you will reach your destination sooner", "Find a safe parking area to take a 15 to 20 minute nap", "Drive late at night when there are not as many users on the roadway"], "question": "To prevent a fatigue-related crash while driving:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 363}
{"candidates": ["drinking several cups of coffee", "waiting several hours", "taking a cold shower"], "question": "If you have had several beers before driving, the effects of alcohol will be reduced only by:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 364}
{"candidates": ["You are only allowed to make right turns in this area", "You are not allowed to pass in this area.", "You are in a \u201cpassing zone\u201d and it is safe to pass other vehicles if no oncoming traffic is present."], "question": "The center of the roadway is marked with one solid yellow line and one broken yellow line. If the broken yellow line is on the right of the solid yellow line (your side) it means:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 366}
{"candidates": ["Separate lanes of traffic moving in opposite directions.", "Separate lanes of traffic moving in the same direction.", "Indicate no passing zones."], "question": "Broken yellow lines (dashes) are used on streets and highways to:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 368}
{"candidates": ["low beam headlights", "emergency flashers", "parking lights"], "question": "To help others see you when daylight begins to fade, you should use your:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 369}
{"candidates": ["reduce your speed, and proceed with caution", "You must come to a complete stop, yield to oncoming traffic or pedestrians, then proceed", "you must come to a complete stop and remain stopped as long as the light is red"], "question": "When approaching an intersection with a flashing red light:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 370}
{"candidates": ["allowed only in your direction of travel", "allowed in both directions", "not allowed in either direction"], "question": "Roads with double solid yellow line markings in the center indicate that passing is:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 372}
{"candidates": ["Assume the other driver will let you pass if you use your turn signal.", "Not assume the other driver will make space for you to return to your lane.", "Assume the other driver will maintain a constant speed."], "question": "If you plan to pass another vehicle, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 377}
{"candidates": ["Passing is not permitted", "Both lanes of traffic are going in the same direction", "Passing is permitted when it's safe"], "question": "A broken yellow line between two lanes of traffic means", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 392}
{"candidates": ["Drive in low gear", "Steer and brake smoothly", "Steer off the road"], "question": "In inclement weather, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 393}
{"candidates": ["Look farther ahead.", "Put on your headlights.", "Drive with both hands on steering wheel."], "question": "As your speed increases it is most important to:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 397}
{"candidates": ["leave straight", "toward the curb", "away from the curb"], "question": "If you park facing up hill where there is a curb, set the parking brake and turn the wheels:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 400}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "you are approaching a school or school crosswalk", "slow down, drive with caution and watch for children"], "question": "he yellow warning sign shown means:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 401}
{"candidates": ["Slow down and be prepared to stop", "Stop regardless of your direction of travel", "Stop if you are driving in the same direction"], "question": "A school bus is picking up or dropping off children, you must:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 405}
{"candidates": ["Cannot see the vehicle directly to your right.", "Have passed the other vehicle\u2019s front bumper.", "See the vehicle\u2019s headlights in your rear view mirror"], "question": "When passing another vehicle, it is safe to return to your lane if you:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 406}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "Reaction time and coordination", "Alertness and concentration"], "question": "Which of the following driving skills are affected by the use of alcohol and/or drugs?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 422}
{"candidates": ["time", "drinking caffeine", "eating foods high in fat"], "question": "Only ____ can reduce the alcohol level and the effects from the body.", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 423}
{"candidates": ["Increases your ability to react to a hazard", "Does not increase the chance of a crash", "Often leads to high-risk decision-making"], "question": "Excessive speed:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 425}
{"candidates": ["2", "1", "3"], "question": "How many alcoholic drinks does it take to effect your driving ability", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 427}
{"candidates": ["maintain your normal speed.", "slow and proceed with caution.", "you must come to a complete stop at the intersection."], "question": "When approaching an intersection with a flashing yellow light:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 428}
{"candidates": ["Visibility ahead is limited", "You may hit another vehicle", "Near blind pedestrians"], "question": "You should not use your horn when", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 429}
{"candidates": ["Always stop, whether there\u2019s a stop sign or not.", "Watch for children and be ready to stop.", "Always sound your horn when you see children."], "question": "At a school crossing sign, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 431}
{"candidates": ["5 to 10 MPH slower than the traffic on the freeway.", "At or near the same speed as the traffic on the freeway.", "The posted speed limit for traffic on the freeway."], "question": "When you are merging onto the freeway, you should be driving:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 441}
{"candidates": ["Check the inside rearview mirror", "Look over your shoulder to make sure the lane is clear", "Slow down"], "question": "When changing lanes:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 451}
{"candidates": ["Your low beams", "Parking lights", "Your high beams"], "question": "When following another vehicle at night you should use:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 452}
{"candidates": ["Not turn in that direction until the light turns green", "Turn in that direction after slowing and checking traffic", "Turn in that direction after you come to a complete stop"], "question": "A red arrow pointing to the right on a traffic light means you may", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 453}
{"candidates": ["Getting adequate rest and staying alert", "Exceeding the posted speed limit and driving too fast for conditions or circumstances", "Scanning the environment and staying focused on the driving task"], "question": "Which of the below are common factors contributing to traffic crashes?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 454}
{"candidates": ["Look ahead towards the right edge of your lane", "Look ahead towards the left edge of your lane", "Look straight ahead in your lane"], "question": "It is night. A vehicle coming towards you has its high beams on which make it hard to see the road ahead, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 456}
{"candidates": ["May not proceed until it changes to green", "Must treat the intersection the same as a stop sign", "Are traveling in the wrong direction"], "question": "If you approach a flashing red traffic light, you:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 457}
{"candidates": ["Four-way flashers", "High beam headlights", "Low beam headlights"], "question": "When driving in fog, it is best to drive with:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 458}
{"candidates": ["During rush hour traffic.", "Under no circumstances.", "When you entered the intersection on the green light."], "question": "You may legally block an intersection:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 459}
{"candidates": ["Using the side mirror and looking over your shoulder", "Using the inside mirror", "Using both the inside and outside mirrors"], "question": "You are entering a freeway. You should check traffic on the freeway by:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 461}
{"candidates": ["Give notice of routes you're driving on.", "Give notice of requirements, prohibitions or restrictions.", "Give notice of service ahead."], "question": "What is the function of the regulatory signs?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 477}
{"candidates": ["5 to 10 seconds", "15 to 20 seconds", "10 to 15 seconds"], "question": "Any resident who operates a motor vehicle must have a driver's license, which of the following is the only exception?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 478}
{"candidates": ["can be a problem for all vehicles", "generally affect only the movement of large vehicles", "cause only visual problems because of dust and dirt blowing around"], "question": "Sudden wind gusts on highways:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 480}
{"candidates": ["Green", "White", "Yellow"], "question": "Regulatory signs are:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 481}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "coordination", "alertness"], "question": "Which of the following driving skills is/are affected by the use of alcohol and/or drugs?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 482}
{"candidates": ["Partially enter the intersection to establish your right of way", "Continue into the intersection and wait for traffic to clear", "Don't enter the intersection until you can get completely across"], "question": "You are approaching a green traffic light, but traffic is blocking the intersection. What is the best thing to do?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 486}
{"candidates": ["You may change lanes only if in the left lane", "You must stay within your lane", "You may cross it to change lanes"], "question": "While driving on a roadway with single broken white line markings:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 487}
{"candidates": ["Vehicle in front of you moves to the right to let you pass", "Yellow line next to the other side of the road is broken", "Yellow line next to your side of the road is broken"], "question": "You may cross double yellow lines to pass another vehicle if the", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 488}
{"candidates": ["Reduce speed.", "Do not pass.", "Traffic light ahead."], "question": "A solid yellow line, on your side of the center line, means:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 489}
{"candidates": ["Blind spots can be checked by looking in your rear view mirrors.", "Large trucks have bigger blind spots than most passenger vehicles.", "They are eliminated if you have one outside mirror on each side of the vehicle."], "question": "Which of the following statements about blind spots is true?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 490}
{"candidates": ["According to road and weather conditions.", "At the speed limit.", "At the speed of vehicles in front of you."], "question": "You should always travel:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 494}
{"candidates": ["The number of passengers in their car", "Their tendency to drive slow", "Erratic and improper lane changes"], "question": "You can identify aggressive drivers by:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 498}
{"candidates": ["At least 30 feet but not more than 100 feet from the nearest track", "A maximum of 50 feet and a minimum of 15 feet from the nearest railroad track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 50 feet from the nearest track"], "question": "At what distance should you stop when you see active crossing devices at the railroad crossing?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 507}
{"candidates": ["Knowledge", "Judgment and physical coordination", "Right-of-way privileges"], "question": "Any amount of alcohol in the blood may affect a driver's:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 510}
{"candidates": ["Speed up", "Reduce your speed", "Stay at the posted speed"], "question": "If the roadway is wet or icy you should", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 511}
{"candidates": ["tranquilizers, marijuana and sedatives", "All the others.", "cough syrups and cold tablets containing codeine or antihistamines"], "question": "Which of the following substances can affect the ability to drive?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 513}
{"candidates": ["turn back onto the roadway immediately", "wait until it is safe to do so, then turn gradually back onto the roadway", "stop"], "question": "Should your wheels drop off the roadway or pavement edge, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 515}
{"candidates": ["construction and maintenance warning", "general warning", "regulatory"], "question": "Signs with orange backgrounds mean:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 516}
{"candidates": ["Adjust the seat to a reclining position", "Kick the tires", "Properly adjust your seat and mirrors"], "question": "When preparing to drive, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 518}
{"candidates": ["Farther behind the truck than for a passenger vehicle", "Closer behind the truck than for a passenger vehicle", "To the right side of the truck and wait to pass"], "question": "You are driving on the freeway behind a large truck, You should drive", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 519}
{"candidates": ["Speed up slightly", "Keep a steady speed", "That it is not safe to pass"], "question": "Sign and lane markings that say \"No passing zone\" tell you:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 520}
{"candidates": ["Play in the steering", "Squealing brakes", "Vehicle control problems"], "question": "If your car's suspension is bad, it can cause:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 521}
{"candidates": ["Keep traffic out of hazardous work zones", "Make drivers drive slower and get angry", "Primarily inconvenience drivers"], "question": "In work zones, barriers, such as drums cones and tunes are used to:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 522}
{"candidates": ["stop in the right lane", "park with all four wheels off the traveled highway, if possible", "stop where you are"], "question": "If your car becomes disabled on the highway, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 523}
{"candidates": ["Prepare to stop if needed", "Keep a steady speed", "Speed up slightly"], "question": "As you approach the top of a hill, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 524}
{"candidates": ["You may turn in that direction after you come to a complete stop", "You cannot turn in that direction", "You may turn in that direction"], "question": "A red arrow on a traffic light means:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 525}
{"candidates": ["Increase your chances of an accident.", "Help prevent traffic congestion.", "Get you to your destination much faster and safer."], "question": "If you drive faster than other vehicles on a road with one lane in each direction and continually pass the other cars, you will:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 526}
{"candidates": ["15 to 20 seconds", "5 to 10 seconds", "10 to 15 seconds"], "question": "To avoid last minute moves, you should be looking down the road to where your vehicle will be in about ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 528}
{"candidates": ["No faster than 65 mph.", "70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic.", "Between 65 mph and 70 mph."], "question": "You are driving on a freeway posted for 65 MPH. The traffic is traveling at 70 MPH. You may legally drive:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 532}
{"candidates": ["Signal for 100 feet before turning.", "Move toward the left side of your lane.", "Avoid driving in the bicycle lane."], "question": "You want to make a right turn at an upcoming intersection. You should slow down and:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 533}
{"candidates": ["That vehicles may pass in all directions.", "That only vehicles next to the broken line may pass.", "That vehicles next to the solid yellow line may pass."], "question": "If you see a solid yellow line next to a broken yellow line this means:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 534}
{"candidates": ["Slow down and cross carefully", "Wait for the green light", "Stop before crossing"], "question": "When you come to a flashing yellow light, you must:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 540}
{"candidates": ["passing is permitted on the right.", "passing is not allowed in either direction.", "passing is permitted on the left."], "question": "When double solid yellow lines mark the center of the road and separate oncoming traffic:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 542}
{"candidates": ["During the first half hour of rain.", "A half hour after it stops raining.", "After it has been raining all day."], "question": "When it is raining, you should be most careful when turning or stopping:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 544}
{"candidates": ["Hold the steering wheel tightly and use the brakes lightly", "Apply the brake and hold it", "Pull over quickly"], "question": "If a tire blows out, you should", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 546}
{"candidates": ["On long trips", "All the time", "On high-speed highways"], "question": "When in a vehicle, wear a seat belt:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 547}
{"candidates": ["Next to each other on the top of the steering wheel", "On opposite sides of the steering wheel", "On the top and bottom of the wheel"], "question": "To be able to turn quickly, your hands must be:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 549}
{"candidates": ["You are on a road with a solid line on your side of the road", "You are on a hill or curve", "There is a broken line on your side of the road"], "question": "You can pass a vehicle ahead if it safe to do so when:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 550}
{"candidates": ["Yield to pedestrians and bicyclist crossing before entering the roundabout", "Both", "Yield to any car coming from your left in the roundabout"], "question": "As you enter into the roundabout you should slow down", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 552}
{"candidates": ["Sleeping", "Working hard", "Drinking alcohol"], "question": "Reaction time is slower after", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 553}
{"candidates": ["Blow your horn to make the motorcycle move onto the shoulder so that you can pass.", "Stay in the right lane as much as possible, because the motorcycle is small and doesn't use all of the lane.", "Have your vehicle entirely into the left lane before and during the pass."], "question": "You are driving behind a motorcycle and want to pass. You must:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 571}
{"candidates": ["Look straight ahead", "Look toward the center of the roadway", "Look toward the right side of the road"], "question": "If the driver of an oncoming vehicle fails to dim the lights:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 573}
{"candidates": ["Drive with your window partly down.", "Accelerate heavily.", "Watch for things in the roadway well ahead of you."], "question": "To avoid panic stops:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 574}
{"candidates": ["stay in the center lane", "move to the lane on your left", "move to the lane on your right"], "question": "If you are continually being passed on the right and the left while driving in the center lane of an expressway, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 576}
{"candidates": ["During the day", "During the night", "In ideal conditions"], "question": "The maximum posted speed limit should be driven only:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 578}
{"candidates": ["As long as it takes to safely pass another vehicle", "Never", "If you don't see any other traffic in your lane"], "question": "When is it OK to drive faster than the posted speed limit?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 579}
{"candidates": ["The bed of a pick-up truck", "The back seat", "The front seat"], "question": "The safest place for children 12 and under to ride in a vehicle equipped with air bags is:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 580}
{"candidates": ["As long as it takes to safely pass another vehicle", "Never", "If you feel it is reasonable and prudent"], "question": "When is it legal to drive faster than the posted speed limit?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 581}
{"candidates": ["Watch only the vehicles behind the gap", "Speed up and let vehicles make way", "Check behind, then watch the vehicle ahead"], "question": "To enter a gap in a highway traffic:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 582}
{"candidates": ["proceed at normal speed, but watch for children", "proceed at 15 mph if no children are present", "stop"], "question": "If you meet a stopped school bus with the lights flashing and the signal arm extended, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 584}
{"candidates": ["Drive slowly enough so you can stop within the area lighted by your headlights.", "Keep the instrument panel lights bright to be more visible to other\tdrivers.", "Turn on your high beam headlights to better see the vehicles ahead of you."], "question": "When driving at night on a dimly lit street, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 585}
{"candidates": ["Slow down, stop all wireless telephone communications and yield the right-of-way.", "Honk their horn several times to alert individuals working in the area of their presence.", "Increase their speed to get out of the way quickly."], "question": "What should drivers do when approaching a construction area?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 601}
{"candidates": ["Decrease the distance you look ahead of your vehicle", "Avoid making fast turns and fast stops.", "Test your tires' traction while going uphill."], "question": "Roads are slippery after it first starts to rain. When the road is slippery you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 603}
{"candidates": ["No, you can block traffic when you drive too slowly.", "Yes, it is a good defensive driving technique.", "Yes, it is always safer than driving faster than other traffic."], "question": "Should you always drive slower than other traffic?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 607}
{"candidates": ["Overtaking cars.", "Oncoming cars.", "No Cars"], "question": "Drivers turning left must yield to:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 608}
{"candidates": ["stay within that speed range", "drive a few miles per hour faster than most", "drive a few miles per hour slower than most"], "question": "In 50-55 mph traffic you are least likely to have an accident if you:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 611}
{"candidates": ["Drive at a constant speed", "Apply the brakes firmly", "Slow down"], "question": "To avoid traction loss from hydroplaning, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 612}
{"candidates": ["Oncoming traffic and pedestrians should yield to you", "You should never yield to oncoming traffic and pedestrians", "You should always yield to oncoming traffic and pedestrians"], "question": "When turning left at an intersection:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 615}
{"candidates": ["Drive slowly enough so you can stop within the area lighted by your headlights.", "Keep the instrument panel lights bright to be more visible to other\tdrivers.", "Turn on your high beam headlights to better see the vehicles ahead of you."], "question": "What should you do if you miss your freeway off-ramp?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 627}
{"candidates": ["Always keep your eyes focused ahead of your car", "Turn off the radio", "Know what is happening around your vehicle"], "question": "The best way to avoid a dangerous situation when driving is to:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 659}
{"candidates": ["Any amount", "0.15% or more", "0.08% or more"], "question": "Your license can be suspended if you are under 21 and drive with a blood alcohol level of:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 660}
{"candidates": ["When the driver you just passed signals you over", "When you can see both headlights in the rearview mirror", "When you look over your shoulder and see the car is behind you"], "question": "When passing another car, you have enough room to return to the driving lane:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 663}
{"candidates": ["See both headlights of the passed vehicle in your rear view mirror", "Beep your horn", "Flash your headlights"], "question": "Before returning to the original lane after passing another vehicle, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 665}
{"candidates": ["use your low beam headlights.", "use your parking lights.", "use your high beam headlights."], "question": "When driving in fog, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 666}
{"candidates": ["pull your vehicle as far to the right as possible without leaving the pavement", "stay in your lane and reduce speed", "stay in your lane and maintain speed unless there is an emergency"], "question": "When another vehicle is passing you:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 668}
{"candidates": ["Reduce your speed", "Activate your turn signal", "Brake hard"], "question": "Prior to entering a curve:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 672}
{"candidates": ["Drive onto the left shoulder to let the other vehicles pass", "Stay in your lane so you don't impede the traffic flow", "Move over into the right lane when it is safe"], "question": "There are two traffic lanes in your direction. You are driving in the left lane and many vehicles are passing you on the right. If the driver behind you wishes to drive faster, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 674}
{"candidates": ["More sober", "More intoxicated", "More coordinated"], "question": "As the percentage of alcohol (BAC) in your blood increases, you become:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 675}
{"candidates": ["Headlights.", "Parking lights", "Emergency flashers"], "question": "If you have trouble seeing other vehicles because of dust or smoke blowing across the roadway, you should drive slower and turn on your:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 679}
{"candidates": ["Turn your wheels sharply towards the side of the road.", "Turn your wheels away from the side of the road.", "Keep your wheels straight."], "question": "When you park on a hill, with the vehicle heading down the hill:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 680}
{"candidates": ["Whenever signs and/or roadway markings permit passing other vehicles", "When entering a curve and there are no oncoming vehicles", "When driving through an intersection and there are no oncoming vehicles"], "question": "When is it safe to pass another vehicle?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 690}
{"candidates": ["try to squeeze around the truck when the truck makes a wide turn and when several car lengths have been left between the large truck and car", "have sufficient space when traveling behind trucks and when consistent speed has been maintained by the car when passing trucks", "disappear into blind spots or are so close they restrict the truck driver's ability to stop or maneuver safely"], "question": "No Zones are areas around trucks where cars:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 694}
{"candidates": ["Must stop for them", "Do not have to stop for them", "Should honk your horn at them"], "question": "If a pedestrian is crossing in the middle of the street, not at a crosswalk (also known as jaywalking) even if it is illegal, you:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 696}
{"candidates": ["Your side of the road is a broken line.", "The other side of the road is a solid line.", "The other side of the road is a broken line."], "question": "You may cross a double, yellow line to pass another vehicle, if the yellow line next to:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 698}
{"candidates": ["If you are under the legal blood alcohol concentration limit, your driving isn't impaired", "If you can walk a straight line after drinking, it is safe to drive", "Alcohol affects judgement, which is needed for driving safely"], "question": "Which of these statements is true about drinking alcohol and driving?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 701}
{"candidates": ["proceed into the lane, since you have the right-of-way", "merge carefully into that gap", "wait for the lane to be clear"], "question": "When entering the interstate, you should check for a gap in traffic in the nearest lane, adjust your speed to meet that gap, signal and:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 702}
{"candidates": ["Unless the vehicle was built before 1978.", "Unless you are in a limousine.", "When the vehicle is equipped with seat belts."], "question": "Always use your seat belt:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 704}
{"candidates": ["20 mph", "25 mph", "15 mph"], "question": "You are approaching a railroad crossing with no warning devices and are unable to see 400 feet down the tracks in one direction. The speed limit is:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "permit", "id": 711}
{"candidates": ["You should wear brightly colored clothing", "You should wear dark-colored clothing", "You should wave your arms"], "question": "To make it easier to be seen by other motorists:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 719}
{"candidates": ["Slow down", "Increase your speed", "Lean the motorcycle"], "question": "If you have to ride over an object, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 720}
{"candidates": ["Ride in the center of the lane", "Ride in the tire tracks left by cars", "Pull off to the side until the rain stops"], "question": "When it starts to rain it is usually best to:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 721}
{"candidates": ["You should always ride in the left portion of the lane", "You should always ride in the right portion of the lane", "You should be flexible about lane position, depending on the curve"], "question": "When going through a curve:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 722}
{"candidates": ["Increase the following distance between your motorcycle and the vehicle in front of you if you are being tailgated.", "Make sure your turn signal turns off after you finish a turn.", "Use your horn only in emergency situations."], "question": "To avoid confusing other drivers you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 723}
{"candidates": ["Decreases", "Stays the same", "Increases"], "question": "As you consume more alcohol, your skill level ____", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 726}
{"candidates": ["Leather", "Wool", "Any soft material"], "question": "When wearing gloves for protection, the gloves should be made of:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 727}
{"candidates": ["Is shiny", "Fits snugly", "Looks good"], "question": "Whichever style you choose, you will get the most protection by ensuring a helmet:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 728}
{"candidates": ["The front tire affects your steering, which also affects your balance", "The front tire being flat will affect your ability to use the front brake", "The front tire being flat will prevent you from accelerating"], "question": "A front wheel that is flat is especially dangerous because:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 729}
{"candidates": ["Prevent the motorcycle from slowing down", "Be able to keep both hands on the handlegrips", "Prevent a change in power, which could cause the back tire to skid"], "question": "Before starting a turn, a motorcycle rider should change gears to:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 733}
{"candidates": ["It depends on road condition and traffic.", "The outside of the curve.", "The inside of the curve."], "question": "Where should you position your motorcycle when entering a curve:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 738}
{"candidates": ["Someone is following too closely", "You will be slowing suddenly", "There is a stop sign ahead"], "question": "It is MOST important to flash your brake light when:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 747}
{"candidates": ["Should be worn at night", "Should be worn day and night", "Should be worn during the day"], "question": "Reflective clothing:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 750}
{"candidates": ["Recommended only on long rides", "Recommended on all rides", "Not recommended"], "question": "Hearing protection is:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 751}
{"candidates": ["Keep the front wheel locked up until you come to a stop", "Release the front brake immediately and only use the rear brake", "Release the front brake immediately and re-apply"], "question": "If the front wheel locks up, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 752}
{"candidates": ["When it is light traffic", "When it is raining", "When it is sunny"], "question": "A larger cushion of space, or following distance, is needed:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 753}
{"candidates": ["there will be a jerk or sway from side to side.", "a discharge of air can usually be seen.", "the rider will usually hear a loud noise."], "question": "If the rear tire of a motorcycle suddenly goes flat, the rider may become aware of the flat tire because", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 754}
{"candidates": ["By avoiding high density traffic areas.", "To see it coming by looking well ahead.", "By increasing the following distance between your motorcycle and the vehicle in front of you."], "question": "What is the best way to stay out of trouble while riding a motorcycle?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 755}
{"candidates": ["Should only be used if you are sharing the lane with another vehicle", "Is safe to use, usually offering adequate traction, unless it is raining", "Should be avoided all the time"], "question": "The center portion of a lane contains an oily strip. This strip", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 756}
{"candidates": ["Left", "Right", "There is no single best lane position"], "question": "In general, what position within the lane is the best to drive in?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 757}
{"candidates": ["Speed up before contact with the object.", "Stay seated, so the seat can cushion some of the impact.", "Try to approach the obstacle at as close to a 90 degree angle as possible."], "question": "A motorcyclist should attempt to avoid an obstacle in the roadway. If that is not possible, the motorcyclist should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 758}
{"candidates": ["Not required, but recommended", "Required", "Only required for beginning motorcycle users"], "question": "Eye protection is", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 759}
{"candidates": ["more frequent", "less frequent", "about the same"], "question": "A motorcycle needs ____ attention than a car.", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 760}
{"candidates": ["Be sure the bike looks good.", "Check that the brake controls turn on the brake lights", "Ensure that paint is not peeling as the wind could cause it to peel more."], "question": "Before every ride you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 761}
{"candidates": ["Dark gray", "Yellow", "Brown"], "question": "Since most crashes happen in daylight, what would be a color to wear to increase your visibility?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 762}
{"candidates": ["More than three-quarters", "More than half", "About a quarter"], "question": "About how many motorcycle/passenger vehicle collisions are caused by drivers entering the motorcyclist\u2019s right of way?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 763}
{"candidates": ["Required", "Not required unless the driver has had their license for less than 2 years", "Optional, but recommended"], "question": "A helmet is:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 764}
{"candidates": ["Ride in the tire tracks left by other vehicles", "Pull off to the side and wait for it to stop raining", "Ride in the center of the lane"], "question": "When it starts to rain, it is usually best to:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 765}
{"candidates": ["Do both at the same time", "Only brake", "Do one, then the other, bit not both at the same time"], "question": "When you must brake and swerve to avoid a hazard, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 766}
{"candidates": ["Doesn\u2019t affect humans", "Is absorbed into the bloodstream right away", "Needs to be digested"], "question": "Unlike other beverages, alcohol", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 767}
{"candidates": ["Should not be used when entering or exiting a highway.", "Is recommended at all times.", "Should be used when riding on curves."], "question": "When riding with a group of motorcyclists, a staggered formation:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 768}
{"candidates": ["Stop until the animal loses interest.", "Approach the animal slowly, then accelerate briskly away from the dog as it approaches.", "Swerve around the animal."], "question": "If you are chased by a dog:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 769}
{"candidates": ["Motorcyclists running wide in a curve or turn and colliding with the roadway or a fixed object.", "Motorcyclists running off the road while trying to avoid a collision with another vehicle.", "Motorcyclists' tendency to drive too fast for weather conditions."], "question": "A primary cause of single vehicle motorcycle collisions is:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 770}
{"candidates": ["Center", "Right", "Left"], "question": "What part of the lane is usually the best place for a motorcyclist to be seen?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 771}
{"candidates": ["You don\u2019t need to wear bright-colored clothes", "You should wear bright-colored clothes", "Dark-colored clothes will increase visibility"], "question": "Since most crashes happen in daylight,", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 772}
{"candidates": ["The posted speed limit.", "A speed which matches the flow of traffic.", "A speed just below the posted speed limit."], "question": "Which of these is unacceptable for proper vehicle control?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 773}
{"candidates": ["Unless you are in a limousine.", "Unless the vehicle was built before 1978.", "When the vehicle is equipped with seat belts."], "question": "What is NOT something you need to do to avoid a crash?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 776}
{"candidates": ["Pass the construction zone carefully and not rubberneck.", "Slow down to watch the workers.", "Decrease your following distance."], "question": "What road condition or surface can increase your chances of a car crash?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 777}
{"candidates": ["Use both brakes at the same time.", "Use the front brake only.", "Use the rear brake first."], "question": "The best way to stop quickly is to:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 779}
{"candidates": ["Keep knees against the gas tank", "Use your arms to hold yourself up", "Sit so your arms are straight when reaching for the handlebars"], "question": "To control a motorcycle well, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 780}
{"candidates": ["Never hold onto the rider.", "Sit as far back as possible.", "Look over their shoulder in the direction of the turn or curve."], "question": "Passengers should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 781}
{"candidates": ["Drive on the left side of the lane", "Drive in the right portion of the lane", "Drive wherever you are comfortable, any part of the lane is acceptable"], "question": "When passing parked cars, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 782}
{"candidates": ["Denim", "Wool", "Leather or synthetic materials"], "question": "What type of material provides the best protection?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 783}
{"candidates": ["Help block the wind", "Be helpful for inexperienced riders", "Place you in their blind spot"], "question": "Driving alongside other vehicles can:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 784}
{"candidates": ["Depends on the situation.", "Staggered formation.", "Single-file formation."], "question": "What formation should you form when riding in a group?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 785}
{"candidates": ["To yield to oncoming traffic", "To proceed through the intersection with caution", "The same as a red traffic light"], "question": "What does a red arrow mean?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 786}
{"candidates": ["Motorcycle drivers don\u2019t have to worry about blind spots", "There are blind spots, but they are too small to matter.", "Motorcycle drivers have blind spots and must perform head checks"], "question": "With rear view mirrors,", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 787}
{"candidates": ["Not encouraged because you never get used to a part of the lane", "Discouraged because it confuses other motorists", "Encouraged to provide safe riding areas with changing situations"], "question": "Using all three positions within a lane is:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 788}
{"candidates": ["Use the front brake only.", "Use the rear brake only.", "Use both brakes."], "question": "When stopping, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 789}
{"candidates": ["Accelerate through the turn", "Lean into the turn", "Reduce your speed."], "question": "Which is not a method used to help maintain control of the motorcycle when entering a turn?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 792}
{"candidates": ["Not use artificial stimulants", "Try to go as far as you can in a single day", "Minimize stopping"], "question": "To stay safe on a long trip, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 793}
{"candidates": ["Cover your ankle", "Be below your ankle", "Be made of a soft, pliable material"], "question": "When riding a motorcycle, boots or shoes should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 794}
{"candidates": ["Keep knees away from the gas tank", "Should use their arms to steer, not support their body", "Sit far enough back that your arms are not bent when reaching the handle grip"], "question": "To control a motorcycle well, the driver:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 795}
{"candidates": ["It knows when to brake automatically by understanding your driving habits", "It link the front and rear brakes together when applying the rear brake", "It is connected to the gears and applies the brake when downshifting"], "question": "What does an Integrated braking system do?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 796}
{"candidates": ["a shoulder of the road", "Only if there is pavement at least eight feet wide allowing for safe passage.", "By driving on the grass if it is level"], "question": "Motorcycles may pass on the right, only if:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 798}
{"candidates": ["Within minutes of being consumed", "About an hour after being consumed", "About two hours after being consumed"], "question": "Alcohol begins to affect the body:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 800}
{"candidates": ["About one-half", "About one-quarter", "About three-quarters"], "question": "The front brake supplies about how much of the potential stopping power?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 801}
{"candidates": ["loose and smooth", "loose and rough", "tight and smooth"], "question": "Before riding, a motorcycle operator should check the clutch. A properly working clutch should feel:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 802}
{"candidates": ["Yield to pedestrians only in the intersection.", "Yield to any vehicle, bicycle, or pedestrian in the intersection.", "Wait four seconds before proceeding."], "question": "Which of the following is NOT suggested if you need to get off the road?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 806}
{"candidates": ["Sometimes the mirrors can be dirty, limiting your view", "Similar to other vehicles, motorcycles have blind spots.", "Mirrors are unreliable"], "question": "Why should a motorcyclist not rely on mirrors?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 811}
{"candidates": ["By the left footrest", "By the right footrest", "By the right handle grip"], "question": "The gearshift is located:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 812}
{"candidates": ["Make no adjustments for tire pressure", "Reduce the tire pressure", "Increase the tire pressure"], "question": "If you will have a passenger on your motorcycle, you will likely have to:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 813}
{"candidates": ["It gives you more time to react", "It limits your escape route options", "It gives you space to maneuver"], "question": "Which of the following is not a benefit of allowing a cushion of space between your vehicle and others?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 814}
{"candidates": ["noticing the other vehicle\u2019s tail lights bouncing up and down", "using the added visibility of the other vehicle to see the bumps", "looking at the bumper and trying to determine if it is bouncing"], "question": "When driving at night, and you are behind another vehicle, you can determine if there are bumps in the road by ____ .", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 815}
{"candidates": ["Not looking ahead for hazards", "Refraining from using turn signals as it might distract drivers", "Being visible to other drivers"], "question": "As a rider, you can lessen your chances of being involved in an accident by:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 816}
{"candidates": ["Turn your shoulders, but not your head", "Turn just your head, not your shoulders", "Turn your head and shoulders to get a better view"], "question": "When looking through a turn, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 817}
{"candidates": ["Gloves", "Pants", "Baseball cap"], "question": "Which of the following is not among the items recommended as protective apparel?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 818}
{"candidates": ["The mirrors have blindspots, and you should always turn your head to look", "The mirrors should not be used, except when parking", "The mirrors provide a perfect view, and you do not have to move your head"], "question": "On a motorcycle when using the rearview mirrors,", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 819}
{"candidates": ["Release the front brake immediately and then re-apply it", "Keep the tire locked up, as it will help you stop quicker", "Release the front brake and only use the rear brake"], "question": "If the front wheel locks during braking, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 820}
{"candidates": ["Left portion of the lane", "Right portion of the lane", "Center portion of the lane"], "question": "What lane position is best for being seen by drivers ahead of you and for minimizing the risk of other vehicles sharing your lane?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 821}
{"candidates": ["Move to a lane not nearest the emergency vehicle", "Stop on the roadway behind the emergency vehicle", "Stop and wait until the emergency vehicle leaves the scene"], "question": "If an emergency vehicle is on the side of the road with its lights on, what do you do?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 822}
{"candidates": ["You will have more time to accelerate when entering a curve", "You will have more space to maneuver", "You will have more time to react"], "question": "Which of the following is NOT a benefit of keeping a \u201ccushion of distance\u201d between you and other vehicles?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 823}
{"candidates": ["A motorcycle can accelerate faster than a car.", "A motorcycle rider can avoid the problems of opening doors and people stepping out from between vehicles by driving in the left part of the lane.", "Motorcycles have a shorter stopping distance."], "question": "A motorcycle rider has an advantage over an automobile driver when passing parked vehicles because:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 824}
{"candidates": ["Just as likely to survive as someone not wearing a helmet", "Less likely to survive than a person not wearing helmet", "Three times as likely to survive than a person not wearing helmet"], "question": "When wearing a helmet at the time of a crash, helmeted drivers are:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 826}
{"candidates": ["Yes, but only if the roadway has a lot of traffic", "No", "Yes, at any time"], "question": "Can motorcycles ride in pairs?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 827}
{"candidates": ["Required by law", "Not encouraged", "Not required, but recommended"], "question": "A plastic face shield is:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 828}
{"candidates": ["Allow them to get in front of you", "Speed up", "Make gestures at them"], "question": "A good way to handle a tailgater is to:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 830}
{"candidates": ["Lean the motorcycle in the direction of the curve", "Turn using the handle bars only.", "Slow down in the turn."], "question": "To execute a turn safely a motorcycle rider should always:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 831}
{"candidates": ["It is usually about the same in judging distance than during the day", "It is usually easier to judge distance than during the day", "It is usually more difficult to judge distance than during the day"], "question": "When driving at night,", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 832}
{"candidates": ["Right", "Either side", "Left"], "question": "If vehicles or other potential hazards are on your right side as you drive a motorcycle, what side of the lane would be the best to drive in?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 840}
{"candidates": ["How quickly the alcohol is consumed", "The amount of alcohol consumed", "How often a person consumes alcohol"], "question": "Which of the following is not a factor in determining Blood Alcohol Content?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 841}
{"candidates": ["be driven without a driver\u2019s license", "only be operated during the day", "be driven with any class of driver\u2019s license"], "question": "A motorized scooter can ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 842}
{"candidates": ["Keep your head and eyes up.", "Look down to see changes in the road surface.", "Stay to the left side of the lane."], "question": "When riding over scored or grooved pavement in a work zone:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 843}
{"candidates": ["Allow feet to hang off footrests", "Keep your knees against the side of the gas tank", "Sit so your arms hold you up"], "question": "To properly control a motorcycle, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 844}
{"candidates": ["In parking lots", "At intersections", "On the open road"], "question": "Most motorcycle/automobile accidents occur:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 846}
{"candidates": ["Yes. They provide a better grip and help protect your hands", "Yes. often your hands get cold when riding", "No. Gloves are not recommended as they can interfere with the controls."], "question": "Should you wear gloves when driving a motorcycle?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 847}
{"candidates": ["Neutral", "First gear", "Third gear"], "question": "What gear should the engine be in when starting the motorcycle?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 848}
{"candidates": ["Only the rear brake should be used", "Only the front brake should be used", "Both the front and rear brake should be applied at the same time"], "question": "When making a non-emergency brake on a motorcycle, :", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 849}
{"candidates": ["Change lanes and let them pass or slow down to allow for more space ahead.", "Ignore them.", "Speed up to put distance between you and the tailgater."], "question": "Usually a good way to handle tailgaters is to:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 850}
{"candidates": ["Allows you to most likely to be seen and you can maintain a space cushion around you.", "You like, without regard to others", "That gets you closest to other vehicles"], "question": "You should pick a lane position that:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 851}
{"candidates": ["louder", "about as loud as", "quieter"], "question": "A motorcycle\u2019s horn is ____ than other vehicles\u2019 horns", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 852}
{"candidates": ["Is that the other vehicle may block the escape route of the motorcyclist", "Is that he motorcyclist can be easily seen by other drivers", "Is the motorcyclist may not be able to read signs on the side of the road."], "question": "One problem with a motorcyclist driving alongside another vehicle,", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 853}
{"candidates": ["They provide wider view of the road", "They provide a narrower view of the road", "They provide a better view of the roadway"], "question": "How do convex mirrors, which are instaleld on some motorcycles, differ from regular mirrors?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 854}
{"candidates": ["Place you in other drivers\u2019 blind spots", "Increase your ability to see and be seen", "Invite others to use your lane"], "question": "A lane position should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 855}
{"candidates": ["Speed up and try to sneak through", "Cover clutch and brakes to reduce reaction time", "Select a lane position that increases your visibility"], "question": "As a motorcycle driver approaching an intersection, what should you NOT do?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 856}
{"candidates": ["The rear brake", "Both brakes are equally powerful", "The front brake"], "question": "Which brake is more powerful on a motorcycle?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 857}
{"candidates": ["release the front brake and only use the rear brake", "release the front brake and then re-apply the brake", "continue to apply the front brake"], "question": "When stopping suddenly, if the front wheel locks up, ____ .", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 858}
{"candidates": ["Passengers only are required to wear helmets.", "Helmets are not required while driving on city streets.", "All motorcycle riders and passengers are required to wear helmets at all times."], "question": "What are the requirements for wearing a helmet?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 859}
{"candidates": ["By driving slower", "By wearing a helmet", "By reading the owner\u2019s manual"], "question": "Head and neck injuries are reduced:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 860}
{"candidates": ["Right portion", "Left portion", "Center portion"], "question": "When passing a vehicle, you should ride in what portion of the lane?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 861}
{"candidates": ["Left side", "Right side", "Middle"], "question": "Oil drippings and debris often collects in which part of a lane?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 862}
{"candidates": ["Wearing a baseball cap is recommended", "You should wear hearing protection to prevent long-term exposure to loud noises", "Helmets provide excellent protection against wind and engine noise, eliminating the need for further hearing protection"], "question": "While riding,", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 863}
{"candidates": ["Wear dark clothes, since it is light outside", "Be comfortable, wearing shorts if it is hot", "Wear bright clothes, so other motorists see you better"], "question": "When riding during the day, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 864}
{"candidates": ["Report the accident without delay to the city police or, in unincorporated areas, to the CHP.", "Both of the above.", "Leave a note on the vehicle."], "question": "Which of these should be done to reduce risks while driving over slippery surfaces?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 867}
{"candidates": ["A sweatshirt", "A DOT compliant helmet", "A leather jacket"], "question": "You have a better chance of avoiding serious injury if you wear all of the following except:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 871}
{"candidates": ["The less effect alcohol has on the body", "The more alcohol accumulates in the body", "The faster alcohol is removed from the body"], "question": "The faster you drink alcohol:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 872}
{"candidates": ["You must observe posted speed limit", "You may exceed the speed limit until the pass is complete", "You may disregard no passing zone markings if you began the pass in a passing zone"], "question": "If passing a vehicle:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 874}
{"candidates": ["On long rides", "At speeds over 55 mph", "At speed less than 30 mph"], "question": "Most motorcycle crashes happen:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 875}
{"candidates": ["Riding in pairs", "Staggered formation", "Single file formation"], "question": "When riding in a group, what is usually the best formation to keep riders closer together while maintaining an adequate space cushion?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 876}
{"candidates": ["Should be avoided", "Allows you to be seen in the rear view mirror", "Makes it difficult for most drivers to see you"], "question": "When behind a car, riding in the center portion of the lane:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 877}
{"candidates": ["Shift into neutral when slowing", "Cover the clutch and the brakes", "Ride slower than the speed limit"], "question": "To reduce your reaction time, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 878}
{"candidates": ["It doesn\u2019t always mean the driver actually saw you", "You know they have seen you", "The other driver will yield to you"], "question": "If someone looks at you and makes eye contact:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 879}
{"candidates": ["Frequent rearview mirror checks", "Not using the rearview mirror", "Constantly looking in the rearview mirror"], "question": "Part of your normal scanning routine while driving should include:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 880}
{"candidates": ["Comfortable shoes", "A baseball cap", "A DOT compliant helmet"], "question": "In any crash you have a better chance of surviving if you wear:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 881}
{"candidates": ["Change lane position to get you into other driver\u2019s field of visions as soon as possible.", "Speed up", "Assume that other drivers will see you and give you the right of way"], "question": "When nearing a blind intersection, a motorcyclist should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 883}
{"candidates": ["Should not be used, except by the leader", "Should be checked frequently", "Can be dangerous as all attention should be focused on the roadway"], "question": "When riding in a group, mirrors:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 884}
{"candidates": ["You are required to go faster than the speed limit", "You must not exceed the speed limit", "You may exceed the speed limit by 10 mph"], "question": "When passing a vehicle,", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 886}
{"candidates": ["Take the motorcycle out of gear", "Change gears during the turn", "Change gears before the turn"], "question": "When entering a turn, it is best to :", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 887}
{"candidates": ["May carry a package with their hands if it does not obstruct their view", "May carry a small package in one hand", "May not carry a package with their hands"], "question": "A person riding a motorcycle:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 889}
{"candidates": ["White lines", "Yellow lines", "Road signs"], "question": "Multiple lanes of traffic in the same direction are separated by:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 890}
{"candidates": ["Come to a complete stop", "Slow down", "Speed up"], "question": "When entering a turn, you should::", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 891}
{"candidates": ["Assume the other driver will maintain a constant speed.", "Assume the other driver will let you pass if you use your turn signal.", "Not assume the other driver will make space for you to return to your lane."], "question": "Before taking your vehicle off the road, you must first ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 898}
{"candidates": ["The motorcycle is on a clear highway", "The motorcycle is leaned over, such as in a curve", "The motorcycle is straight up"], "question": "There may be less traction available for braking when:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 900}
{"candidates": ["Sneakers", "Leather boots", "Sandals"], "question": "What type of footwear is the best for motorcycle riders?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 901}
{"candidates": ["Fasten securely", "Restrict your vision so you can focus on the road ahead", "Not allow eyeglasses or sunglasses to be worn, as that may distract the driver"], "question": "To be effective, eye or face shield protection must:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 902}
{"candidates": ["Is a good way to help others see you", "Often distracts other drivers", "Attracts unwanted attention"], "question": "A headlight:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 903}
{"candidates": ["Is in the right part of the lane, next to the curb.", "Is in the left part of the lane, next to the center line.", "Can vary depending on road and/or traffic conditions."], "question": "The best lane position for a motorcycle:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 904}
{"candidates": ["On the gas tank", "Hanging loosely", "On the footrests"], "question": "When riding, your feet should be:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 905}
{"candidates": ["Change lanes frequently", "Focus only on your driving, not how others are doing", "Be visible \u2013 wear bright or reflective clothing"], "question": "To reduce the chance of a collision, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 906}
{"candidates": ["At an angle of 45 to 90 degrees to the curb", "Without a wheel or fender touching the curb", "Away from the curb, but on line with the outside edge of other parked vehicles."], "question": "How should a motorcycle be parked?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 907}
{"candidates": ["The amount of alcohol consumed", "Body weight", "Age"], "question": "What factor does NOT play a major role in affecting your blood alcohol content (BAC)?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 908}
{"candidates": ["Maintain the rear brake until you stop", "Let go of the rear brake", "release the rear brake and only use the front brake"], "question": "If you accidentally lock you rear tire on a good traction surface, you should", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 909}
{"candidates": ["It is acceptable for a motorcyclist to move between lanes to drive between the stopped or slowed vehicles", "It is acceptable for a motorcyclist to weave between the vehicles because it allows a motorcyclist to get through the congested area quicker.", "A motorcycle driver should not weave between lanes, as a motorcycle, even though small, still needs a full lane of traffic."], "question": "When other vehicles are slowed or stopped:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 910}
{"candidates": ["Left", "Right", "Center"], "question": "When preparing to pass a vehicle, you should ride in what portion of the lane?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 911}
{"candidates": ["just behind the front drivers", "In the rear", "In front"], "question": "When riding in a group, inexperienced riders should be:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 912}
{"candidates": ["Drive past the stop sign and stop partially in the intersection to get a good view", "Stop at the stop sign first and then creep up until you can see better", "Stop beyond the stop sign but before the intersection and look"], "question": "If you approach a blind intersection with a stop sign, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 913}
{"candidates": ["Use a proper lane position for the situation", "Not use turn signals", "Follow other vehicles closely"], "question": "To lessen your chances of a crash occurring, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 915}
{"candidates": ["Side saddle", "In front of you", "Behind you"], "question": "Where should a passenger sit?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 916}
{"candidates": ["Accelerate", "Slow down", "Make sudden moves"], "question": "What should you do if you must drive on a slippery surface?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 917}
{"candidates": ["Goggles will protect you from the wind, while a windshield won\u2019t", "A windshield will keep your eyes from watering better than goggles", "A windshield will protect you from the wind, but goggles don\u2019t"], "question": "A difference between googles and a face shield is:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 919}
{"candidates": ["Lock the rear tire", "Apply both brakes", "Only apply the front brake"], "question": "To stop quickly:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 920}
{"candidates": ["Provides protection in a crash", "Should not stand out to other motorists", "Feels uncomfortable"], "question": "The right clothing:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 921}
{"candidates": ["place as much of the weight on one side as possible", "load the bags as evenly as possible", "place the bags as high as possible on the motorcycle"], "question": "If using saddlebags to carry a load, you should", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 923}
{"candidates": ["Just as noticeable", "Not as noticeable", "More noticeable"], "question": "A motorcycle\u2019s brake light is ____ than a vehicle\u2019s brake light.", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 924}
{"candidates": ["Should only be done by a certified mechanic", "Takes only minutes", "Takes about half an hour"], "question": "A pre-ride inspection:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 925}
{"candidates": ["Ride in the right portion of the lane", "Ride in the center portion of the lane", "Speed up"], "question": "When you are being passed, you should", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 926}
{"candidates": ["About three drinks per hour", "About two drinks per hour", "About one drink per hour"], "question": "How fast does the human body remove alcohol?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 927}
{"candidates": ["Encourage others to share your lane", "Allow you to see", "Place you in others\u2019 blind spots"], "question": "The proper position within a lane should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 930}
{"candidates": ["Need to shift down", "Need to put the motorcycle in neutral", "Need to shift up"], "question": "As a motorcycle increases speed, you will:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 931}
{"candidates": ["Helps protect your whole face.", "Only protects your eyes.", "Is not necessary if you have a windshield."], "question": "A plastic shatter-resistant face shield:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 932}
{"candidates": ["You should only use your headlight at night or when conditions reduce the amount of light", "The headlight should be tinted orange", "You should always use the headlight"], "question": "To improve your chances of being seen:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 933}
{"candidates": ["will have little effect on protecting you from wind blasts", "is very important as it may affect whether you are seen", "has little impact on whether other vehicles can see you"], "question": "When riding a motorcycle, your lane position ____ .", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 934}
{"candidates": ["Keep your knees away from the gas tank.", "Turn your head and shoulders to look through turns.", "Turn just your head, not your shoulders to look through turns"], "question": "When turning, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 935}
{"candidates": ["heavy", "soft", "loose"], "question": "One way to tell if your front tire suddenly goes flat is that the steering will feel:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 937}
{"candidates": ["Maintain a steady speed and ride straight across.", "Exaggerate the zig zag motion to alert other drivers", "Speed up to get over the surface faster"], "question": "If riding over rain grooves or bridge gratings and your motorcycle begins to weave. You should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 938}
{"candidates": ["Move closer to the vehicle in front of you to use its lights to see farther down the road.", "Keep driving at your normal speed because slowing down would increase the chance of being struck from behind.", "Reduce your speed because it is harder to see something lying in the road."], "question": "When riding at night you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 939}
{"candidates": ["When riding in a group.", "On the expressway.", "At intersections."], "question": "The greatest potential for conflict between you and other traffic is:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 941}
{"candidates": ["You are better able to draft off other vehicles", "You will be able to stop faster", "You will have more time to react"], "question": "One of the benefits of having a \u201ccushion of space\u201d between you and other vehicles is", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 942}
{"candidates": ["Have blindspots, just like cars", "Are not required", "Do not have blindspots because a motorcycle is usually smaller than a car"], "question": "Mirrors on motorcycles:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 943}
{"candidates": ["The front brake is more powerful", "The rear brake is more powerful", "Both brakes are equally powerful"], "question": "On a motorcycle,", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 944}
{"candidates": ["Change lanes and let them pass", "Go faster", "Get off the roadway"], "question": "Usually a good way to handle tailgaters is to", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 945}
{"candidates": ["On any road", "On the highway", "At an intersection"], "question": "Where is the greatest potential for conflict between you and other vehicles?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 946}
{"candidates": ["Time", "Exercise.", "Drinking coffee"], "question": "What is a way to get sober after drinking?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 947}
{"candidates": ["Open", "Closed", "Covered"], "question": "Before starting out, you should make sure the fuel valve is", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 948}
{"candidates": ["Have blind spots and require a head check before switching lanes", "Do not have blind spots since they are so small", "Are easily seen by other vehicles"], "question": "Motorcycles:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 949}
{"candidates": ["be unwilling to act to avoid a potential hazard", "stay focused only straight ahead of your motorcycle", "scan the path of travel, looking at least 10 to 15 seconds ahead"], "question": "To reduce the chance of collision, a motorcycle driver should", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 950}
{"candidates": ["continue riding since the danger is over", "pull to the side of the road and check the tires and rims for damage", "test your brakes to ensure they are still working"], "question": "If you drive over an object, you should ____ .", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 951}
{"candidates": ["Ride a little faster", "Start slowing earlier than you usually would", "Find smaller gaps to merge into"], "question": "When riding with a passenger, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 952}
{"candidates": ["20 mph", "25 mph", "30 mph"], "question": "What should you do if there is a large animal, such as a deer or elk, in the road?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 953}
{"candidates": ["Use the left portion of the lane to see around other vehicles ahead.", "Ride close to the vehicle in front of you to see better with their headlights.", "Reduce your speed to increase your chance of avoiding a hazard."], "question": "When riding at night:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 963}
{"candidates": ["Downshift immediately to a lower gear to improve traction.", "Relax, stay on course and ride straight across.", "Proceed in a zig-zag pattern until you cross the bridge."], "question": "If your motorcycle starts to wander back and forth while riding over metal bridge gratings you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 964}
{"candidates": ["Gravel road", "Dirt on the pavement", "Dry pavement"], "question": "Which of the following is an example of a potentially slippery surface?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 965}
{"candidates": ["It fits snugly enough that it does not flap in the wind", "It fits loosely and flaps in the wind", "That is it not made of leather or other sturdy material"], "question": "When choosing a jacket for protection, you should ensure:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 966}
{"candidates": ["Amount of alcohol consumed", "Height", "Temperature"], "question": "What factor may affect the blood alcohol content of a person?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 968}
{"candidates": ["If you cannot see the truck\u2019s mirrors, the driver cannot see you", "You should concentrate on driving the motorcycle and not worry about the truck\u2019s mirrors", "You should not be able to see the truck\u2019s mirrors"], "question": "If you are driving near a truck:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 969}
{"candidates": ["Can become a hazard for a driver", "Severely limits your vision", "Allows you to see as far to the sides as necessary"], "question": "An approved helmet:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 970}
{"candidates": ["Increase your ability to be seen", "Invite others into your lane", "Avoid surface hazards"], "question": "Your lane position should do all of the following, except:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 971}
{"candidates": ["Allow them to pass", "Since they are behind you, there is no reason to worry about tailgaters", "Speed up"], "question": "What is a good way to handle tailgaters?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 973}
{"candidates": ["You should take the jacket off to stay cool", "You should keep it on since many jackets are designed to keep you cool when it is hot", "You should take frequent breaks to cool off"], "question": "If wearing a jacket for protection when it is hot:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 974}
{"candidates": ["Your feet should comfortably reach the ground while seated on the motorcycle", "Your fingertips barely reach the handlebars", "The seat is at least one foot higher than your waist"], "question": "Choosing a motorcycle that \u201cfits you\" means:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 975}
{"candidates": ["Be pointed with your toes aimed downward", "Be on the footrests for balance", "Be comfortable"], "question": "When riding a motorcycle, your feet should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 976}
{"candidates": ["Brown", "Orange", "Yellow"], "question": "What color of clothing will make you less visible to other motorists?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 978}
{"candidates": ["0.1", "0.08", "0.12"], "question": "It is illegal to drive a motorcycle with a blood alcohol content (BAC) of ____ or more.", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 982}
{"candidates": ["inexperienced and experienced riders should be mixed up", "experienced riders should be placed behind the leader", "inexperienced riders should be placed behind the leader"], "question": "When motorcyclists ride in a group, ____ .", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 983}
{"candidates": ["Are not required", "Are required for the driver and passenger", "May be shared by the driver and passenger"], "question": "Footrests:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 985}
{"candidates": ["Put the bike in neutral", "Shift down to a lower gear", "Shift up to a higher gear"], "question": "As your motorcycle increase speed, you will need to:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 986}
{"candidates": ["Move to the part of the lane that allows other drivers to see you", "Move to the part of the lane closest to the traffic control device", "Move to the outside edge of the lane"], "question": "If you approach a blind intersection, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 991}
{"candidates": ["There is less traction available for stopping", "The brake controls do not work in a turn", "The driver is usually focused on the turn, not braking"], "question": "Stopping in a turn can be difficult because:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 992}
{"candidates": ["Brake on the good wheel and pull off the road as soon as possible", "Shift your weight toward the good wheel and brake normally", "Hold the handlegrips firmly and stay off the brakes"], "question": "If you get a flat tire while riding, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 993}
{"candidates": ["Should not be done at highway speeds", "Allows for maximum braking power", "Is ineffective in stopping a motorcycle"], "question": "Using both the front and rear brakes:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 995}
{"candidates": ["Improve steering", "Cause control problems", "Be helpful in most situations"], "question": "Locking your brakes can:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 997}
{"candidates": ["Left", "Right", "Center"], "question": "When passing parked vehicles and there are no oncoming vehicles, what part of your lane should a motorcycle driver be?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1000}
{"candidates": ["Scan your path ahead", "Turn your headlight off during the day", "Be ready to act to avoid a hazard"], "question": "To lessen your chance of a crash occurring, you should do all of the following except:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1001}
{"candidates": ["Cause you to keep control of the motorcycle", "Cause you to get through the turn faster", "Cause you to not hold the turn, possibly putting you in another lane of traffic"], "question": "Taking a turn too fast can:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1002}
{"candidates": ["Find the lane with the least amount of oily buildup", "Not worry about oil and grease buildups in the lane", "Avoid riding on oil and grease buildups"], "question": "In the center portion of a traffic lane, there is usually an oily strip. Motorcyclists should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1003}
{"candidates": ["you can usually maintain control the motorcycle", "you will likely lose control of the motorcycle", "you will need to release the rear brake to gain control"], "question": "If stopping suddenly on a straightaway and the rear wheel locks up, ____", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1004}
{"candidates": ["You start to lose control in a curve.", "The motorcycle starts to wobble.", "The throttle is stuck and you can't free it."], "question": "You should operate the engine cut-off switch and pull in the clutch when:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1005}
{"candidates": ["Vehicles will be entering the roadway", "The same as a stop sign. Come to a complete stop and go when it is safe to do so", "Yield to traffic"], "question": "What does a flashing red light mean?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1006}
{"candidates": ["They are both equal", "The front brake", "The rear brake"], "question": "On a motorcycle, which brake provides more stopping power?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1009}
{"candidates": ["Have a large bend at the elbow when reaching the handlegrips.", "Have to stretch to reach the handlegrips", "Be slightly bent when holding the handlegrips"], "question": "When sitting on a motorcycle, your arms should", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1010}
{"candidates": ["If the pavement is slippery", "If you can see through vehicles in front of you to determine traffic conditions", "If traffic is light"], "question": "When should you use a longer following distance?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1011}
{"candidates": ["Incorrect tire pressure or uneven loading", "Improperly tightening the front wheel to the frame", "Hitting an object with the front tire"], "question": "A \u201cwobble,\u201d a sudden shaking of the front wheel and handle bars, can usually be traced to:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1012}
{"candidates": ["Take frequent rest breaks", "Drive faster", "Take artificial stimulants"], "question": "The best way to avoid fatigue when riding your motorcycle on long trips is to:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1013}
{"candidates": ["1", "2", "3"], "question": "How many alcoholic drinks need to be consumed before driving ability is affected?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1014}
{"candidates": ["Following too closely", "Lane sharing", "Not being seen by other drivers"], "question": "____ is a major factor in collisions caused by motorcycles.", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1015}
{"candidates": ["When you entered the intersection on the green light.", "Under no circumstances.", "During rush hour traffic."], "question": "An arm extended straight down with the palm facing back indicates a(n):", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1016}
{"candidates": ["It gives you more time to respond", "It prevents you from finding an escape route", "It provides more space to maneuver"], "question": "Which of the following is not a reason to keep a cushion of space between you and the vehicle in front of you?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1020}
{"candidates": ["Follow each other as closely as possible", "Maintain a safe following distance between each other", "Not worry about distances between members"], "question": "When riding in a group, the members should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1021}
{"candidates": ["Only wear a jacket at night", "Only wear a jacket if it is cold outside", "Always wear a jacket"], "question": "When riding a motorcycle, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1023}
{"candidates": ["Quicker", "About the same", "Slower"], "question": "When riding with a passenger, the motorcycle will respond:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1024}
{"candidates": ["Should be used on all rides", "Is not needed with a helmet", "Is only recommended on long rides"], "question": "Hearing protection:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1026}
{"candidates": ["Not required, but recommended", "Only required for beginning motorcycle users", "Required"], "question": "Helmets are", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1029}
{"candidates": ["Is not a danger, since it is only caused by the wind", "can cause irreversible hearing damage", "is just part of riding a motorcycle"], "question": "Long-term exposure to wind noise", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1030}
{"candidates": ["Yes, a helmet dramatically reduces the view to the sides", "It depends \u2013 some helmets limit the view", "No, a DOT-certified helmet doesn\u2019t limit the view to the sides"], "question": "Some riders don\u2019t wear helmets because they think it limits their view to the sides. Is this true?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1031}
{"candidates": ["not talk or move unnecessarily", "Get on the motorcycle before the engine starts", "Sit as far back as possible so you have more room on the seat."], "question": "When riding with a passenger on your motorcycle, you should instruct the passenger to:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1032}
{"candidates": ["There is no single best lane position for all situations", "The left portion of the lane", "The right portion of the lane"], "question": "The safest part of the lane in any situation is:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1033}
{"candidates": ["Green with white letters", "Blue with white letters", "Orange with black letters"], "question": "Service signs are what colors?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1034}
{"candidates": ["Usually more dangerous than either is alone", "Usually minimal, since they cancel each other out", "About the same as just the alcohol"], "question": "The combination of alcohol and drugs is:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1035}
{"candidates": ["Is suggested, because you are farther away from the vehicle.", "Is not encouraged or discouraged as it has no impact on safety.", "Is not suggested because it invites the other driver to move back into your lane too early"], "question": "For motorcycle drivers, moving to the part of the lane farthest from a passing vehicle:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1036}
{"candidates": ["React quicker, taking a shorter amount of time to stop or start", "React about the same, taking the same amount of time to start and stop", "React slower, taking longer to stop and speed up"], "question": "When travelling with a passenger on the motorcycle, the motorcycle will:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1038}
{"candidates": ["Fits loosely", "Meets U.S. DOT standards", "Has no obvious defects"], "question": "You will get the most protection from a helmet if it is all of the following except:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1041}
{"candidates": ["On the right handle grip", "In front of the left footrest", "In front of the right footrest"], "question": "Where is the gearshift located?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1042}
{"candidates": ["2 seconds", "4 seconds", "3 seconds"], "question": "Following distances at night should be:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1043}
{"candidates": ["Ride in the tire tracks left by other vehicles", "Get off the road", "Ride in the center portion of the lane"], "question": "When it starts raining, it is best to ____", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1044}
{"candidates": ["Find a different route", "Maintain the same speed", "Cover the clutch and both brake levers to reduce reaction time."], "question": "In high risk areas, where dangers could be present, a motorcyclist should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1046}
{"candidates": ["Before every ride", "Once a month", "Every week"], "question": "You should conduct a safety inspection of your motorcycle:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1050}
{"candidates": ["Reduce your speed", "Avoid using the high beam light", "Decrease your following distance"], "question": "When driving at night, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1052}
{"candidates": ["Half", "Three-quarter", "Full face"], "question": "Which of the following is not a common type of a helmet?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1054}
{"candidates": ["Ride in the right portion of the lane", "Ride in the left portion of the lane", "Ride in the center portion of the lane"], "question": "When you are being passed you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1055}
{"candidates": ["Using your mirrors is enough to see other vehicles", "You must do a head check because a motorcycle has blind spots", "Only using a turn signal is adequate when changing lanes"], "question": "When riding a motorcycle:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1056}
{"candidates": ["On the highway", "On a rural road", "At an intersection"], "question": "The greatest potential for conflict between a motorcycle and other traffic is:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1057}
{"candidates": ["Stagger the formation", "Ride in single file formation", "Pair up"], "question": "When riding in a group, motorcyclists should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1058}
{"candidates": ["Is shiny", "Fits loosely", "Has no cracks or defects"], "question": "When choosing a helmet, you should ensure that it:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1061}
{"candidates": ["A motorcyclist should stop", "A motorcyclist should never assume a motorist sees them", "A motorcyclist should assume the driver sees them"], "question": "When cars are merging from an entrance ramp:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1062}
{"candidates": ["Allow you to blend in to traffic", "Provide an escape route", "Encourage others to use your lane"], "question": "Your lane position should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1063}
{"candidates": ["Dust", "Noise", "Glare"], "question": "A plastic shatter-resistant face shield can protect you from:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1064}
{"candidates": ["Secured as low as possible", "Secured on a sissy bar", "Secured as high as possible"], "question": "When carrying a load, it should be:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1065}
{"candidates": ["When you slow down more quickly than others would expect", "When you slow down where others won\u2019t expect it", "When people are walking on the sidewalk"], "question": "When should you not flash your brake light?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1066}
{"candidates": ["some motorists may not react quickly enough to the rain.", "they may not be used to wet conditions.", "the oil on the road gets washed to the side of the road."], "question": "Motorcyclists may find it difficult to ride right after it starts raining because:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1068}
{"candidates": ["Stop and wait for traffic to pass", "The traffic light is about to change to red", "The traffic light is about to change to green"], "question": "What does a solid yellow light mean?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1069}
{"candidates": ["They need as much room to stop as other vehicles", "They require about the same amount of room to stop as other vehicles", "They need less room to stop when compared to other vehicles"], "question": "While motorcycles are smaller than most other vehicles:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1070}
{"candidates": ["Tight enough to prevent you from moving freely", "Snug enough to keep from flapping in the wind", "Loose fitting to allow the wind to catch the fabric"], "question": "When riding, jackets and pants should be:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1071}
{"candidates": ["Safe, Experienced, and Evasive", "Slow, Experienced , and Error-free", "Search, Evalaute, and Execute"], "question": "The SEE strategy stands for:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1072}
{"candidates": ["Provide a wider view of the road behind you", "Are illegal", "Provide a narrower view of the road behind you"], "question": "Convex mirrors:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1073}
{"candidates": ["Using only the front brake", "Locking up both wheels", "Using both brakes, but not locking up either wheel"], "question": "Maximum straight-line braking is achieved by:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1075}
{"candidates": ["have increased control of the motorcycle", "go off the road", "have increased stability of the motorcycle"], "question": "If a motorcycle rider takes a turn too fast, they may", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1076}
{"candidates": ["Appearance", "Price", "Protection"], "question": "What should be the first consideration when buying your motorcycle helmet:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1081}
{"candidates": ["In broad daylight", "At night", "At dusk"], "question": "When do most crashes occur?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1082}
{"candidates": ["0.04", "0.08", "0.02"], "question": "A person with a blood alcohol content of ____ or more is considered intoxicated.", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1085}
{"candidates": ["warm", "black or a dark color", "made of leather or synthetic materials"], "question": "When selecting a jacket that will be used as protective apparel, a motorcycle rider should look for a jacket that is:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1086}
{"candidates": ["Bright colored clothing to increase your chances of being seen", "Dark colored clothes to contrast with the sunlight", "Any color of clothing since it is daytime, other vehicles can see you"], "question": "If riding during the day, you should wear", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1088}
{"candidates": ["Because you may be in the vehicle\u2019s blind spot", "Because another driver may want to use your lane to pass", "Because you may have access to escape routes"], "question": "Why should you not ride next to a vehicle if you can avoid it?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1089}
{"candidates": ["to keep your high beam headlight on", "ensure the motorcule is painted a dark color", "To flash your lights"], "question": "In normal driving conditions, one of the best ways to allow others to see you on a motorcycle is:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1091}
{"candidates": ["Use only the rear brake, since the front brake is ineffective on slippery surfaces", "Drive on the shoulder to be out of the way of traffic", "Avoid sudden moves, as the sudden move could cause a skid"], "question": "When riding on a slippery surface, you should", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1092}
{"candidates": ["Is a significant contributing factor to many motorcycle crashes", "Should not be a concern, since the motorcycle has two brakes", "Usually has no consequences"], "question": "Improper braking:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1093}
{"candidates": ["Dark colored clothes", "Clothes that are uncomfortable", "Bright colored clothes"], "question": "When riding, you should wear:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1094}
{"candidates": ["Can cause the brakes to lock.", "Is the best way to slow down when the streets are wet.", "Is the best way to stop in an emergency."], "question": "Grabbing the front brake or jamming down on the rear brake:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1095}
{"candidates": ["Take frequent rest breaks.", "Turn on the radio and open the window.", "Drink caffeine."], "question": "To minimize the potential for fatigue:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1096}
{"candidates": ["With the rear brake only", "With both brakes", "With the front brake only"], "question": "How should you brake?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1097}
{"candidates": ["Shift down through the gears", "Stay in your gear", "Shift up through the gears"], "question": "When slowing or stopping a motorcycle, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1098}
{"candidates": ["sitting so you can use arms to control the motorcycle", "sitting at an angle so your arms support your weight", "using your arms to hold yourself up"], "question": "Proper posture to control a motorcycle means:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1099}
{"candidates": ["release the rear brake and then quickly apply and release the brake until you stop", "keep the tire locked up until you stop", "release the brake and only use the front brake"], "question": "If you lock up the rear wheel on a good traction surface, you should ____ .", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1117}
{"candidates": ["Center", "Right", "Left"], "question": "When being passed, either from behind, or by oncoming vehicles, usually it is best for motorcycle drivers to be in what part of the lane?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1131}
{"candidates": ["Turning the handlebars quickly", "Getting the cycle to lean quickly", "Shifting your weight quickly"], "question": "The key to making a quick turn is:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1140}
{"candidates": ["Keep the headlight on.", "Honk your horn.", "Use eye contact."], "question": "The best way to help others see your motorcycle is to:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1141}
{"candidates": ["Orange, red, yellow or green", "Blue, black, gray or purple", "Brown, gold, silver or white"], "question": "What colors are best for motorcycle riders to be seen?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1143}
{"candidates": ["Is a good way to tell the other driver sees you", "Is required before proceeding through the intersection", "Does not mean the other driver sees you"], "question": "When at an intersection, \u201ceye contact\u201d:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1145}
{"candidates": ["Center", "Right", "Left"], "question": "When being passed from behind, what portion of the lane should you ride in?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1149}
{"candidates": ["Allow more distance to stop", "Ride at slower speeds", "Tell the passenger to hold onto the back of the bike"], "question": "If you have a passenger aboard your motorcycle, you should do all of the following, except:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1150}
{"candidates": ["Should sit as far forward as possible without crowding you.", "Put their feet on the ground when the motorcycle is stopped.", "Not ride without a back rest."], "question": "Passengers on motorcycles should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1151}
{"candidates": ["Place your foot under the shift lever and lift up", "Use your thumb to move the lever", "Place your foot over the shift lever and push down"], "question": "To shift up to a higher gear, you will", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1153}
{"candidates": ["Side mirrors should not be used by motorists", "The wind may prevent the use of a side mirror", "Most people don\u2019t use their side mirrors as often as the rear view mirror"], "question": "Riding in the left third of the lane allows drivers to see you in their side mirror. What is a downside to this?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1154}
{"candidates": ["In a staggered formation", "In single file formation", "Side-by-side"], "question": "How should a group of motorcycle drivers pass another vehicle?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1155}
{"candidates": ["No higher than 15 inches above the seat", "Even with the seat", "No higher than the driver\u2019s head"], "question": "Handlebars must be:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1158}
{"candidates": ["Protects you in a collision", "Allows you to blend in with other vehicles", "Protects you from the elements"], "question": "The right clothing does all of the following except:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1161}
{"candidates": ["You may complete the pass in a no passing zone if the pass was started in a passing zone", "You must remain below the posted speed limit", "You may exceed the posted speed limit, but not by more than 10 mph"], "question": "When attempting to pass another vehicle:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1162}
{"candidates": ["2 seconds", "4 seconds", "3 seconds"], "question": "For the recommended following distance, how long should it take your vehicle to reach a point passed by the vehicle in front of you?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1163}
{"candidates": ["Keep your eyes moving to look for possible hazards.", "Always put one car length between you and the car ahead.", "Look only at the car in front of you while driving."], "question": "Which of these can be done to lessen the chances of a crash?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 1168}
{"candidates": ["Are used to move air to the brakes.", "Should not be used in cold weather.", "Are helpful to remove water and oil from the air tanks."], "question": "Air tank drains:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1187}
{"candidates": ["Slow your vehicle down.", "Not impact your speed.", "Speed your vehicle up."], "question": "On any upgrade, gravity will:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1188}
{"candidates": ["Other drivers may not see the flares if the weather is sunny.", "There may be fuel spilled on the ground that could catch fire.", "Flares are expensive."], "question": "After an accident, flares should be used with caution because:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1189}
{"candidates": ["Can only use a cell phone on rural roads", "Can use a cell phone", "Can only use a hands-free mobile phone"], "question": "Drivers of a Commercial Motor Vehicle:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1190}
{"candidates": ["Driving away from the scene", "Caring for the injured", "Trying to move your vehicle to the side of the road"], "question": "If involved in an accident, which of the following is not recommended?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1191}
{"candidates": ["To see if the vehicle is on an incline.", "To see if there are any fresh fluids on the ground.", "To see if the vehicle is in a parking spot."], "question": "When approaching a vehicle for a pre-trip inspection, a driver should look under the vehicle:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1193}
{"candidates": ["10", "5", "20"], "question": "Cargo should have one tie down for how many feet of cargo?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1194}
{"candidates": ["10 \u00be inches", "4 inches", "7 \u00bd inches"], "question": "What is the minimum size of a placard?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1195}
{"candidates": ["Is when you use your brakes as hard as possible without locking the wheels", "Is when you lock your wheels", "Is when you only slightly tap the brakes"], "question": "The controlled braking method:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1196}
{"candidates": ["Looks", "Gas mileage", "Safety"], "question": "What is the most important reason for inspecting your vehicle?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1197}
{"candidates": ["By about one-quarter", "By about one-half", "By about one-third"], "question": "On a wet road, how much should you reduce your speed?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1198}
{"candidates": ["50", "75", "100"], "question": "When does the air compressor governor allow air to start pumping?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1200}
{"candidates": ["Your wheels must be within 18 inches of the curb.", "One of your rear wheels must touch the curb.", "Your front wheels must be turned toward the street."], "question": "The emergency line has two functions. It controls the emergency brakes on combination vehicles and what else?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1203}
{"candidates": ["Yes, it is a good defensive driving technique.", "No, you can block traffic when you drive too slowly.", "Yes, it is always safer than driving faster than other traffic."], "question": "When you back up with a trailer you should position your vehicle so you can ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1209}
{"candidates": ["You must always obey school crossing-guards.", "There are children present.", "Directly before and after school hours."], "question": "On a truck with air brakes, what does the braking system\u2019s air compressor do?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1214}
{"candidates": ["You should turn very sharply.", "You should brake hard.", "You should not brake as it may cause the wheels to lock."], "question": "If turning to avoid a hazard:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1216}
{"candidates": ["Any driver with a CDL", "A driver with a minimum of 10 years of experience", "A driver with a hazardous materials endorsement"], "question": "Who may drive a vehicle that uses placards when carrying hazardous materials?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1218}
{"candidates": ["Slowing down and keeping a reasonable following distance", "Not expecting delays on a drive", "Avoiding gestures and keeping hands on the wheel"], "question": "Which of the following is not a step in avoiding becoming an aggressive driver?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1219}
{"candidates": ["18", "21", "15"], "question": "What is the minimum age to apply for a CDL?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1220}
{"candidates": ["90 inches", "102 inches", "60 inches"], "question": "What is the maximum width of a load that can be transported?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1221}
{"candidates": ["Push the brake pedal more lightly than usual.", "Push the brake pedal as you normally would.", "Push the brake pedal harder than usual."], "question": "When braking with ABS, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1222}
{"candidates": ["The air conditioning unit", "The oil pressure", "Coolant and antifreeze levels"], "question": "When driving in winter, which of the following should receive extra attention in a pre-trip inspection?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1224}
{"candidates": ["Put both sets of wheels on the shoulder", "Try to leave the shoulder as quickly as possible", "Brake as hard as possible"], "question": "In an emergency, if you must leave the roadway and use the shoulder, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1225}
{"candidates": ["They will lose their CDL for 6 months", "They will lose their CDL for 60 days", "They will lose their CDL for 10 days"], "question": "Regardless of what vehicle the person is in at the time of the violation, what happens when a person is caught violating the texting law for the second time?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1226}
{"candidates": ["Not use the brake pedal.", "Move the steering wheel.", "Press the accelerator."], "question": "If the spring brakes are on, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1227}
{"candidates": ["Slow down as you pass him/her.", "Make eye contact and then pass him/her.", "Stop and let him/her finish crossing the street."], "question": "While the engine is off and the brakes released, a straight truck or bus air brake system should not leak at a rate of more than ____ psi per minute.", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1238}
{"candidates": ["Can be dangerous.", "Slows the vehicle, but cannot stop it.", "Still allows you additional control when braking."], "question": "Having ABS on only one axle:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1246}
{"candidates": ["No faster than 65 mph.", "70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic.", "Between 65 mph and 70 mph."], "question": "When backing with a trailer,", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1247}
{"candidates": ["1/32", "4/32", "2/32"], "question": "How much tread should be in every major groove of a tire that is not in front?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1248}
{"candidates": ["Locks up the wheels", "Prevents the vehicle from accelerating when going uphill", "Help you avoid wheel lock up"], "question": "What do ABS brakes do?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1250}
{"candidates": ["Brake fade on long hills", "Loss of hydraulic pressure", "Downshifting"], "question": "Which of the following is not a reason for hydraulic brake failure?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1251}
{"candidates": ["Rely on the taillights", "Use the four-way emergency flashers", "If pulled off the road, you don\u2019t need to worry about other vehicles"], "question": "If pulled over on the side of the road, how should you alert other motorists?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1252}
{"candidates": ["Points are the same as for a non-commercial vehicle", "Points are given at 3 times the point count", "Points are given at one and a half times the point count"], "question": "How are points calculated when driving a commercial vehicle?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1253}
{"candidates": ["2", "3", "0"], "question": "How many mirrors are required for every registered vehicle?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1255}
{"candidates": ["You may hit a vehicle behind you", "The transmission may be damaged", "The truck is not made to go backwards"], "question": "What is a danger of rolling backward when you start to accelerate?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1256}
{"candidates": ["Should drive slower than other traffic for 200 feet.", "Should wait for the first two vehicles to pass, then drive into the lane.", "Need a large enough gap to get up to the speed of traffic."], "question": "What is a front brake limiting valve?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1261}
{"candidates": ["Always put one car length between you and the car ahead.", "Look only at the car in front of you while driving.", "Keep your eyes moving to look for possible hazards."], "question": "When checking the trailer emergency brakes ensure ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1275}
{"candidates": ["Air pressure may increase with the temperature.", "The tread wears down more quickly than in cooler weather.", "They may melt."], "question": "In very hot weather, tires should be checked regularly because:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1277}
{"candidates": ["Pull into a service station", "Notify emergency services of your problem and your location.", "Park in an open area, away from buildings, trees, brush and other vehicles"], "question": "If there is a fire in your vehicle, what should you not do?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1281}
{"candidates": ["Push the clutch in", "Shift to neutral", "Push the clutch out"], "question": "When stopping with a manual transmission vehicle, what should you do when the engine is close to idle?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1282}
{"candidates": ["An escape ramp", "Going off the road", "Using the shoulder"], "question": "If your brakes fail on a downgrade, what is your best hope to stop?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1283}
{"candidates": ["6 seconds", "4 seconds", "5 seconds"], "question": "When driving a 50-foot truck at 50 mph, what should be your minimum following distance?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1284}
{"candidates": ["Turn the wheel in the opposite direction", "Turn the wheel more in the direction you want to turn", "Nothing, the vehicle will follow naturally"], "question": "When backing up, once a trailer starts to turn, what should you do to follow the trailer?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1285}
{"candidates": ["Flares", "Red reflective triangles", "A flashlight"], "question": "Which of the following is NOT required emergency equipment?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1305}
{"candidates": ["Hold enough air for the brakes to be used several times if the compressor stops working.", "Do not hold air unless there is an emergency.", "Hold only enough air for one braking cycle."], "question": "The air storage tanks:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1309}
{"candidates": ["4", "2", "3"], "question": "When you double your speed from 20 to 40 mph, the braking distance is increased how many times?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1310}
{"candidates": ["Stop in a shorter distance than a full truck", "Stop in about the same distance as a full truck", "Require a longer distance than a full truck"], "question": "Empty trucks:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1311}
{"candidates": ["Aim the extinguisher at the top of the fire", "Stay as far away as possible", "Get as close as possible"], "question": "When using a fire extinguisher on a fire you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1312}
{"candidates": ["The time required for the brakes to work after the brake pedal is pressed", "The distance between the brake pedal and the floor", "The amount of air pressure used to stop the vehicle"], "question": "What is brake lag?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1329}
{"candidates": ["Left and right", "Normal and slippery", "Low and high"], "question": "What are the two markings on a front brake limiting valve?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1333}
{"candidates": ["On the front only", "On the front, back and both sides of a vehicle", "On the driver\u2019s side of the vehicle"], "question": "Where do placards have to be placed?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1334}
{"candidates": ["Vibration", "Sound", "Smoother steering"], "question": "What is not a sign of a tire failure?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1335}
{"candidates": ["To prevent cargo from shifting", "To prevent cargo from being unloaded too quickly", "To prevent cargo from being loaded too high"], "question": "What is blocking used for?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1336}
{"candidates": ["The yellow light on the left rear of the trailer will stay on", "All the rear lights will flash and then shut off", "The red light on the right side of the trailer will flash three times and then stay on"], "question": "When starting the engine, how can you tell if the ABS system is not working on a truck with a trailer?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1337}
{"candidates": ["No sooner than three minutes", "Within seconds", "Within five minutes"], "question": "How long should it normally take for engine oil pressure to come up to normal after starting the vehicle?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1338}
{"candidates": ["The owner", "The mechanic", "The driver"], "question": "Who is responsible for the safe operation of a vehicle?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1339}
{"candidates": ["They will be put out of service for 24 hours", "They will be required to drive no more than 55 mph", "They will be told not to drink any more"], "question": "What happens if a person is caught driving with a detectable amount of alcohol, under .04 percent?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1340}
{"candidates": ["A red or orange flag must be placed on the end of the load", "The load can only be transported between 6 p.m. and 3 a.m.", "A vehicle with flashing lights must drive behind truck with the load"], "question": "What must be done with a load that extends 4 feet or more beyond the rear of the body?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1341}
{"candidates": ["1/32", "4/32", "2/32"], "question": "How much tread should be in every major groove of a front tire?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1345}
{"candidates": ["Small children should ride in the back seat.", "It is OK for small children to ride in the front passenger seat of your car.", "Use the rear-facing child restraint system in the front passenger seat."], "question": "Stab braking occurs when which of the following steps are performed?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1358}
{"candidates": ["Only when the trailer is carrying a load", "Only to test the trailer\u2019s brakes", "Only in inclement weather when the trailer may skid"], "question": "When should the trailer hand valve be used?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1359}
{"candidates": ["Push down the brake pedal.", "Turn on the lights.", "Turn off the vehicle."], "question": "When the spring brakes are on, you should never:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1360}
{"candidates": ["Difficulty focusing, with frequent blinking", "Yawning repeatedly or rubbing eyes", "Staying in your lane"], "question": "Which of the following is not a sign of fatigue?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1362}
{"candidates": ["Other brake systems will squeak too loudly", "Air brakes are complicated", "Air brakes are very effective systems"], "question": "Why do larger vehicles use air brakes?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1365}
{"candidates": ["Is a good way to stay awake on long trips.", "Is distracting.", "Can cause mechanical damage."], "question": "Rough acceleration:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1366}
{"candidates": ["You should steer sharply in one direction.", "You should always steer to the left.", "You may be able to drive onto the shoulder."], "question": "To avoid a hazard:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1367}
{"candidates": ["A liquid burning flare", "A fire extinguisher", "An axe"], "question": "Which of the following is not required safety equipment?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1369}
{"candidates": ["No part of the vehicle should be visible in the mirror", "A part of the vehicle should be visible in the mirror", "More than half of the mirror should show the vehicle"], "question": "When adjusting your mirrors:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1370}
{"candidates": ["Offer about the same traction as the rest of the roadway", "Offer more traction", "Very slippery"], "question": "Tar in the road pavement often rises to the top in very hot weather. Spots where the tar \u201cbleeds\u201d are:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1373}
{"candidates": ["Increase following distance", "Speed up", "Reduce speeds gradually"], "question": "If being tailgated while driving a large vehicle, you should do all of the following except:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1374}
{"candidates": ["Cracked", "Loose", "Tight"], "question": "If the vehicle has air brakes, the air compressor drive belt should be checked before each drive. In what condition should the belt be in?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1395}
{"candidates": ["The longer you wait, vehicles may get out of your way", "The longer you wait, the slower your vehicle will travel", "The longer you wait, the faster the vehicle will go"], "question": "If your brakes fail when going downhill, why should you decide what to do as quickly as possible?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1418}
{"candidates": ["Run the air conditioner", "Pull over and find out what is wrong", "Continue to drive"], "question": "What should you do if the coolant temperature gauge goes above the highest safe temperature?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1425}
{"candidates": ["When you have already started the grade", "As far down the grade as possible", "Before beginning the grade"], "question": "When going down a grade, when should you switch to a lower gear?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1427}
{"candidates": ["Because it involves mental and physical distraction at the same time", "Because people like to read", "Because a message may be upsetting"], "question": "Why is texting a worrisome distraction:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1428}
{"candidates": ["Prevent cargo from shifting", "Prevent skidding", "Keep doors closed while driving"], "question": "Tie downs are used to:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1430}
{"candidates": ["Brake normally, you will still have brakes", "Push the brake down as hard as you can", "Pump the brake repeatedly"], "question": "How should you brake if your vehicle loses ABS?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1432}
{"candidates": ["The vehicle\u2019s driver will be allowed to drive, but only at reduced speeds", "The vehicle will be put \u201cout of service\u201d until it is fixed", "The vehicle will be fine to drive since most of the spring is in place"], "question": "What can happen if one-fourth of the leaves in a leaf spring are missing when the vehicle is inspected?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1433}
{"candidates": ["Stop, then proceed when you think all of the children have exited the bus.", "Slow to 25 MPH and pass cautiously.", "Stop as long as the red lights are flashing."], "question": "With a working ABS, the anti-lock braking system indicator lights will ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1443}
{"candidates": ["Signal continuously \u2013 do not cancel a signal until the turn is completed", "Don\u2019t over-signal \u2013 if no one is near you, there is no need to signal", "Signal early \u2013 signal well before the turn"], "question": "Which of the following is not a good rule when using turns signals?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1447}
{"candidates": ["Set the control to the off position", "Set the control to normal", "Set the control to the neutral position"], "question": "To ensure normal stopping power, vehicles equipped with a front brake limiting valve should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1448}
{"candidates": ["The air brakes should be used", "The vehicle should be placed in a lower gear and brakes used to supplement braking", "The vehicle should be continually downshifted instead of using the brakes"], "question": "When going down a steep downgrade,", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1449}
{"candidates": ["How frequently you drink", "How much you drink", "The temperature of the drink"], "question": "Which of the following determines your Blood Alcohol Concentration?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1450}
{"candidates": ["Expected to explain your knowledge of the pre-trip process", "Watching a film on how to inspect a vehicle", "Watching someone else check the vehicle"], "question": "During a pre-trip test, you will be:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1453}
{"candidates": ["Removing coolant.", "A check of the engine oil level.", "Washing the tire rims."], "question": "A pre-trip inspection should include:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1455}
{"candidates": ["Using the brakes mostly and once in a while downshifting", "Only using the brakes", "Downshifting and then using brakes"], "question": "When going on a long downgrade, how should you brake?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1457}
{"candidates": ["65 mph", "55 mph", "45 mph"], "question": "For a truck with three axles, what is the maximum speed limit?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1458}
{"candidates": ["Only before the trip", "Only by the loading personnel", "Before the trip and after the first 50 miles"], "question": "When travelling with cargo, the cargo should be checked:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1459}
{"candidates": ["You should rely on the movement of other motorists to indicate if a train is approaching", "You should rely on the signals to indicate if a train is approaching", "You should not rely on signals to indicate if a train is approaching"], "question": "When approaching a railroad crossing,", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1461}
{"candidates": ["0.1", "0.08", "0.04"], "question": "A person will lose their CDL for one year for a first offense of driving with a Blood Alcohol Concentration of ____ or more.", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1462}
{"candidates": ["Push in the diamond-shaped yellow knob", "Move a lever to the right", "Pull out the diamond-shaped yellow knob"], "question": "On newer vehicles how do you put on the parking brake?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1476}
{"candidates": ["Shows how much air pressure is available", "Shows how much air pressure would be required to stop the vehicle", "Shows how much air pressure you are applying to the brakes"], "question": "What does an application pressure gauge do?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1477}
{"candidates": ["Double clutching", "Single clutching", "Triple clutching"], "question": "Most heavy trucks with manual transmissions require ____ to change gears.", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1478}
{"candidates": ["Continue trying to get the vehicle off the tracks", "Stay in the vehicle", "Get out of the vehicle and call for assistance"], "question": "What should you do if you vehicle gets stuck on railroad tracks?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1485}
{"candidates": ["A type of air brake system", "A low pressure warning system", "A tube that carries air to the brakes"], "question": "What is a \u201cwig wag\u201d?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1488}
{"candidates": ["Be impossible", "Take a short amount of time", "Take a long time"], "question": "If using the spring brakes when hauling a heavy load, a complete stop will:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1506}
{"candidates": ["Not a hazard when driving.", "Usually thin.", "Usually thick."], "question": "Black ice is:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1507}
{"candidates": ["3 minutes", "12 minutes", "15 minutes"], "question": "Air pressure should build up in a single air system, within how long?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1509}
{"candidates": ["12-15 seconds", "5-6 seconds", "2-3 seconds"], "question": "How far ahead do most good drivers look?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1513}
{"candidates": ["Speed up", "Travel at the same rate as on level roadway", "Slow down"], "question": "When travelling on a downgrade, the vehicle will:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1517}
{"candidates": ["Stay off the brakes.", "Use the brakes.", "Swerve."], "question": "If a tire fails, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1519}
{"candidates": ["Traffic on the street moves to the right.", "Traffic on the street moves to the left.", "A sign permits the turn."], "question": "If you are using the proper braking technique and your \"safe speed\" is 40 mph, you would wait until your speed reaches 40 mph and then apply the brakes hard enough for you to gradually reduce your speed to ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1522}
{"candidates": ["The pavement is dry", "The spray is caught on the underside of the vehicle", "Ice has formed on the road"], "question": "When driving in wet conditions, what does a lack of spray from other vehicles indicate?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1532}
{"candidates": ["Open the hood as soon as possible", "Not use a fire extinguisher", "Turn the engine off as soon as possible"], "question": "With an engine fire, what should you do?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1543}
{"candidates": ["Air gauges", "Air filter", "Low pressure warning device"], "question": "Which of the following items is not part of a vehicle\u2019s air brake system?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1545}
{"candidates": ["Is encouraged so you can see better", "Is discouraged, because you should look at both sides equally", "Is only recommended if it is raining"], "question": "When backing in an unfamiliar area, using driver-side backing:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1562}
{"candidates": ["It stores the compressed air.", "It turns on the air compressor.", "It stops the compressor from pumping air."], "question": "What does the air compressor governor do?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1563}
{"candidates": ["Usually shorter with a heavy load", "Usually taller than with a heavy load", "Usually the same height with a load or without"], "question": "A cargo van with a light load is:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1565}
{"candidates": ["Move to a lane not next to the stopped vehicle", "Use the shoulder", "Move to the far part of the lane, but not switch lanes"], "question": "Move-over laws require a driver approaching a stopped emergency vehicle, to:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1569}
{"candidates": ["0.02", "0.08", "0.04"], "question": "Driving a commercial motor vehicle with a Blood Alcohol Content of ____ percent or more is illegal.", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1571}
{"candidates": ["Consists of one air brake system for the left side of the truck and one system for the right side of the truck, each with its own set of controls.", "Is a single air brake system with two different sets of controls.", "Consists of two separate air brake systems that share a single set of controls."], "question": "A dual air brake system:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1573}
{"candidates": ["You must designate which system you are using", "Air tanks are shared between both systems", "Each system has its own air tanks"], "question": "In a dual air brake system,", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1574}
{"candidates": ["GPS", "Bluetooth", "Antilock Braking System"], "question": "Truck tractors with air brakes built after March 1, 1997 must have:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1597}
{"candidates": ["Test your tires\u2019 traction while going uphill.", "Decrease the distance you look ahead of your vehicle.", "Avoid making fast turns and fast stops."], "question": "What color are advance warning signs at passive railroad-highway crossings?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1623}
{"candidates": ["Sell or transfer your vehicle.", "Get a new prescription for lenses or contacts.", "Fail a smog test for your vehicle."], "question": "Portable tanks are bulk packaging, which are not permanently attached to a vehicle whereas cargo tanks are ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1638}
{"candidates": ["One of your rear wheels must touch the curb.", "Your front wheels must be turned toward the street.", "Your wheels must be within 18 inches of the curb."], "question": "Which of the following is a serious error that can be caused by drinking alcohol before or while you are driving?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1681}
{"candidates": ["Your wheels must be within 18 inches of the curb.", "Your front wheels must be turned toward the street.", "One of your rear wheels must touch the curb."], "question": "A placarded vehicle must have how many identical placards?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1727}
{"candidates": ["The posted speed limit for traffic on the freeway.", "5 to 10 MPH slower than the traffic on the freeway.", "At or near the same speed as the traffic on the freeway."], "question": "To transport a forbidden hazardous material, you need to ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1748}
{"candidates": ["They are eliminated if you have one outside mirror on each side of the vehicle.", "Blind spots can be checked by looking in your rear view mirrors.", "Large trucks have bigger blind spots than most passenger vehicles."], "question": "A basic description of a hazardous material will include ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1751}
{"candidates": ["During rush hour traffic.", "When you entered the intersection on the green light.", "Under no circumstances."], "question": "Your school bus will have an ABS malfunction lamp that is what color?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1764}
{"candidates": ["Explain to the dispatcher what happened and make a decision on how to respond", "Tell students to panic", "Ask the students if they want to leave"], "question": "Before evacuating a bus in response to a hazard, the driver should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1771}
{"candidates": ["Letting some students evacuate the bus.", "Letting students evacuate the bus and scatter.", "Keeping students on the bus."], "question": "As a general rule, student safety is best maintained by:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1772}
{"candidates": ["You will still have brakes", "You will not have any brakes", "You should only use the parking brake"], "question": "If ABS is malfunctioning:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1774}
{"candidates": ["Strongly discouraged.", "Only to be done in the morning.", "Strongly encouraged."], "question": "Backing a school bus is:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1775}
{"candidates": ["Get everyone out of the bus and move far from the bus", "Keep everyone inside the bus and wait for help", "Keep everyone inside of the bus and try to wave the train down to make it stop"], "question": "If a bus stalls on a railroad track, what should be done?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1776}
{"candidates": ["Parents", "The school district", "The driver"], "question": "Bus stops should be changed by:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1777}
{"candidates": ["Are crossed by at least 10 vehicles every hour.", "Do not have any traffic control devices installed.", "Have traffic control devices installed."], "question": "Active railroad crossings:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1778}
{"candidates": ["The front tires touching the ground", "The sides of the school bus", "Under the school bus"], "question": "What should properly adjusted mirrors on a school bus should allow the driver to see?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1779}
{"candidates": ["Count the number of students boarding the bus.", "Lock up your wheels.", "Keep your wheels from locking up."], "question": "ABS helps you:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1780}
{"candidates": ["The students do not get caught on the handrail or door", "They are leaving in pairs", "The students do not talk while exiting"], "question": "As students exit the bus, the driver should watch students to ensure:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1782}
{"candidates": ["Not have students exit in an orderly fashion", "Walk through the bus and check for any sleeping/hiding students", "Not watch students as they leave"], "question": "After students unload at the school, the driver should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1783}
{"candidates": ["Increase your speed.", "Loosen your grip on the steering wheel.", "Reduce your speed."], "question": "If you must drive during periods of high winds, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1784}
{"candidates": ["The left side of the bus from front to back", "The entire area in front of the bus", "Right and front left front tires touching the ground"], "question": "Properly adjusted crossover mirrors allow you to see all of the following except:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1785}
{"candidates": ["The floor of the bus", "The rear tires", "All of the students on the bus"], "question": "The overhead inside rearview mirror should be positioned to see:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1786}
{"candidates": ["Not move them.", "Encourage them to try to stand.", "Move them off the bus."], "question": "If a student is believed to have suffered a back injury, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1787}
{"candidates": ["10", "5", "15"], "question": "If you must back up your bus, you should assign someone to be lookout. What is the purpose of the lookout?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1800}
{"candidates": ["Pulling over the to the side of the road", "Turning on the red alternating lights", "Opening the door and signaling for students to approach"], "question": "When making a stop to pick up students, the driver should ensure all traffic has stopped before:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1802}
{"candidates": ["The front bumper danger zones.", "The rear bumper.", "The left side of the bus."], "question": "Crossover mirrors help the driver see:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1803}
{"candidates": ["200 feet", "100 feet", "50 feet"], "question": "Properly adjusted mirrors on a school bus should allow the driver to see how far behind?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1804}
{"candidates": ["In times of limited visibility", "Only at night", "All the time"], "question": "If your bus is equipped with a roof-mounted strobe light, when should the light be used?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1807}
{"candidates": ["Escort the students across the road while holding an approved hand-held stop sign", "Stay in their seat and watch the students cross the road", "Stand on the driver\u2019s side of the bus while watching students cross the road"], "question": "For students in pre-K through eighth grade who must cross a highway to get on the school bus, what should the driver do?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1808}
{"candidates": ["Keeping the key in the ignition is leaving he driver\u2019s compartment", "Read a book while student unload", "Secure the bus by turning off the ignition switch"], "question": "When unloading students at the school, the driver should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1809}
{"candidates": ["In the front of the bus", "To the front and sides of the bus", "To the sides of the bus"], "question": "Where are danger zones located on a school bus?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1810}
{"candidates": ["So they walk to the bus, providing the driver a better view of their movements", "Because students should walk for exercise", "Because it is difficult to get closer to the students"], "question": "When stopping to pick up students, why should you park at least 10 feet away from the students?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1812}
{"candidates": ["At least 50 feet", "At least 200 feet", "At least 100 feet"], "question": "If equipped with flashing lights, how far in advance of the bus stop should the lights be activated?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1815}
{"candidates": ["Opening windows", "Looking for articles left on the bus", "Looking for sleeping students"], "question": "After the route is completed or school trip is finished, a post-trip inspection should include all of the following except:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1839}
{"candidates": ["In the truck's manual", "In the DOT Emergency Response Guidebook (ERG)", "On the EPA\u2019s website"], "question": "Where are the identification numbers assigned to chemicals located?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1848}
{"candidates": ["The name of the material", "Where the material is from", "Special provisions of the material"], "question": "In the Hazardous Material Table, what is in Column 2?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1849}
{"candidates": ["How the materials will be transported", "The materials being transported", "Who should accept the materials being transported"], "question": "What does a shipping paper describe?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1850}
{"candidates": ["The label may be placed on a tag securely attached to the item", "There should be a QR Code attached that can be scanned", "The HazMat label should be reduced in size to fit on the item"], "question": "How do you label a package if the hazardous material label will not fit on the package?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1851}
{"candidates": ["Straps.", "Hooks.", "Dollies."], "question": "When loading containers of hazardous materials, you should not use:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1852}
{"candidates": ["100", "5", "25"], "question": "A person should not smoke within ____ feet of a vehicle placarded for Class 3 (flammable liquids) or Division 2.1 (gases).", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1853}
{"candidates": ["The California Highway Patrol", "The California Environmental Protection Agency", "The California Department of energy"], "question": "If a route you are planning to use has a route restriction, who should you contact?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1854}
{"candidates": ["2 years", "1 year", "5 months"], "question": "How long do shippers need to keep a copy of shipping papers?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1855}
{"candidates": ["Load the containers by hand", "Use the vehicle\u2019s emergency brake", "Roll the containers"], "question": "If loading corrosive materials you should not:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1856}
{"candidates": ["Guessing", "Attending hazardous materials training courses", "Talking to other people"], "question": "What is away to learn more about transporting hazardous materials in addition to reading the manual?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1857}
{"candidates": ["Eyeballing it", "With a tire pressure gauge", "Pushing on the tire to feel the pressure"], "question": "What is the only way to check tire pressure?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1858}
{"candidates": ["Once every year", "Once every three years", "Once every five years"], "question": "Regulations require hazardous materials employees be trained and tested how often?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1859}
{"candidates": ["Two", "Four", "Three"], "question": "How many identical placards must be placed on a vehicle?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1860}
{"candidates": ["The shipper\u2019s certification", "A verbal agreement", "A notarized statement"], "question": "Unless a package is clearly unsafe, what does the driver need to accept a package?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1861}
{"candidates": ["The engine should be left on", "The gas nozzle may be left unattended", "The engine should be turned off"], "question": "When refueling a vehicle with hazardous materials:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1862}
{"candidates": ["The vehicle does not need to be placarded.", "The vehicle must always be placarded.", "The vehicle must be placarded, but only if transporting more than 200 pounds of the material."], "question": "If transporting mass explosives:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1863}
{"candidates": ["The shipping paper is written in code", "The shipping paper matches the marking and labels on packages", "That all packages are labeled as poison"], "question": "A driver should ensure:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1864}
{"candidates": ["Check to see if the doors are hot", "Throw water on the doors", "Use gloves to open the doors"], "question": "In a fire, what should you do before opening trailer doors?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1865}
{"candidates": ["Location in the vehicle", "Where the materials originated", "Immediate hazards to health"], "question": "What must be included in the emergency response information?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1866}
{"candidates": ["Combustible liquid", "Explosives", "Water"], "question": "What is not a hazardous material?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1867}
{"candidates": ["The price of the materials.", "An emergency response telephone number.", "The use of the materials."], "question": "Shipping papers must include:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1868}
{"candidates": ["The destination", "The type of container of the materials", "The hazards class of the materials"], "question": "To know which placard you must use, you need to know:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1869}
{"candidates": ["Braced to prevent movement during transportation.", "Made of cardboard.", "Brightly-colored."], "question": "Containers of hazardous materials must be:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1871}
{"candidates": ["You can always use tunnels.", "You must have a written route plan.", "You should take the shortest possible route."], "question": "If transporting explosives:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1872}
{"candidates": ["The items do not need to be marked differently", "Circled by a pen or marker", "Highlighted in a contrasting color"], "question": "If a shipping paper has both hazardous and non-hazardous materials, how should the hazardous materials be marked?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1873}
{"candidates": ["Away from heat sources.", "Near heat sources.", "Away from shadows."], "question": "Load hazardous materials:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1874}
{"candidates": ["Continue driving to find a phone booth and call the National Response Center.", "Leave the area to find help.", "Park the vehicle."], "question": "If you identify hazardous materials leaking while you are driving, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1875}
{"candidates": ["The List of Hazardous Substances and Reportable Quantities", "The Periodic Table of Elements", "The Hazardous Materials Table (Title 49, CFR, \u00a7172.101)"], "question": "Which of the following is not a list to search to determine if an item is a hazardous material?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1876}
{"candidates": ["The packages should be placed in the cab", "The packages should be loaded on their side", "Radiation will pass through to other packages"], "question": "If transporting a package that contains radiation, it is important to know that:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1877}
{"candidates": ["An injured person requires hospitalization", "When there is no fire", "When a person is killed"], "question": "The National Response Center must be notified of an incident involving all of the following except:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1882}
{"candidates": ["By sounding a siren", "By the posting of placards on the truck", "By flashing lights on the truck"], "question": "If transporting hazardous materials, how are others warned?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1895}
{"candidates": ["Other drivers when they want to slow down.", "The truck driver to stop the vehicle.", "Other drivers when merging onto a freeway."], "question": "Why should you avoid forcing an automatic transmission into a lower gear at a high speed?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1924}
{"candidates": ["It is better to take the left lane", "It doesn\u2019t matter which lane you use", "It is better to take the right lane"], "question": "If you are turning left and there are two turning lanes:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1934}
{"candidates": ["Yellow", "Blue", "Green"], "question": "Vehicles with ABS have what color malfunction lamps to indicate the ABS is not working?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1935}
{"candidates": ["2", "1", "4"], "question": "You may not consumer alcohol within how many hours of going on duty?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1936}
{"candidates": ["Enter the intersection and wait until traffic clears.", "Merge into another lane and try to go around the traffic.", "Stay out of the intersection until traffic clears."], "question": "If you unlock the pintle hook with the converter dolly still under the rear trailer what will happen?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1954}
{"candidates": ["Each time the inspection is completed, different items should be looked at", "It is ok to do it in a different order each time", "The inspection should be done the same way each time"], "question": "When completing a pre-trip inspection:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1956}
{"candidates": ["Are in addition to other braking systems and do not reduce braking power", "Reduce the normal braking capacity", "Are not effective on larger vehicles"], "question": "Antilock Braking Systems:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1958}
{"candidates": ["Use water", "Wait for firefighters", "Stay inside the vehicle"], "question": "If you\u2019re not sure what to do with a fire, what should you do?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1959}
{"candidates": ["It is raining.", "Drivers turn too quickly.", "Drivers turn too slowly."], "question": "Rollovers happen when:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1964}
{"candidates": ["Ensure there is extra room when entering traffic", "Assume there is enough room to merge into traffic", "Stop suddenly if needed"], "question": "When driving a double or triple, the driver should:", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1991}
{"candidates": ["Any 3-axle vehicle regardless of the weight.", "A vehicle pulling two trailers.", "A 3-axle vehicle if the Gross Vehicle Weight is less than 6,000 pounds."], "question": "Why should you hang the electrical cable with the plug down when uncoupling?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1996}
{"candidates": ["The other side of the road is a broken line.", "The other side of the road is a solid line.", "Your side of the road is a broken line."], "question": "What is the function of an \"application pressure gauge\"?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 1999}
{"candidates": ["Transporting an unrestrained animal inside the vehicle.", "Listening to music through headphones that cover both ears", "Adjusting your outside mirrors."], "question": "What types of trailers can get stuck on raised crossings?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2003}
{"candidates": ["25 mph", "20 mph", "30 mph"], "question": "Because backing up is always dangerous, when you park try to do so in a way that will allow you to ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2004}
{"candidates": ["Help prevent traffic congestion.", "Get you to your destination much faster and safer.", "Increase your chances of an accident."], "question": "What does the air compressor governor control?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2011}
{"candidates": ["One vehicle is traveling faster or slower than the flow of traffic.", "All vehicles are traveling about the same speed.", "One lane of traffic is traveling faster than the other lanes."], "question": "You are doing a walk around inspection of a double trailer rig. You should be sure the converter dolly air tank drain valves are ____ and the pintle hook is ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2034}
{"candidates": ["Begin driving just after the vehicle starts", "Let the air compressor build up a minimum of 100 psi pressure in the primary and secondary systems", "Let the vehicle warm up to ensure the fuel reaches the engine"], "question": "Before driving a vehicle with a dual brake system, the driver should:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2060}
{"candidates": ["The vehicle will not shift out of gear", "The front lights will flash", "The warning light will come on"], "question": "What should happen if the air pressure in the air brake system tanks falls below55 psi?", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2061}
{"candidates": ["There is usually no noticeable affect", "Either the front or rear brakes will not be operating fully", "None of the brakes will work at all"], "question": "In a dual brake system, if one air system is very low on pressure:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2063}
{"candidates": ["Because the air gets old and needs to be replaced", "Because compressed air contains some water and the eater collects in the tanks", "To allow for a change in pressure"], "question": "Why do you need to drain the air tank regularly?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2064}
{"candidates": ["Always put one car length between you and the car ahead.", "Look only at the car in front of you while driving.", "Keep your eyes moving to look for possible hazards."], "question": "Shippers use the hazardous materials regulation to determine the product's ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2082}
{"candidates": ["Flashing lights", "Placards", "Color coded pieces of tape"], "question": "What is used to warn others of hazardous materials?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2102}
{"candidates": ["Any lane (as long as it is safe)", "The lane closest to the left curb", "The lane in the center of the road."], "question": "You are testing your trailer's service brakes. First, you should ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2112}
{"candidates": ["Leave a note on the vehicle.", "Both of the above.", "Report the accident without delay to the city police or, in unincorporated areas, to the CHP."], "question": "To prevent roll overs, drivers of combination vehicles should avoid ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2136}
{"candidates": ["The other side of the road is a broken line.", "The other side of the road is a solid line.", "Your side of the road is a broken line."], "question": "When stopping a trailer skid you should first recognize the skid. Once you have, you need to ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2142}
{"candidates": ["By touching", "By using the shipping papers", "By tasting"], "question": "If you notice a cargo leak, how should you identify the hazardous materials leaking?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2147}
{"candidates": ["At or slightly above the posted speed limit", "At the posted speed limit", "Well below the posted speed limit"], "question": "Highway curves should be taken:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2149}
{"candidates": ["About the same level of skill", "More skill", "Less skill"], "question": "Combination vehicles usually require \u00ad\u00ad\u00ad\u00ad\u00ad____ than single vehicle", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2151}
{"candidates": ["Heaviest at the front", "Heaviest in the middle", "Heaviest at the rear"], "question": "When loading a tank with bulkheads or smaller tanks, the load should be:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2153}
{"candidates": ["The vehicle will speed up", "You may have trouble putting the vehicle into the next gear", "You may kill the engine"], "question": "When switching gears, what happens if you remain in neutral too long?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2160}
{"candidates": ["A flag", "Hydraulic brakes", "ABS"], "question": "Truck tractors built after March 1, 1997, must be equipped with:", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2161}
{"candidates": ["The carrier", "The shipper", "The driver"], "question": "Who must mark and label the materials for shipping?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2185}
{"candidates": ["15 hours", "10 hours", "4 hours"], "question": "For tanks greater than 500 gallons, what is the maximum driving time within a work period?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2187}
{"candidates": ["Approaching you from behind.", "You have already passed.", "You are approaching from behind."], "question": "For school bus drivers, the danger zone may extend as much as ____ ft. from the front bumper.", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2219}
{"candidates": ["The first rain after a dry spell.", "During a heavy downpour.", "After it has been raining for awhile."], "question": "Before evacuating yourself and the students from the school bus during an emergency situation, you should ask yourself ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2231}
{"candidates": ["May be too slow for a bus", "May be too fast for a bus", "Is usually safe for buses too"], "question": "A posted speed safe for cars:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2301}
{"candidates": ["Wait until the passengers on the bus quiet down", "Open the forward door", "Open the emergency windows"], "question": "When driving a bus, one way to better hear if a train is coming is to:", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2303}
{"candidates": ["Parallel with the pavement.", "Turned to the right (away from the street).", "Turned to the left (toward the street)."], "question": "It's important that the battery box of your vehicle does not ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2339}
{"candidates": ["Farther behind the truck than you would for a passenger vehicle.", "No more than one car length behind the truck so the driver can see you.", "Closely behind the truck in bad weather because the driver can see farther ahead."], "question": "A safe place to evacuate students will generally be at least 100 ft. off the road except when ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2342}
{"candidates": ["Test your tires\u2019 traction while going uphill.", "Decrease the distance you look ahead of your vehicle.", "Avoid making fast turns and fast stops."], "question": "When your brake's main air pressure is lost ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2455}
{"candidates": ["When you want to pass a driver ahead of you who is turning right.", "During rush hour traffic if there are no bicyclists in the bike lane.", "When you are within 200 feet of a cross street where you plan to turn right."], "question": "To test the parking brake you should ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2457}
{"candidates": ["At least 30 feet but not more than 50 feet from the nearest track", "A maximum of 50 feet and a minimum of 15 feet from the nearest railroad track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 100 feet from the nearest track"], "question": "What should you do if you notice your trailer drifting while you are backing up?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2470}
{"candidates": ["Your side of the road is a broken line.", "The other side of the road is a solid line.", "The other side of the road is a broken line."], "question": "Placards are used to ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2484}
{"candidates": ["Approaching you from behind.", "You are approaching from behind.", "You have already passed."], "question": "Why should you not drive your vehicle if the air pressure does not build up quickly enough?", "answer": 1, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2489}
{"candidates": ["Should be treated as a separate traffic lane.", "May be crossed to enter or exit a private driveway.", "May not be crossed for any reason."], "question": "Rust around wheel nuts often means that ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2494}
{"candidates": ["You can frustrate the other drivers and make them angry.", "You help reduce traffic congestion.", "Your actions cannot result in a traffic citation."], "question": "A combination vehicle has two air lines: the emergency line and ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2508}
{"candidates": ["Next to a red painted curb.", "Within 100 feet of an elementary school.", "On the side of the freeway in an emergency."], "question": "What might you not be able to do if your vehicle is hydroplaning?", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2511}
{"candidates": ["When there are no vehicles approaching nearby.", "On a one-way street on a green arrow.", "Across two sets of solid double, yellow lines."], "question": "A combination vehicle has two air lines. The first is the service line and the second is ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "al", "type": "cdl", "id": 2529}
{"candidates": ["Cyclists could be riding at the very high speed.", "All the others.", "Cyclists are more vulnerable than motorists"], "question": "Why should drivers exercise greater care when bicyclists are riding nearby?", "answer": 2, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 2597}
{"candidates": ["At all times.", "Only during school hours.", "Unless you do not see any children present."], "question": "You must obey instructions from school crossing guards:", "answer": 0, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 2618}
{"candidates": ["That only vehicles next to the broken line may pass.", "That vehicles next to the solid yellow line may pass.", "That vehicles may pass in all directions."], "question": "When two vehicles approach an uncontrolled intersection, what is the driver of the vehicle on the left supposed to do?", "answer": 0, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 2622}
{"candidates": ["70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic.", "Between 65 mph and 70 mph.", "No faster than 65 mph."], "question": "You are driving on a freeway posted for 65 mph. Most of the other vehicles are driving 70 mph or faster. You may legally drive:", "answer": 2, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 2649}
{"candidates": ["Overspeeding.", "Driving under the influence of alcohol or other drugs.", "Reckless driving."], "question": "Which of the following is not a valid reason for revoking a driver's license?", "answer": 1, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 2655}
{"candidates": ["If the shoulder is wide enough to accommodate your vehicle", "Under no circumstances", "If the vehicle ahead of you is turning left."], "question": "You may drive off from the paved roadway to pass another vehicle:", "answer": 1, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 2672}
{"candidates": ["7", "6", "8"], "question": "How many classes of driver's licenses does the state of Alaska have?", "answer": 0, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 2684}
{"candidates": ["A speed just below the posted speed limit.", "A speed which matches the flow of traffic.", "The posted speed limit."], "question": "Which of the following choices shows an incorrect speed for the designated roadway?", "answer": 1, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 2686}
{"candidates": ["1 day.", "5 days.", "3 days."], "question": "Within how many days are you required to notify the Division of Motor Vehicles of your change in address or name?", "answer": 2, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 2713}
{"candidates": ["Keep your phone within easy reach so you won't need to take your eyes off the road.", "Use hands-free devices so you can keep both hands on the steering wheel.", "Review the number before answering a call."], "question": "The safest precaution that you can take regarding the use of cellular phones and driving is:", "answer": 1, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 2823}
{"candidates": ["Slow down or stop, if necessary, and then make the turn.", "Signal and turn immediately.", "Stop before entering the right lane and let all other traffic go first."], "question": "You are getting ready to make a right turn. You should:", "answer": 0, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 2824}
{"candidates": ["Obey traffic signs, traffic signals, road markings and traffic rules.", "Never yield to the vehicles.", "Wear glasses if you need them to see properly."], "question": "Which of these is NOT a valid safety tip for bicyclists to observe when operating their bicycle in Alaska?", "answer": 0, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 2833}
{"candidates": ["Avoid driving in the bicycle lane.", "Signal for 100 feet before turning.", "Move toward the left side of your lane."], "question": "Which of the following are ways to ensure you safely complete a left turn?", "answer": 1, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 2890}
{"candidates": ["A vehicle pulling two trailers.", "Any 3-axle vehicle regardless of the weight.", "A 3-axle vehicle if the Gross Vehicle Weight is less than 6,000 pounds."], "question": "With a Class C drivers license a person may drive:", "answer": 2, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 2921}
{"candidates": ["You can frustrate the other drivers and make them angry.", "Your actions cannot result in a traffic citation.", "You help reduce traffic congestion."], "question": "When you tailgate other drivers (drive close to their rear bumper):", "answer": 0, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 2974}
{"candidates": ["Stop and let the pedestrian cross the street.", "Make sure the pedestrian sees you, but continue driving.", "Carefully drive around the pedestrian."], "question": "A pedestrian is crossing your lane but there is no marked crosswalk. You should:", "answer": 0, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 3004}
{"candidates": ["Merge into another lane and try to go around the traffic.", "Enter the intersection and wait until traffic clears.", "Stay out of the intersection until traffic clears."], "question": "If you have a green light, but traffic is blocking the intersection, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 3005}
{"candidates": ["The lane in the center of the road.", "The lane closest to the left curb", "Any lane (as long as it is safe)"], "question": "To turn left from a multilane one-way street onto a one-way street, you should start your turn from:", "answer": 1, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 3036}
{"candidates": ["Next to a red painted curb.", "On the side of the freeway in an emergency.", "Within 100 feet of an elementary school."], "question": "You may not park your vehicle:", "answer": 0, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 3037}
{"candidates": ["No, you can't applying for a driver's license when applying to become an organ donor.", "Yes, on the license application form, you can check the box indicating that you would like to become a registered donor.", "Not sure."], "question": "Can you apply to become an organ donor when applying for a driver's license?", "answer": 1, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 3041}
{"candidates": ["When you want to pass a driver ahead of you who is turning right.", "During rush hour traffic if there are no bicyclists in the bike lane.", "When you are within 200 feet of a cross street where you plan to turn right."], "question": "When can you drive in a bike lane?", "answer": 2, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 3064}
{"candidates": ["To 20-25 mph.", "To 15-20 mph.", "To 25-30 mph."], "question": "What speed should you slow down to when approaching a roundabout?", "answer": 0, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 3074}
{"candidates": ["2", "3", "1"], "question": "What is the minimum number of rear-end tail lights required for your car?", "answer": 1, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 3103}
{"candidates": ["6", "2", "12"], "question": "If you speed 20 mph or more over the speed limit, how many points will be entered on your Alaska Driving Record?", "answer": 0, "state": "ak", "type": "permit", "id": 3126}
{"candidates": ["Your actions cannot result in a traffic citation.", "You help reduce traffic congestion.", "You can frustrate the other drivers and make them angry."], "question": "If you see a driver merging onto your highway, what should you do?", "answer": 2, "state": "ak", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 3221}
{"candidates": ["At all times.", "Only during school hours.", "Unless you do not see any children present."], "question": "What can you do to get yourself familiar with a new motorcycle?", "answer": 0, "state": "ak", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 3222}
{"candidates": ["A 3-axle vehicle if the Gross Vehicle Weight is less than 6,000 pounds.", "Any 3-axle vehicle regardless of the weight.", "A vehicle pulling two trailers."], "question": "If your throttle is stuck and you cannot free it, what should you do?", "answer": 0, "state": "ak", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 3252}
{"candidates": ["15", "10", "5"], "question": "While walking to your cycle which of the following tasks should be done?", "answer": 2, "state": "ak", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 3277}
{"candidates": ["The lane in the center of the road.", "Any lane (as long as it is safe)", "The lane closest to the left curb"], "question": "To make a quick turn you should definitely ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "ak", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 3282}
{"candidates": ["Enter the intersection and wait until traffic clears.", "Merge into another lane and try to go around the traffic.", "Stay out of the intersection until traffic clears."], "question": "Which of the following is a drug that can affect your riding skills?", "answer": 2, "state": "ak", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 3310}
{"candidates": ["Use hands-free devices so you can keep both hands on the steering wheel.", "Review the number before answering a call.", "Keep your phone within easy reach so you won't need to take your eyes off the road."], "question": "Which of the following are listed in the Alaska Motorcycle Handbook as safe actions to take when riding on slippery surfaces?", "answer": 0, "state": "ak", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 3371}
{"candidates": ["70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic.", "No faster than 65 mph.", "Between 65 mph and 70 mph."], "question": "Do motorcycles need as much distance to stop as cars do?", "answer": 1, "state": "ak", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 3427}
{"candidates": ["By using only the front brake", "By using both brakes", "By using only the rear brake"], "question": "How should you make a quick stop on wet pavement?", "answer": 1, "state": "ak", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 3469}
{"candidates": ["Carefully drive around the pedestrian.", "Stop and let the pedestrian cross the street.", "Make sure the pedestrian sees you, but continue driving."], "question": "When preparing to ride, you must check which part of the motorcycle, while sitting on it?", "answer": 1, "state": "ak", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 3486}
{"candidates": ["During rush hour traffic if there are no bicyclists in the bike lane.", "When you are within 200 feet of a cross street where you plan to turn right.", "When you want to pass a driver ahead of you who is turning right."], "question": "What tools should you not depend on as a tool when driving?", "answer": 1, "state": "ak", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 3546}
{"candidates": ["Under no circumstances", "If the shoulder is wide enough to accommodate your vehicle", "If the vehicle ahead of you is turning left."], "question": "Of the following which is the most important to do before riding?", "answer": 0, "state": "ak", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 3576}
{"candidates": ["At or near the same speed as the traffic on the freeway.", "The posted speed limit for traffic on the freeway.", "5 to 10 MPH slower than the traffic on the freeway."], "question": "How does shifting from one portion of a lane to another benefit motorcyclists?", "answer": 0, "state": "ak", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 3605}
{"candidates": ["A special lane for slow moving vehicles", "The carpool lane and must merge into the next lane", "An exit lane"], "question": "You are driving in the far right lane of a four lane freeway and notice thick broken white lines on the left side of your lane. You are driving in", "answer": 2, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5015}
{"candidates": ["Maintain your speed and don\u2019t change lanes", "Slow and pull off the road", "Turn on your high beams"], "question": "If you come upon a severe dust storm, you should", "answer": 1, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5021}
{"candidates": ["200 feet", "500 feet", "100 feet"], "question": "When approaching a car from behind at night, lower your high beam headlights when you are within:", "answer": 0, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5045}
{"candidates": ["You should come to a safe stop and wait for the light to turn green", "You should proceed with caution", "You must clear the intersection before the light turns red"], "question": "You are approaching an intersection where the traffic light has changed to yellow:", "answer": 0, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5049}
{"candidates": ["A left turn against a red light can only be made within 100 feet of an elementary school.", "A left turn against a red light can only be made from a one-way street onto a one-way street.", "A left turn against a red light can only be made on the side of the freeway in an emergency."], "question": "When are you allowed to make a left turn against a red light?", "answer": 1, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5061}
{"candidates": ["25 mph", "15 mph", "30 mph"], "question": "If no speed limit is posted around a school crosswalk, what is standard speed limit?", "answer": 0, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5064}
{"candidates": ["Should ride facing traffic", "Should follow the same laws as drivers", "Must stay in the right lane"], "question": "Bicyclists:", "answer": 1, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5079}
{"candidates": ["Except in school zones", "From a two-way road to a one-way road", "From a one-way road to a one-way road"], "question": "Unless prohibited by a sign, you may left turn on red:", "answer": 2, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5080}
{"candidates": ["10 days", "45 days", "30 days"], "question": "You must notify MVD of an address change within:", "answer": 0, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5106}
{"candidates": ["Slowing down to look at collision scene", "Using public transportation instead of your vehicle", "Avoiding unnecessary lane changes"], "question": "Which of the following blocks the smooth flow of traffic?", "answer": 0, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5135}
{"candidates": ["Bandages.", "Mircoscope.", "Gauze."], "question": "What is an item that does NOT need to be included in a roadside emergency preparedness kit?", "answer": 2, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5159}
{"candidates": ["Directly before and after school hours.", "You must always obey school crossing-guards.", "There are children present."], "question": "You must obey instructions from school crossing-guards when:", "answer": 1, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5173}
{"candidates": ["Low beams.", "Fog lights only.", "High beams."], "question": "When driving in fog, you should use your:", "answer": 0, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5178}
{"candidates": ["Only where indicated by a sign", "Only on a divided road", "Except where prohibited by a sign"], "question": "Right turn on red is permitted:", "answer": 2, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5194}
{"candidates": ["Stop before entering the intersection as long as you can do so safely.", "Stop. Yield to all cross traffic before crossing the intersection.", "Slow down and cross the intersection carefully."], "question": "You see a flashing yellow traffic signal at an upcoming intersection. The flashing yellow light means:", "answer": 2, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5209}
{"candidates": ["Your front wheels must be turned toward the street.", "One of your rear wheels must touch the curb.", "Your wheels must be within 18 inches of the curb."], "question": "When parking your vehicle parallel to the curb on a level street.", "answer": 2, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5218}
{"candidates": ["8", "10", "12"], "question": "If you accumulate ____ or more points within any 12-month driving period, you will be required to attend Traffic Survival School, or your license may be suspended.", "answer": 0, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5221}
{"candidates": ["15 mph", "25 mph", "10 mph"], "question": "The speed limit when approaching a school crossing is:", "answer": 0, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5228}
{"candidates": ["Honk the horn.", "Stop at the sidewalk.", "Yield to vehicles already on the main road."], "question": "When entering a road from an alley:", "answer": 2, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5288}
{"candidates": ["Laughing gas.", "Greenhouse gas.", "Crying gas."], "question": "What name is nitrous oxide commonly known as?", "answer": 0, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5309}
{"candidates": ["The driver's age.", "The square of the speed of the car at the instant the brakes are applied.", "The square of initial velocity."], "question": "Which of the following choices is NOT directly related to braking distance?", "answer": 1, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5312}
{"candidates": ["May not be crossed for any reason.", "Should be treated as a separate traffic lane.", "May be crossed to enter or exit a private driveway."], "question": "Two sets of solid, double, yellow lines that are two or more feet apart:", "answer": 0, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5327}
{"candidates": ["Any lane can do.", "The far right lane.", "The far left lane."], "question": "Which lane can you safely make a left turn on a one-way road onto a one-way road?", "answer": 2, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5334}
{"candidates": ["Within the distance lighted by your parking lights.", "Within 5-10 seconds.", "Within the distance you can see ahead."], "question": "When driving at night, be sure that you can stop:", "answer": 2, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5357}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "Attend alcohol treatment programs.", "Pay the fine."], "question": "What will a person be required to do if they commit an aggravated DUI?", "answer": 0, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5364}
{"candidates": ["If the driver is arrested for driving under influence.", "All the others.", "If the driver is found to be driving with a revoked license or driving with a license suspended."], "question": "A person's car may be impounded for which of the following reasons?", "answer": 1, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5372}
{"candidates": ["In a marked crosswalk", "In any crosswalk or intersection", "Crossing any street"], "question": "Give the right-of-way to any pedestrian who is:", "answer": 2, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5374}
{"candidates": ["At least 200 feet", "3 to 6 seconds", "At least 500 feet"], "question": "If a fire vehicle is responding to an emergency, you must stay back:", "answer": 2, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5376}
{"candidates": ["The truck driver to stop the vehicle.", "Other drivers when they want to slow down.", "Other drivers when merging onto a freeway."], "question": "If a vehicle is approaching you from behind at a high rate of speed, what should you do when stopped at a light?", "answer": 0, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5401}
{"candidates": ["There are children present.", "You must always obey school crossing-guards.", "Directly before and after school hours."], "question": "When driving, all of the following are good rules to follow except ____?", "answer": 1, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5402}
{"candidates": ["Be cautious and drive through it, since dust storms usually don\u2019t last very long", "Slow down, carefully pull completely off the road, turn off your lights, take your foot off the brake and wait until the storm passes", "Slow down, carefully pull completely off the road, turn on your lights and wait until the storm passes"], "question": "If a dust storm is approaching or you encounter one while driving, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5404}
{"candidates": ["Look out the back window", "Keep other vehicles out of your blind spots", "Frequently check your rearview mirror"], "question": "To know where traffic is behind you:", "answer": 2, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5406}
{"candidates": ["Other drivers can 'cut' in front of you, improving traffic flow", "It inflates to protect you from injury in case of a collision", "If another driver makes a mistake, you have time to react"], "question": "What is the benefit of a space cushion around your vehicle", "answer": 2, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5407}
{"candidates": ["Traffic Survival School", "Traffic Regulation School", "Court"], "question": "If you ran a red light and received a traffic citation, upon conviction you must attend ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5428}
{"candidates": ["Headlights.", "Interior lights", "Parking lights"], "question": "It is a very windy day. You are driving and a dust storm blows across the freeway reducing your visibility. You should drive slower and turn on your:", "answer": 0, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5442}
{"candidates": ["6 months", "1 year", "3 months"], "question": "On a first violation, a person convicted of not having/not able to produce evidence of current financial responsibility for the vehicle, could receive a suspension of their license for ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5453}
{"candidates": ["Turn off the heater. ", "Add coolant. ", "Drive faster to home."], "question": "What should you do in the event of your engine overheating?", "answer": 0, "state": "az", "type": "permit", "id": 5454}
{"candidates": ["When you entered the intersection on the green light.", "Under no circumstances.", "During rush hour traffic."], "question": "When carrying passengers and cargo you will need extra equipment. Which of these is an example?", "answer": 1, "state": "az", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 5611}
{"candidates": ["During rush hour traffic.", "When you entered the intersection on the green light.", "Under no circumstances."], "question": "What does the Arizona Motorcycle Manual characterize as a large animal?", "answer": 2, "state": "az", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 5636}
{"candidates": ["Stop before entering the intersection as long as you can do so safely.", "Slow down and cross the intersection carefully.", "Stop. Yield to all cross traffic before crossing the intersection."], "question": "If a friend has clearly had too much to drink, you should ____", "answer": 1, "state": "az", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 5670}
{"candidates": ["Within three feet of a private driveway.", "In an unmarked crosswalk", "In a bicycle lane."], "question": "The greatest amount of conflict between you and other traffic is at:", "answer": 1, "state": "az", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 5701}
{"candidates": ["Change lanes and maintain your current speed.", "Be prepared for workers and equipment ahead.", "Slow down because the lane ends ahead."], "question": "When you ride in a group with others, you should ____", "answer": 1, "state": "az", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 5730}
{"candidates": ["You can frustrate the other drivers and make them angry.", "Your actions cannot result in a traffic citation.", "You help reduce traffic congestion."], "question": "What is the best thing to wear to increase your chances of being seen when riding a motorcycle?", "answer": 0, "state": "az", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 5756}
{"candidates": ["The first rain after a dry spell.", "During a heavy downpour.", "After it has been raining for awhile."], "question": "What is the limit for blood alcohol content that you would need to be considered intoxicated?", "answer": 0, "state": "az", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 5757}
{"candidates": ["Yes, it is a good defensive driving technique.", "No, you can block traffic when you drive too slowly.", "Yes, it is always safer than driving faster than other traffic."], "question": "A safe way to keep friends from hurting themselves while intoxicated is ____", "answer": 1, "state": "az", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 5759}
{"candidates": ["Cannot see the vehicle directly to your right.", "Have passed the other vehicle\u2019s front bumper.", "See the vehicle\u2019s headlights in your rear view mirror."], "question": "What tests are required to be administered for a three-wheel license endorsement?", "answer": 2, "state": "az", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 5788}
{"candidates": ["High beams.", "Fog lights only.", "Low beams."], "question": "What is required for you to earn your license?", "answer": 2, "state": "az", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 5818}
{"candidates": ["Directly before and after school hours.", "There are children present.", "You must always obey school crossing-guards."], "question": "Three major factors come into play when determining your BAC level. They are the amount you drink, how fast you drink and ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "az", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 5820}
{"candidates": ["Decrease the distance you look ahead of your vehicle.", "Test your tires\u2019 traction while going uphill.", "Avoid making fast turns and fast stops."], "question": "What gear is recommended to prevent injury on a motorcycle?", "answer": 2, "state": "az", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 5851}
{"candidates": ["Talk on your cell phone while driving.", "Always signal your intention when changing lanes.", "Use your horn frequently."], "question": "What can you do to reduce \"road rage\"?", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7262}
{"candidates": ["At least 500 ft from any oncoming vehicle.", "At least 200 ft from any oncoming vehicle.", "At least 300 ft from any oncoming vehicle."], "question": "When should you dim your high beams?", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7277}
{"candidates": ["Crossing to enter or exit a private driveway", "Crossing a railroad", "Merging on a multi-lane road"], "question": "You should adjust your speed to match the vehicles around you when ____?", "answer": 2, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7280}
{"candidates": ["Tilt the steering wheel downward, if possible, so the airbag points toward your chest instead of your head or neck.", "Move your seat back so that you are at least 10 inches from the steering wheel.", "All the others."], "question": "What is the best answer if your car is equipped with a passenger side airbag?", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7299}
{"candidates": ["Vehicles", "A hazard", "Dangerous"], "question": "When used on roadways, bicyclists are considered", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7316}
{"candidates": ["Go ahead. The motorist has the right-of-way", "Wait for them to cross", "Pull to the right and go behind them"], "question": "If the motorist sees pedestrians in a crosswalk, what should the motorist do?", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7321}
{"candidates": ["Signal and pull into the slow lane", "Put on your hazard lights and pull off the road", "Stop in your lane and put on your hazard lights"], "question": "The vehicle has a mechanical problem", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7349}
{"candidates": ["Sound your horn as you pass", "Flash your headlights as you pass", "Judge the distance to the first oncoming vehicle"], "question": "To pass on a two-lane road, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7373}
{"candidates": ["Fail a smog test for your vehicle.", "Sell or transfer your vehicle.", "Get a new prescription for lenses or contacts."], "question": "You must notify the DMV within 5 days if you:", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7391}
{"candidates": ["Right, not a privilege", "Privilege, not a right", "Requirement"], "question": "Having a Driver\u2019s License is a:", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7418}
{"candidates": ["Have a decreased reaction time", "Yield right-of-way to emergency vehicles", "Keep a 3-4 second following distance"], "question": "A driver who has been drinking is more likely to:", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7437}
{"candidates": ["Blood alcohol concentration", "Blood alcohol content", "Blood alcohol conservation"], "question": "BAC means:", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7496}
{"candidates": ["Fail to carefully watch for workers and moving equipment.", "All the others.", "Tailgate another vehicle."], "question": "Which of the following is a dangerous thing to do in work zones?", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7521}
{"candidates": ["When they are clean and dry.", "Just after it starts to rain.", "When it has been raining hard for several hours."], "question": "Streets and highways are most slippery:", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7534}
{"candidates": ["Stop, check for cars and enter when safe.", "Check for cars, increase your speed to match the flow of traffic and merge when the way is clear.", "Check for cars, reduce speed to 25 MPH before entering traffic lane."], "question": "When entering an interstate highway, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7558}
{"candidates": ["Call the Police.", "Check for Injuries.", "All the others."], "question": "When you are at the scene of a crash, which of these should you do?", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7577}
{"candidates": ["At all times.", "Unless they conflict with existing signs, signals, or laws.", "Only if you see orange cones on the road ahead."], "question": "You see a signal person at a road construction site ahead. You should obey his or her instructions:", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7600}
{"candidates": ["Must merge into the bicycle lane before turning.", "May not enter the bicycle lane.", "Should only merge into the bicycle lane if you stop before turning."], "question": "To make a right turn at the corner, you:", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7603}
{"candidates": ["expects no breaks and gives none", "considers what other drivers might do and is prepared", "knows the other driver will do the right thing"], "question": "Which of the following describes the thinking of a defensive driver?", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7644}
{"candidates": ["Your front wheels must be turned toward the street.", "Your wheels must be within 18 inches of the curb.", "One of your rear wheels must touch the curb."], "question": "Which of the following statements about tractor-trailers is true?", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7667}
{"candidates": ["Safely get off the road.", "All the others.", "Carefully engage emergency brake."], "question": "If your brakes stop working, you should try____.", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7697}
{"candidates": ["Low-light conditions. ", "Bright lights, reflections and glare.", "All the others."], "question": "Which of the following items can reduce your field of vision while driving?", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7722}
{"candidates": ["3", "5", "2"], "question": "You should have your eyes examined every ____ years to check for poor vision.", "answer": 2, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7785}
{"candidates": ["Deaf person", "Blind person", "Pedestrian"], "question": "A ____ is an individual who cannot see you.", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7786}
{"candidates": ["Take a few minutes to cool off.", "Play the radio loud so you won\u2019t think about it", "Drive on the interstate so you can let off steam."], "question": "If you have an argument with another person and you are angry, before driving a car you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7822}
{"candidates": ["Stop and help.", "Exchange information.", "Leave the scene."], "question": "What should you NOT do when you see a traffic crash?", "answer": 2, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7842}
{"candidates": ["1 hour", "5 mins", "2 hours"], "question": "How long does it take alcohol to get from the bloodstream to the brain?", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "permit", "id": 7847}
{"candidates": ["The roadway under a bridge", "Dry pavement", "Road markings"], "question": "Driving on ____ may provide poor traction", "answer": 2, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 7849}
{"candidates": ["Move toward the left side of your lane.", "Signal for 100 feet before turning.", "Avoid driving in the bicycle lane."], "question": "A skid can occur if you ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 7907}
{"candidates": ["stay in place when let go", "snap back when let go", "stay loose when let go"], "question": "Before a ride, a motorcycle operator should check the throttle. The throttle should", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 7909}
{"candidates": ["Closer", "Farther", "Larger"], "question": "Smaller vehicles appear ____ and slower than they really are.", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 7917}
{"candidates": ["In about two hours", "In about an hour", "Within minutes"], "question": "Alcohol reaches the brain about how long after being consumed?", "answer": 2, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 7922}
{"candidates": ["One-quarter", "Full-face", "Three-quarter"], "question": "Which is not a common type of helmet?", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 7924}
{"candidates": ["continue straight through the tracks.", "attempt to cross the tracks at a 90 degree angle.", "use the shoulder so you can slow down to cross the tracks"], "question": "When a motorcycle driver crosses railroad tracks, it is usually best to:", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 7928}
{"candidates": ["One lane of traffic is traveling faster than the other lanes.", "All vehicles are traveling about the same speed.", "One vehicle is traveling faster or slower than the flow of traffic."], "question": "When is it ever completely safe to consume drugs and/or alcohol before riding a motorcycle", "answer": 2, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 7929}
{"candidates": ["Stop before entering the intersection as long as you can do so safely.", "Slow down and cross the intersection carefully.", "Stop. Yield to all cross traffic before crossing the intersection."], "question": "If you are convicted of riding under the influence of drugs or alcohol, which of the following penalties may you receive?", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 7931}
{"candidates": ["Transporting an unrestrained animal inside the vehicle.", "Adjusting your outside mirrors.", "Listening to music through headphones that cover both ears"], "question": "What is the best option, or combination of options to maximize your visibility when riding?", "answer": 2, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 7932}
{"candidates": ["So you could be seen in the vehicle\u2019s side mirror", "So you could be seen next to the other vehicle", "So you could be seen in the vehicle\u2019s rear view mirror"], "question": "When riding behind a vehicle, you should position yourself:", "answer": 2, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 7943}
{"candidates": ["Is better than shifting before the curve.", "Is the best way to control your speed.", "Should only be done if it can be done smoothly."], "question": "Upshifting or downshifting in a curve:", "answer": 2, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 7951}
{"candidates": ["Immediately take it out on the highway", "Get familiar with it in a controlled area", "Assume all controls are in the same location as on your motorcycle"], "question": "If you borrow a motorcycle, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 7952}
{"candidates": ["Adjust your speed accordingly", "Let others know your intentions by sounding your horn or using lights", "Not let others know your intentions."], "question": "If you need to react to a danger in the road, which is one item you SHOULD NOT do:", "answer": 2, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 7969}
{"candidates": ["The center of the lane", "The left side of the lane", "The right side of the lane"], "question": "When being passed by another vehicle, which lane position should you be in?", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 7987}
{"candidates": ["not recommended because you may be in their blind spot.", "recommended because you are still in a separate lane", "recommended because it blocks the wind"], "question": "On a motorcycle, driving alongside another vehicle in the next lane over is:", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 7995}
{"candidates": ["Not return to the lane until you see the front of the truck in your rear view mirror", "Return to the lane whenever you want to since you are in front of the truck now", "As soon as you have passed the truck, it is acceptable to get over to the lane"], "question": "After passing a truck on a two-way road, you should", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8007}
{"candidates": ["Do them both (brake and swerve) at the same time", "Use only the front brake while swerving", "Do one (brake or swerve), then the other"], "question": "If to avoid a danger, you must brake and swerve, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8008}
{"candidates": ["Glance at the paint to make sure it is not chipped", "Test of the turn signals", "Check of the tires"], "question": "A pre-ride inspection should include all of the following except:", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8013}
{"candidates": ["Apply both brakes at the same time", "Only use the front brake", "Only use the rear brake"], "question": "When a motorcyclist needs to stop quickly, he or she should ____ .", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8017}
{"candidates": ["Ride in the center portion of the lane", "Ride in the left portion of the lane", "Ride in the right portion of the lane"], "question": "If you are being passed from behind, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8018}
{"candidates": ["100", "75", "50"], "question": "When riding in a group, where should the beginners or inexperienced riders go?", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8025}
{"candidates": ["It can affect your ability to operate a motorcycle.", "Your riding skills will not be affected.", "You cannot be arrested for drinking and riding."], "question": "If you have only one drink before riding:", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8032}
{"candidates": ["Conditions that look the same ahead as you are driving on.", "Traffic control devices, such as signals and signs", "A change in road and surface characteristics"], "question": "All drivers should anticipate potential dangers and think of ways to avoid those dangers. Which is NOT a potential problem?", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8035}
{"candidates": ["Fit snugly", "Be uncomfortable", "Be loose fitting and flap when riding"], "question": "When wearing a jacket for protection, the jacket should:", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8040}
{"candidates": ["Encouraged if traffic is congested", "Usually prohibited", "Acceptable if vehicles are travelling slowly"], "question": "Lane sharing is:", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8045}
{"candidates": ["Is acceptable all the time", "May increase the risk of riding and should be done with caution", "Is ok, since it is only over-the-counter medication, it is likely not too strong"], "question": "Taking over-the-counter medication before riding:", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8060}
{"candidates": ["Both brakes always need to be used at the same time", "Using the front brake would increase stability of the motorcycle.", "Using the front brake could cause the bike to tip over"], "question": "Why should the front brake not be used when making a u-turn?", "answer": 2, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8062}
{"candidates": ["To determine if vehicles behind you are aware that you are stopped.", "To look for people pulling out of parking spots.", "To watch for pedestrians"], "question": "Using your mirrors can be helpful in determining the conditions around you. What is a reason for using your mirrors while stopped at an intersection?", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8072}
{"candidates": ["Should give a clear view to either side.", "Is not needed if your motorcycle is equipped with a windshield.", "Is only needed when riding in bad weather."], "question": "Eye protection:", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8097}
{"candidates": ["Continue to use the lights", "Honk the horn to notify other drivers of the turn", "Use hand signals"], "question": "If bright sunlight makes it difficult to see the turn signal, the motorcyclist should:", "answer": 2, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8098}
{"candidates": ["Increase following distance", "Increase speed", "Decrease following distance"], "question": "When riding at night, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8099}
{"candidates": ["No parking", "The right edge of the traffic lane", "Merge"], "question": "A solid white line on the side of the road means", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8106}
{"candidates": ["Should only be worn while riding at night.", "Do not increase a motorcycle rider's safety.", "Can make motorcycle riders easier to see."], "question": "Brightly colored, reflective helmets and clothing:", "answer": 2, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8110}
{"candidates": ["trying to judge if you can go faster than other vehicles.", "looking for potential escape routes near intersections, shopping areas or schools.", "looking at pedestrians"], "question": "Part of scanning for dangers on or near the road includes", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8113}
{"candidates": ["The motorcycle should not lean", "The motorcycle and rider should lean in the same direction", "The motorcycle and rider should lean in opposite directions"], "question": "In normal turns,", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8119}
{"candidates": ["Slowly pass vehicles that seem to be stopped for no reason.", "Look to the sides of your vehicle to see what is coming.", "Stop, listen, and proceed cautiously."], "question": "To increase conspicuity, when should a headlight be used?", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8143}
{"candidates": ["Either over or in front of the rear axle.", "Piled up against a sissy bar or frame on the back of the seat.", "Carried on the gas tank in front of the driver."], "question": "If you must carry a load it should be:", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8151}
{"candidates": ["Drive faster than during the day.", "Drive at the same rate of speed as you would during the day", "Drive slower than you normally would during the day"], "question": "When riding a motorcycle at night, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8153}
{"candidates": ["On the left side of the lane", "In a position that allows you to see and be seen the most", "In the center of the lane"], "question": "When entering a curve, where should you position the motorcycle?", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8159}
{"candidates": ["Staggered", "Single-file", "Paired up"], "question": "What formation should be used by motorcycle operators riding in groups?", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8161}
{"candidates": ["use your mirrors and turn your head.", "use your mirrors and, unless you notice anything unusual, you do not need to turn your head.", "either use your mirrors or turn your head."], "question": "When changing lanes,a motorcycle driver should:", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8172}
{"candidates": ["Slow down because the lane ends ahead.", "Change lanes and maintain your current speed.", "Be prepared for workers and equipment ahead."], "question": "As a motorcyclist, if you are positioned in the right lane you should be able to ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8177}
{"candidates": ["Get on the motorcycle before you", "Hold firmly to your waist, hips or belt", "Sit as far back as possible"], "question": "When preparing to ride with a passenger, you should instruct the passenger before your ride to", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8190}
{"candidates": ["Have long heels", "Cover your ankles", "Have long laces"], "question": "Boots or shoes should:", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8195}
{"candidates": ["That vehicles may pass in all directions.", "That vehicles next to the solid yellow line may pass.", "That only vehicles next to the broken line may pass."], "question": "Studies have shown that most motorcyclists involved in a crash ____", "answer": 2, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8203}
{"candidates": ["It is OK for small children to ride in the front passenger seat of your car.", "Small children should ride in the back seat.", "Use the rear-facing child restraint system in the front passenger seat."], "question": "For experienced riders, how many hours on average do they ride in a day?", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8205}
{"candidates": ["Improper tire inflation", "A lack of fuel", "A lack of oil"], "question": "Engines will seize because of", "answer": 2, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8224}
{"candidates": ["Flash your lights to signal another vehicle to go", "Yield to the vehicle on the right", "Continue through the intersection and expect the other vehicle to stop"], "question": "At an intersection with no traffic signs or traffic lights, what do you do?", "answer": 1, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8226}
{"candidates": ["Not assume the other driver will make space for you to return to your lane.", "Assume the other driver will let you pass if you use your turn signal.", "Assume the other driver will maintain a constant speed."], "question": "What areas are going to be tested on the On-Motorcycle skill test before earning your license?", "answer": 0, "state": "ar", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 8231}
{"candidates": ["The lane closest to the middle of the street", "The far left lane", "Any lane available"], "question": "To Turn left from a one-way street with multiple lanes onto a two way street, start the turn in", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9609}
{"candidates": ["The road ahead may be slippery", "There is a sharp curve in the road ahead", "The road ahead has many curves"], "question": "The yellow signs means:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9610}
{"candidates": ["Stay in your lane, slow down, and let it pass", "Drive to the right edge of the road and slow down", "Drive to the right edge of the road and stop"], "question": "You are driving on a city street and see an emergency vehicle with flashing lights behind you. What should you do?", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9611}
{"candidates": ["Always dangerous to do", "Only dangerous in large vehicles", "Dangerous if you have a helper"], "question": "Backing your vehicle is", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9613}
{"candidates": ["Always drive at the posted speed limit", "Never drive faster than is safe for current conditions", "Keep your speed close to that of other traffic"], "question": "California's \"Basic Speed Law\" says you must", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9616}
{"candidates": ["Always slow down and maintain your position", "Assert your right of way by driving faster", "Make room for the merging traffic, if possible"], "question": "You are on the freeway and traffic is merging into your lane. You should:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9617}
{"candidates": ["Flaggers (signal persons) at construction sites", "security guards patrolling parking lots", "Other drivers whose vehicles are broken down on the roadway"], "question": "Drivers are required to obey instructions from", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9618}
{"candidates": ["Move your vehicle out of the traffic lane, if possible", "Not move your vehicle for any reason", "Leave your vehicle in the traffic lane until law enforcement arrives"], "question": "You are involved in a minor collision at an intersection. There are no injuries and very little vehicle damage, you should", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9619}
{"candidates": ["Solid red lights, red arrows and flashing yellow lights", "Solid red lights, flashing red lights and yellow lights", "Solid red lights, flashing red lights and blacked out traffic signals"], "question": "For which of the following traffic lights must you always stop your vehicle:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9620}
{"candidates": ["0.08% -- Eight hundredths of one percent", "0.05% -- five hundredths of one percent", "0.10% -- One tenth of one percent"], "question": "It is illegal for a person 21 years of age or older to drive with a blood alcohol concentration (BAC) that is____ or higher", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9623}
{"candidates": ["On a one-way street on a green arrow.", "When there are no vehicles approaching nearby.", "Across two sets of solid double, yellow lines."], "question": "U-turns in residential districts are legal:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9627}
{"candidates": ["reduces collisions by preventing from being \"cut off\"", "cannot result in traffic violation", "Can frustrate other drivers and make them angry"], "question": "Tailgating other drivers (driving too close to their rear bumper)", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9636}
{"candidates": ["whenever bicyclists are not present", "if you drive slower than 15mph", "No more than 200 feet before making a right turn"], "question": "You may drive in a bike lane", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9638}
{"candidates": ["You should treat the signal like a stop sign", "Stop. Yield to all cross traffic before crossing in the intersection", "Slow down and be alert at the upcoming intersection"], "question": "A flashing yellow traffic signal at an intersection means", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9639}
{"candidates": ["Should drive slower than other traffic for 200 feet.", "Should wait for the first two vehicles to pass, then drive into the lane.", "Need a large enough gap to get up to the speed of traffic."], "question": "When you enter traffic from a stop (away from the curb), you:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9643}
{"candidates": ["Stop then proceed when all the pedestrians have crossed", "Cautiously pass the vehicle at 10mph or less", "Change lanes look carefully and pass the stopped vehicle"], "question": "The driver ahead of you stops at a crosswalk. What should you do?:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9649}
{"candidates": ["Stopping immediately, even if you are in an intersection", "Driving near to the right edge of the road as possible and stopping", "Moving into the right lane and driving slowly until it has passed"], "question": "You must yield the right of way to an emergency vehicle by", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9651}
{"candidates": ["Away from the curb", "Into the curb", "Parallel to the curb"], "question": "Which way do you turn your front wheels to park downhill next to a curb:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9652}
{"candidates": ["The sides of the pickup bed are at least 24 inches high", "In secured seats and using approved safety belts", "The back of the pickup is covered with a camper shell"], "question": "A person may legally ride in the back of a pickup truck when:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9653}
{"candidates": ["Continue through the intersection, pull to the right and stop", "Stop immediately in the intersection until it passes", "Pull to the right in the intersection and stop"], "question": "You are crossing an intersection and an emergency vehicle is approaching with a siren and flashing lights. You should:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9654}
{"candidates": ["Under no circumstances because it is always legal", "If road or wheather conditions require a slower speed", "Only if you are approaching a sharp curve in the road"], "question": "If you drive 55mph in a 55mph zone, you can be given a speeding ticket", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9671}
{"candidates": ["On your headlights", "Up the instrumental panel lights", "On your parking lights"], "question": "At dawn or dusk or in rain or snow, it can be hard to see and be seen. A good way to let other drivers know you are there is to turn", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9672}
{"candidates": ["25mph", "35mph", "30mph"], "question": "You are driving on a freeway posted for 65mph. Traffic is heavy and moving at 35mph. The best speed for you vehicle is most likely:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9673}
{"candidates": ["The driver you passed signals you to return to your lane", "You signal for three seconds your intention to return to your lane", "You see the headlights of the passed vehicle in your rearview mirror"], "question": "After passing a vehicle, it is safe to return to your driving lane when:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9675}
{"candidates": ["Illegally share lanes with motor vehicles", "Must ride facing oncoming traffic", "Are entitled to share the road with you"], "question": "You must look for bicycle riders in the same lanes used by motor vehicles because they:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9676}
{"candidates": ["To see potential hazards early", "And focus on the middle of the road", "Because it is a legal requirement"], "question": "While driving, you should look 10 to 15 seconds ahead of you", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9678}
{"candidates": ["The area around the trucks where your car is no longer visible.", "The area around the trucks where you are so close that the truck can't stop or maneuver safely.", "All the others."], "question": "A big truck driver's blind spots, sometimes known as the \"NO ZONE\", are where?", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9691}
{"candidates": ["That vehicles next to the solid yellow line may pass.", "That only vehicles next to the broken line may pass.", "That vehicles may pass in all directions."], "question": "Non-resident military personnel stationed in California who are eligible for military extensions should present ____ to law enforcement.", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9693}
{"candidates": ["Motor homes or pickup trucks towing a boat trailer.", "Tank trucks marked with hazardous materials placards.", "Any vehicle with 3 or more axles or weighing more than 4,000 pounds."], "question": "Which of these vehicles must always stop before crossing railroad tracks?", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9700}
{"candidates": ["Not count on other drivers making room for you", "Assume they will let you pass if you use your turn signal", "Assume they will maintain a constant speed"], "question": "When planning to pass an other vehicle, you should", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9702}
{"candidates": ["Only when a crosswalk is painted on the street", "Only at controlled intersections", "Whether or not a crosswalk is marked"], "question": "Pedestrians crossing at corners have the right-of-way:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9703}
{"candidates": ["When making a call while stopped at the red light", "Never", "When making a call for emergency assistance"], "question": "When is it legal to use a cell phone without a hands-free device while driving", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9704}
{"candidates": ["25mph", "20mph", "15mph"], "question": "The speed limit in any alley is", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9706}
{"candidates": ["The lane closest to the left curb", "Any lane as long as it seems safe to do so", "The center lane"], "question": "To left from a one-way street onto a one-way street, start from:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9707}
{"candidates": ["5 to 10 seconds", "15 to 20 seconds", "10 to 15 seconds"], "question": "To avoid last minute moves, you should be looking down the road to where your vehicle will be in about", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9730}
{"candidates": ["Only if you or the other driver is injured.", "Only if you are at fault.", "If there is property damage in excess of $750 or if there are any injuries."], "question": "If you are involved in a traffic collision, you are required to complete and submit a written report (SR1) to the DMV:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9731}
{"candidates": ["One of your rear wheels should touch the curb", "Your front wheels should be parallel to the road if there is no curb", "Use your parking break and leave the vehicle in gear or \"park\""], "question": "When parking your vehicle on any hill:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9733}
{"candidates": ["Merge into another lane", "Changing lanes frequently", "Decreasing your following distance"], "question": "Which of the following will help you avoid being hit from behind", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9734}
{"candidates": ["Maintain traction by following other vehicles closely", "Shift to a low gear before going down steep hills", "Pump your brakes to keep them from freezing"], "question": "When driving on a slippery surface such as snow or ice:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9735}
{"candidates": ["When the warning lights are not flashing", "When you can see clearly in both directions", "Under no circumstances"], "question": "When may you legally go around or under a rail road crossing gate:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9736}
{"candidates": ["As a regular driving lane during periods of heavy traffic", "To begin or end left turns or start a permitted U-Turn", "To pass vehicles that are moving slowly"], "question": "The two-way road you are driving on has a lane marked as shown in the picture. This lane is used:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9738}
{"candidates": ["Tapping your horn before you back up", "Checking your vehicle before you get in", "Looking over your right shoulder as you back up"], "question": "Safely backing your vehicle includes all of the following except:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9739}
{"candidates": ["Five feet longer", "Two feet longer", "Ten feet longer"], "question": "When you are trying to parallel park, you should first look for a space that is at least ____ longer than your car.", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9749}
{"candidates": ["Not restricted by law", "Legal, if it is your child", "Illegal at all times"], "question": "Smoking inside a vehicle when a person younger than 18 years of age is present", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9759}
{"candidates": ["Loading zone for freight only.", "Loading zone for passengers or mail only.", "Loading zone for freight or passengers."], "question": "A white painted curb means:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9761}
{"candidates": ["Leave a note on the vehicle.", "Report the accident without delay to the city police or, in unincorporated areas, to the CHP.", "All the others."], "question": "You have been involved in a minor traffic collision with a parked vehicle and you can't find the owner. You must:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9762}
{"candidates": ["Motorcycle", "Passenger vehicle", "Station wagon"], "question": "Allow extra space in front of your vehicle when following a:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9764}
{"candidates": ["Legal only at intersections, unless a sign prohibits them", "Always illegal because they are dangerous", "Legal whenever oncoming vehicles are not a hazard"], "question": "U-turns in business districts are:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9767}
{"candidates": ["Avoid the puddle if possible", "Shift into neutral as you drive through the water", "Maintain the posted speed to make it through the water"], "question": "If there is a deep puddle in the road ahead, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9769}
{"candidates": ["Away", "To", "Towards"], "question": "When there is no curb and you are parking uphill, turn the wheels so that the vehicle will roll ____ from the center of the road if the brakes fail.", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9784}
{"candidates": ["All the others", "Name change documents containing your legal name both before and after", "A marriage certificate"], "question": "Which of the following are acceptable examples of true full name verification documents, for the purposes of obtaining a driver license?", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9785}
{"candidates": ["Right. Towards the side of the road.", "So they face straight ahead", "Left. Towards the center of the road"], "question": "You want to park downhill on a two-way road and there is no curb. Which way do you turn your front wheels?", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9790}
{"candidates": ["Roadways on bridges and overpasses", "Roadways paved with asphalt", "Roadways near the top of hills"], "question": "On freezing wet days, which of the following roadways is most likely to hide spots of ice", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9792}
{"candidates": ["You can't get all the way across before the light turns red", "The light is yellow and you can stop safely", "The light is flashing yellow and you didn't stop first"], "question": "It is against the law to enter an intersection when", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9793}
{"candidates": ["So other drivers can see you", "On the high beam setting", "Only when driving on the freeway"], "question": "Turn on your windshield wipers and use your headlights on rainy, snowy or foggy days:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9794}
{"candidates": ["When pulling next to, but not away from the curb", "Only when pulling away from the curb", "When pulling next to or away from the curb"], "question": "When parking next to a curb, you should use your turn signals", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9819}
{"candidates": ["Should only merge into the bicycle lane if you stop before turning", "Must merge into the bicycle lane before making your turn", "You may not enter the bicycle lane to make your turn"], "question": "Your driving lane is next to a bicycle lane. You want to make a right turn at the incoming intersection. You:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9824}
{"candidates": ["Oncoming vehicles also turning left", "All approaching vehicles", "Pedestrians on the sidewalk waiting for a \"WALK\" signal"], "question": "You want to turn left in an upcoming corner. Give the right of way to:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9825}
{"candidates": ["Change lanes to the left and speed up", "Stop your vehicle until you can see what has happened", "Slow down and pass very carefully"], "question": "There is a vehicle stopped on the right shoulder of the road with its hazard lights on. You should:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9826}
{"candidates": ["Slow down and let the vehicle pass", "Honk your horn then pass the bicyclist", "Wait until the bicyclist rides off the roadway"], "question": "If you want to pass a bicyclist in a narrow traffic lane when an oncoming vehicle is approaching", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9827}
{"candidates": ["Plan on being out of the state for more than 30 days", "Refinance the remaining balance of your vehicle loan", "Are in a collision that caused more than $1000 in damage to property"], "question": "You must file a report of traffic accident occurring in California with DMV within 10 days if you", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9828}
{"candidates": ["Often, even at controlled intersections", "When it helps prevent collisions", "Never it confuses other drivers"], "question": "When should you yield your legal right-of-way", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9833}
{"candidates": ["Do not \u201ccut off\u201d other drivers.", "All the others.", "Do not tailgate."], "question": "Which of the options help one avoid aggressive driving and road rage situations?", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9844}
{"candidates": ["25 mph", "30 mph", "20 mph"], "question": "Unless otherwise posted the speed limit in a residential area is", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9849}
{"candidates": ["They do not freeze because they are made of concrete", "They tend to freeze before the end of the road does", "They tend to freeze before the rest of the road does"], "question": "Which of the following is true about roadways on bridges and overpasses in cold, wet weather?", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9852}
{"candidates": ["At the legal freeway speed limit", "At or near the same speed as the freeway traffic", "Slower than the freeway traffic"], "question": "When merging onto the freeway, you should be driving:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9853}
{"candidates": ["Wait until you have entered the curve to begin braking", "Slow to a safe speed before the curve", "Slow to the posted speed limit for the freeway"], "question": "You exit a freeway on a ramp that curves downhill. You should:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9855}
{"candidates": ["For picking up or dropping off passengers", "Allowed for no longer than 15 minutes", "For disabled persons with a special placard or plate"], "question": "A curb painted blue means parking is", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9856}
{"candidates": ["Lets other drivers know what your intentions are", "Is illegal to turn off your signal before completing a turn", "Is always unsafe to turn off a signal before completing a turn"], "question": "You should signal continuously while turning because it", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9857}
{"candidates": ["All carpool lanes from regular traffic lanes", "Traffic moving in opposite directions on a two-way road", "Traffic lanes on one-way streets"], "question": "Yellow lines separate:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9858}
{"candidates": ["Slow down before entering curves and intersections", "Speed up to enter curves and slow down to exit them", "Shift to a lower gear after starting down a steep hill"], "question": "To help avoid skidding on slippery surfaces you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9859}
{"candidates": ["20mph", "25mph", "15mph"], "question": "At an uncontrolled intersection where you can't see cross traffic until you are just about to enter the intersection, the speed limit is:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9860}
{"candidates": ["The lane nearest the curb or edge of the roadway", "The lane closest to the center of the road", "Either lane, depending on oncoming traffic"], "question": "When making a right turn from a highway with two lanes in your direction, you may turn from:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9881}
{"candidates": ["Assume there is enough space for your vehicle, if you signal first", "Signal for at least five seconds", "Slow down before you start to change lanes"], "question": "When changing lanes on a freeway, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9884}
{"candidates": ["Drive at a constant speed to gain better traction", "Slow down gradually and not apply the brakes", "Apply the brakes firmly to prevent your vehicle from sliding"], "question": "If your vehicle starts to lose traction because of water on the road (hydroplaning) you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9887}
{"candidates": ["If a single person sustains more than $750 in damage, or if anyone is injured or dies.", "All the others.", "If you or another party are involved in a collision."], "question": "The DMV retains information for your permanent record on every collision reported to the DMV in what cases?", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9901}
{"candidates": ["You are approaching from behind.", "Approaching you from behind.", "You have already passed."], "question": "Dim your headlights for oncoming vehicles or when you are within 300 feet of a vehicle:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9906}
{"candidates": ["Speed up to cross the intersection before the light turns red", "Stop before entering the intersection if you can so safely", "Slow down and proceed through the intersection without caution"], "question": "You are approaching an intersection at the posted speed limit when signal turns yellow. You should", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9915}
{"candidates": ["Are backing out of a parking space", "Are temporarily parked in a traffic lane to make delivery", "Need to warn other drivers of a collision ahead"], "question": "Flash your brake lights or turn on your emergency flashers if you", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9917}
{"candidates": ["Change lanes, drive slowly and pass cautiously", "Stop until all the children have left the bus", "Stop until the lights stop flashing"], "question": "When a school bus with its red lights flashing is stopped ahead on your side of the road you must", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9918}
{"candidates": ["Listening to music through a set of dual headphones", "Reading a road map", "Adjusting your outside mirrors"], "question": "While all the following are dangerous to do while driving, which is also illegal", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9935}
{"candidates": ["Only if you have been drinking alcohol.", "Whenever you drive in California.", "Only if you have a collision."], "question": "You consent to take a chemical test for the alcohol content of your blood, breath, or urine:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9937}
{"candidates": ["Only when a bus or trolley is present", "At any time for any reason", "Only when a bus or trolley is unloading passengers"], "question": "A safety zone is a specially marked area for passengers to get on or off the buses or trolleys. You may not drive through a safety zone:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9942}
{"candidates": ["Parked on a hill or sloping driveway", "Waiting to make a left turn at a traffic light", "Parked on the side of a level roadway and there is no curb"], "question": "Your wheels should be pointed straight ahead, unless you are:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9946}
{"candidates": ["At most DMV field offices that provide DL services", "At one specific office near your home", "Only after making an appointment"], "question": "You may take the knowledge, vision and behind-the-wheel driving test ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9961}
{"candidates": ["You cannot turn on a red arrow, even if you stop first", "Red arrows are only used to stop traffic which is turning left", "Red arrows are only used for protected turn lanes"], "question": "What is the difference between traffic lights with red arrows and those with solid red lights", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9971}
{"candidates": ["25mph", "15mph", "20mph"], "question": "The speed limit at an uncontrolled railroad crossing is:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9973}
{"candidates": ["One-way street onto a one way street", "One-way street onto a two-way street", "Two-way street onto a one-way street"], "question": "You may make a left turn on a red light only from a:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9976}
{"candidates": ["Assume the other driver will maintain a constant speed.", "Assume the other driver will let you pass if you use your turn signal.", "Not assume the other driver will make space for you to return to your lane."], "question": "California residents who drive on public highways or use public parking facilities must have a California driver license, unless ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9990}
{"candidates": ["When a driver turns on red", "All the others", "In marked crosswalks"], "question": "When do pedestrians have the right of way in crosswalks?", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9991}
{"candidates": ["15 mph", "30 mph", "25 mph"], "question": "The speed limit for a blind intersection is what?", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 9993}
{"candidates": ["Intersections", "Tunnels", "Bridges and over-passes"], "question": "Which of the following roadways freezes first when wet", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10000}
{"candidates": ["Maintain your speed but watch for other vehicles", "Slow down an cross carefully", "Stop before crossing the intersection"], "question": "What should you do at an intersection with a flashing yellow signal light:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10005}
{"candidates": ["Up to twelve months in jail", "Up to six months in jail", "No jail time but you must pay a fine of $500"], "question": "If you are convicted of driving with an excessive blood alcohol concentration(BAC), you may be sentenced to serve:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10006}
{"candidates": ["Stop, then proceed when you think all of the children have exited the bus.", "Slow to 25 MPH and pass cautiously.", "Stop as long as the red lights are flashing."], "question": "A school bus ahead of you in your lane is stopped with red lights flashing. You should:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10027}
{"candidates": ["Stop first. Then do what the officer tells you", "Wait for the green light", "Do as the officer tells you"], "question": "A police officer is signaling you to continue driving through a red light, What should you do?", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10032}
{"candidates": ["They are not allowed to drive on freeways", "They must stop before crossing railroad tracks", "They are not allowed to exceed 35mph"], "question": "Which is true about vehicles displaying a diamond-shaped sign (indicating a hazardous load)?", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10033}
{"candidates": ["Signal before you arrive at the intersection", "Turn your front wheels to the left to be prepared to turn", "Move to the left of the center lane"], "question": "You enter a designated turn lane to make a left turn at an upcoming intersection. There is oncoming traffic. You should:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10034}
{"candidates": ["They are properly secured", "The tailgate of the truck is closed", "The sides of the truck bed are at least 18 inches high"], "question": "Animals may be transported in the back of a pickup truck only if", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10036}
{"candidates": ["Having one more interior lights on", "Wearing a headset that covers both ears", "Using cruise control on residential streets"], "question": "All of the following are dangerous while driving,. Which is also illegal:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10038}
{"candidates": ["10 days", "3 days", "5 days"], "question": "If you sell a vehicle, you must report it to the DMV within ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10050}
{"candidates": ["Buyers", "Dealers and lessor-retailers", "Local DMV offices"], "question": "When you purchase a vehicle from a licensed dealer in California, who collects the registration fees?", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10053}
{"candidates": ["Require to use both the lap and shoulder belt", "Only require to use the lap belt", "Only required to use the shoulder belt"], "question": "If you are riding in a vehicle equipped with a lap belt and also a separate shoulder belt, you are", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10054}
{"candidates": ["Check the incoming number before answering the call", "Let the call go to voicemail", "Answer the call because it may be an emergency"], "question": "If your cell phone rings while you are driving and you do not have a hands-free device you should", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10055}
{"candidates": ["Under the front seat", "In the trunk", "In the glove department"], "question": "It is legal to drive with an alcoholic container that has been opened if the container is:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10060}
{"candidates": ["Unless you are driving in a limousine", "Unless you are riding in a vehicle built before 1978", "And fail to do so will result in a traffic ticket"], "question": "You must use your seatbelt", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10062}
{"candidates": ["Backing, changing lanes or slowing down quickly", "Backing, making a sharp turn or crossing an intersection", "Changing lanes, crossing intersections or slowing down quickly"], "question": "Three of the most important times to check traffic behind you are before", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10064}
{"candidates": ["If the vehicle ahead is turning left", "If there are two or more lanes traveling in your direction", "Under no circumstances."], "question": "You can drive off the road to pass another vehicle", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10066}
{"candidates": ["Because it helps you keep up with traffic", "Because it takes 1/4 mile to stop your vehicle completely", "In order to see potential hazards early"], "question": "On a freeway, you should look farther ahead than you would on a city street:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10067}
{"candidates": ["1 year", "2 months", "30 days"], "question": "If you are out of California on active military duty and you have a valid California driver license, your license remains valid for the time you are outside of the state and ____ after your honorable discharge.", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10076}
{"candidates": ["It is safest to drive in the lane next to the center line", "You should drive ahead or behind the other vehicles", "Drive along side the other vehicles so the drivers can see you"], "question": "When driving on a multilane street with two way traffic:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10085}
{"candidates": ["Left towards the center of the road", "Right towards the side of the road", "So they face straight ahead"], "question": "You want to park uphill on a two-way road and there is no curb. Which way do you turn your front wheels?", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10086}
{"candidates": ["You must \"Slow for the Cone Zone\"", "Fines are the same for violations committed in work zones", "Slow down only if you think workers are present"], "question": "Which of these statements is true about road work zones", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10091}
{"candidates": ["A seven-year old who is 4 feet 7 inches tall", "An eight year old who is 4 feet 9 inches tall", "A six-year old who is 4 feet 10 inches tall"], "question": "Which child requires a child passenger restraint system?", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10092}
{"candidates": ["You must not squeeze past the bicyclist", "May not pass the bicyclist for any reason", "You must honk your horn before passing the bicyclist"], "question": "You want to pass a bicyclists riding on the right edge of your lane", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10093}
{"candidates": ["May complete its turn in either of the two lanes.", "Must stay in the right lane at all times while turning.", "Often have to use of the left lane to complete the turn"], "question": "Large trucks turning onto a street with two lanes in each direction:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10094}
{"candidates": ["Only if the key is in the ignition", "If they are supervised by a person twelve years of age or older", "Even if they are secured in a child passenger restraint system"], "question": "It is illegal to leave children age six or younger unattended in vehicle on a hot day:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10095}
{"candidates": ["Your vehicle fails a smog test", "You are involved in a collision and there is an injury", "You change your insurance company"], "question": "You must file a report of traffic accident occurring in California with the DMV when", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10098}
{"candidates": ["You have the right-of-way", "Whoever if signaling to make a turn has the right-of-way", "The driver on your left has the right-of-way"], "question": "You reach an intersection with stop signs on all four corners at the same time as the driver on your left. Who has the right of way:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10117}
{"candidates": ["The maximum speed limit in California is 70 mph on certain freeways.", "You should never drive faster than is safe for current conditions.", "You should never drive faster than posted speed limits."], "question": "California's \"Basic Speed Law\" says:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10121}
{"candidates": ["You transport two or more young children in a passenger vehicle.", "You don't have room on the other side to completely cross the tracks.", "The railroad crossing is located in a city or town that has frequent train traffic."], "question": "Always stop before you cross railroad tracks when:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10122}
{"candidates": ["Only if you are stopped and cited", "Only if you are involved in a collision", "If you are involved in a collision or stopped for a citation"], "question": "You must show proof of insurance to law enforcement:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10124}
{"candidates": ["Looking over your shoulder while making lane changes", "Adjusting your rearview mirror before you start driving", "Continuously changing lanes to pass other vehicles"], "question": "Which of the following increases your chances of having a collision?", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10125}
{"candidates": ["If the vehicle ahead of you is turning left.", "If the shoulder is wide enough to accommodate your vehicle", "Under no circumstances"], "question": "You may drive off of the paved roadway to pass another vehicle:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10144}
{"candidates": ["They usually have the right of way at intersections", "It is illegal for motorcycles to share traffic lanes", "Their smaller size makes them harder to see"], "question": "Always look carefully for motorcycles before you change lanes because:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10149}
{"candidates": ["Drive on the shoulder until a gap in traffic appears", "Slowly inch your vehicle into the traffic lane", "Continue waiting and yielding traffic in the lane"], "question": "You were parked and have been waiting a long time with your turn signal on to re-enter traffic. However traffic is heavy. You should:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10150}
{"candidates": ["Unless you entered the intersection on a yellow light", "Under any circumstances", "Unless you entered the intersection on a green light"], "question": "You should not start across an intersection if you know you will block the intersection when the light turns red", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10151}
{"candidates": ["Unless they conflict with existing signs, signals, or laws.", "Only if you see orange cones on the road ahead.", "At all times."], "question": "In which of the following situations should you not use your horn?", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10169}
{"candidates": ["Never look over your right shoulder", "Glance over your shoulder", "Always slow down in your traffic lane"], "question": "Before you change lanes, you should check your mirrors and:", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10179}
{"candidates": ["Wait for the owner to return", "Call your insurance company when you get home", "Leave a note with your name and address on the parked vehicle"], "question": "You hit a parked vehicle and can't find the owner. What must you do?", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10180}
{"candidates": ["A middle course between the oncoming and parked vehicles", "Closer to the oncoming vehicles than the parked vehicles", "Closer to the parked vehicles than the oncoming vehicles"], "question": "You are driving and there are oncoming vehicles on your left and a row of parked vehicles on your right. You should steer:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10183}
{"candidates": ["Are being tailgated by another driver", "Follow a small passenger vehicle", "Drive slower than the posted speed limit"], "question": "You should increase the distance between your vehicle and the vehicle ahead when you:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "permit", "id": 10185}
{"candidates": ["Under the seat", "In the motorcyclist\u2019s pocket", "On the windshield of the motorcycle"], "question": "Where can a motorcyclist NOT place a toll road transponder?", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10220}
{"candidates": ["The pavement is slippery", "The sun is shining", "You believe stopping will be routine"], "question": "The normal following distance should be extended if:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10236}
{"candidates": ["Nothing. Most bikes are similar, so you don\u2019t have to take time to identify items such as brakes.", "Learn the gear pattern by working the throttle, clutch and brakes. Each bike is a little different.", "Just start riding. There is no better way to learn than by doing."], "question": "Before riding an unfamiliar motorcycle, what should the rider do?", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10240}
{"candidates": ["drive really slow", "ride the center line", "allow an adequate space cushion"], "question": "To reduce the chance of a collision a motorcycle driver should", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10268}
{"candidates": ["only on weekends", "only if they have a passenger", "unless otherwise posted"], "question": "Carpool/HOV lanes can be used by motorcycle drivers", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10271}
{"candidates": ["Adjusting your outside mirrors.", "Listening to music through headphones that cover both ears", "Transporting an unrestrained animal inside the vehicle."], "question": "What is a good method to make sure that a group of motorcyclists ride together?", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10286}
{"candidates": ["U.S. DOT compliant", "a dark color so it doesn't create a glare.", "free of stickers or other artwork"], "question": "By law, motorcycle helmets must be", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10307}
{"candidates": ["Any lane (as long as it is safe)", "The lane in the center of the road.", "The lane closest to the left curb"], "question": "Where should beginners ride when they are part of a group of riders?", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10315}
{"candidates": ["the moped cannot be used on the freeway", "the moped can only be used when there is not stopped traffic on the freeway", "the moped can be used if it is not driven faster than 25 mph"], "question": "If a sign prohibits the use of a moped on a freeway, ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10354}
{"candidates": ["Should only merge into the bicycle lane if you stop before turning.", "May not enter the bicycle lane.", "Must merge into the bicycle lane before turning."], "question": "When a vehicle is tailgating you, what is the appropriate course of action?", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10374}
{"candidates": ["Local law enforcement personnel", "Property owners adjacent to the path.", "Permission cannot be granted"], "question": "Who can grant access to ride a moped on a bike path?", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10393}
{"candidates": ["Increased", "Decreased", "The same as a motorcycle without a trailer"], "question": "If a motorcyclist is towing a trailer, the following distance between the motorcycle and other vehicles should be:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10430}
{"candidates": ["Approaching you from behind.", "You have already passed.", "You are approaching from behind."], "question": "If you are riding with a passenger, you must instruct them to do all of the following, except ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10439}
{"candidates": ["Never. Motorized bicycles may never use a bicycle lane.", "Only when authorized by local authority or ordinance.", "Only when carrying a passenger."], "question": "When can a motorized bicycle, or moped, be operated in a bicycle lane?", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10453}
{"candidates": ["can travel in any lane on a highway", "must not travel faster than 45 mph", "are not allowed in carpool lanes"], "question": "Motorcycles pulling trailers ____ .", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10458}
{"candidates": ["3", "2", "4"], "question": "A motorcycle can have no more than ____ wheels.", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10459}
{"candidates": ["Between 65 mph and 70 mph.", "No faster than 65 mph.", "70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic."], "question": "Which of the following should you do when tire goes flat while riding?", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10468}
{"candidates": ["5 seconds", "10 seconds", "2 seconds"], "question": "At highway speeds how much time should a motorcycle driver allow between signaling and changing lanes?", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10473}
{"candidates": ["Should not drive your motorcycle", "Should drive your motorcycle if you believe you are not impaired", "Should drive your motorcycle only short distances"], "question": "If you have been drinking alcohol, you:", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10486}
{"candidates": ["All vehicles are traveling about the same speed.", "One vehicle is traveling faster or slower than the flow of traffic.", "One lane of traffic is traveling faster than the other lanes."], "question": "What is a common flying object that hits motorcyclists while they are riding?", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10495}
{"candidates": ["Must contact the highway department", "Only needs to file a report if planning to report the accident to their insurance company", "Must submit a report of the accident to the DMV"], "question": "Effective Jan. 1, 2017, the driver of a motor vehicle involved in a collision with property damages more than $1,000 ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10505}
{"candidates": ["Only if you or the other driver is injured.", "Only if you are at fault.", "If there is property damage in excess of $750 or if there are any injuries."], "question": "The \"Evaluate\" step of the SEE strategy suggests you should ____ while you are riding.", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10530}
{"candidates": ["35", "30", "25"], "question": "A motorized bicycle, or moped, cannot go faster than ____ mph.", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10542}
{"candidates": ["Other drivers when they want to slow down.", "The truck driver to stop the vehicle.", "Other drivers when merging onto a freeway."], "question": "What is the proper way to park a motorcycle at the curb?", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10551}
{"candidates": ["A speed which matches the flow of traffic.", "The posted speed limit.", "A speed just below the posted speed limit."], "question": "What is one thing you should do before riding an unfamiliar motorcycle?", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10556}
{"candidates": ["Look to the sides of your vehicle to see what is coming.", "Stop, listen, and proceed cautiously.", "Slowly pass vehicles that seem to be stopped for no reason."], "question": "Which of the following is an effective way to ensure a smooth and enjoyable motorcycle ride?", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10557}
{"candidates": ["Yield to any vehicle, bicycle, or pedestrian in the intersection.", "Wait four seconds before proceeding.", "Yield to pedestrians only in the intersection."], "question": "At times it is impossible to avoid an obstacle such as a pothole, bump, etc. At what degree of an angle should you approach the obstacle with?", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10559}
{"candidates": ["Windshield wipers", "Brakes", "Kill switch"], "question": "Of the following, which item would you NOT be asked to identify in a pre-trip inspection when taking the motorcycle skills test?", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10584}
{"candidates": ["5", "15", "10"], "question": "Which helmet offers the best coverage and protection to all of the head?", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10591}
{"candidates": ["Face or eye protection", "A ball cap", "Sneakers"], "question": "You have a better chance of avoiding serious injury if you wear :", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10593}
{"candidates": ["100 feet", "50 feet", "150 feet"], "question": "How far in advance should a motorcycle driver signal a turn?", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10598}
{"candidates": ["When others won\u2019t expect you to brake, such as in the middle of a block", "To alert motorists that you are driving near them", "When you are in slowed traffic."], "question": "Flashing your brake light helps other motorists see a motorcycle. What would be an example of flashing the brake lights to help other drivers see you?", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10602}
{"candidates": ["Class M2", "Class M1", "Class C"], "question": "To operate a moped you must have at least a ____ license.", "answer": 0, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10605}
{"candidates": ["Get a new prescription for lenses or contacts.", "Sell or transfer your vehicle.", "Fail a smog test for your vehicle."], "question": "Which of the following is a new law effective September 2014?", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10617}
{"candidates": ["0.1", "0.08", "0.01"], "question": "In California, it is illegal for a person under the age of 21 to drive a vehicle with a blood alcohol content of (BAC) ____", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10625}
{"candidates": ["Move toward the left side of your lane.", "Signal for 100 feet before turning.", "Avoid driving in the bicycle lane."], "question": "When riding on the highway at highway speeds, how early should you put your turn signal on to signify that you are going to change lanes?", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10649}
{"candidates": ["The rear brake should be applied first", "The front brake should be applied first", "Both front and rear brakes should be applied at the same time"], "question": "When braking with a motorcycle:", "answer": 2, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10654}
{"candidates": ["Secured as high as possible", "Secured as low as possible", "Attached to a sissy bar"], "question": "If traveling with a load, the load should be", "answer": 1, "state": "ca", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 10667}
{"candidates": ["40 mph", "30 mph", "20 mph"], "question": "What is the speed limit when traveling on an open mountain highway?", "answer": 0, "state": "co", "type": "permit", "id": 12109}
{"candidates": ["yellow, red, and green", "green, yellow, and red", "red, yellow and green"], "question": "Traffic lights are usually what colors, from top to bottom?", "answer": 2, "state": "co", "type": "permit", "id": 12139}
{"candidates": ["When approaching the curve", "When entering the curve", "After the midway point of the curve"], "question": "When approaching a curve in the road, when is it safe to accelerate?", "answer": 2, "state": "co", "type": "permit", "id": 12226}
{"candidates": ["Steer away", "Stop", "All the others"], "question": "When facing a collision, which of the following are options a driver has?", "answer": 1, "state": "co", "type": "permit", "id": 12284}
{"candidates": ["Only the passenger in the passenger seat.", "All passengers and the driver.", "Only the driver."], "question": "Who is required to wear a safety belt?", "answer": 1, "state": "co", "type": "permit", "id": 12285}
{"candidates": ["3 months", "6 months", "12 months"], "question": "How long must a minor have his or her instruction permit for?", "answer": 2, "state": "co", "type": "permit", "id": 12310}
{"candidates": ["Remain calm and do not slam on the brakes.", "Grip the steering wheel with both hands firmly.", "Speed up and pull off the road as soon as possible."], "question": "If your tire ever blows out, what is the wrong thing to do?", "answer": 1, "state": "co", "type": "permit", "id": 12311}
{"candidates": ["Assume the other driver will maintain a constant speed.", "Assume the other driver will let you pass if you use your turn signal.", "Not assume the other driver will make space for you to return to your lane."], "question": "You should always do what before reaching a curve in the road?", "answer": 2, "state": "co", "type": "permit", "id": 12431}
{"candidates": ["A speed just below the posted speed limit.", "A speed which matches the flow of traffic.", "The posted speed limit."], "question": "If your right wheels run off the edge of the pavement, ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "co", "type": "permit", "id": 12462}
{"candidates": ["1,000 feet", "2,000 feet", "1,500 feet"], "question": "Whether day or not, Colorado law requires headlights to be on when visibility is less than ____ feet", "answer": 0, "state": "co", "type": "permit", "id": 12463}
{"candidates": ["18 years old", "20 years old", "16 years old"], "question": "Under Colorado law, it is prohibited for drivers under what age to use a cell or mobile phone while driving unless it is an emergency?", "answer": 0, "state": "co", "type": "permit", "id": 12491}
{"candidates": ["Turning 21", "Turning 22", "Turning 25"], "question": "Minor licenses cannot be renewed before when?", "answer": 0, "state": "co", "type": "permit", "id": 12521}
{"candidates": ["Slow down or stop, if necessary, and then make the turn.", "Signal and turn immediately.", "Stop before entering the right lane and let all other traffic go first."], "question": "____ of reported motorcycle accidents involve riders with ____ of experience.", "answer": 0, "state": "co", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 12699}
{"candidates": ["Parallel with the pavement.", "Turned to the left (toward the street).", "Turned to the right (away from the street)."], "question": "Which of the following items doesn't have to do with keeping distance to the side?", "answer": 2, "state": "co", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 12700}
{"candidates": ["May be crossed to enter or exit a private driveway.", "May not be crossed for any reason.", "Should be treated as a separate traffic lane."], "question": "When signaling to other drivers that you are getting off of the road, which of the following is not an action you must complete?", "answer": 1, "state": "co", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 12726}
{"candidates": ["Be prepared for workers and equipment ahead.", "Slow down because the lane ends ahead.", "Change lanes and maintain your current speed."], "question": "In an emergency situation, you should ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "co", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 12728}
{"candidates": ["Have passed the other vehicle\u2019s front bumper.", "See the vehicle\u2019s headlights in your rear view mirror.", "Cannot see the vehicle directly to your right."], "question": "What does \"engine seizure\" mean?", "answer": 1, "state": "co", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 12788}
{"candidates": ["Transporting an unrestrained animal inside the vehicle.", "Adjusting your outside mirrors.", "Listening to music through headphones that cover both ears"], "question": "Which of the following items is not recommended you do when traveling with a passenger on your motorcycle?", "answer": 2, "state": "co", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 12789}
{"candidates": ["Change lanes and maintain your current speed.", "Slow down because the lane ends ahead.", "Be prepared for workers and equipment ahead."], "question": "What is a common cause of a \"wobble\"?", "answer": 2, "state": "co", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 12790}
{"candidates": ["You do not have room on the other side to completely cross the tracks.", "The railroad crossing is located in a city or town that has frequent train traffic.", "You transport two or more young children in a passenger vehicle."], "question": "Engine seizure is another way of describing when an engine locks or freezes. This is usually caused by what?", "answer": 0, "state": "co", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 12851}
{"candidates": ["Within the distance lighted by your parking lights.", "Within 5-10 seconds.", "Within the distance you can see ahead."], "question": "What's the first thing you should try if your throttle gets stuck while you are riding?", "answer": 2, "state": "co", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 12877}
{"candidates": ["A sign permits the turn.", "Traffic on the street moves to the left.", "Traffic on the street moves to the right."], "question": "What can shifting suddenly cause?", "answer": 1, "state": "co", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 12880}
{"candidates": ["It is OK for small children to ride in the front passenger seat of your car.", "Small children should ride in the back seat.", "Use the rear-facing child restraint system in the front passenger seat."], "question": "In a motorcycle group who should set the pace?", "answer": 1, "state": "co", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 12881}
{"candidates": ["After it has been raining for awhile.", "During a heavy downpour.", "The first rain after a dry spell."], "question": "When traveling in a group what is the recommended limit for a group size before you should break into smaller groups?", "answer": 2, "state": "co", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 12940}
{"candidates": ["Both of the above.", "Report the accident without delay to the city police or, in unincorporated areas, to the CHP.", "Leave a note on the vehicle."], "question": "Which of the following is NOT a step a motorcyclist should follow when attempting get off the road?", "answer": 0, "state": "co", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 12998}
{"candidates": ["Look to the sides of your vehicle to see what is coming.", "Stop, listen, and proceed cautiously.", "Slowly pass vehicles that seem to be stopped for no reason."], "question": "To completely stop a motorcycle safely you should always roll off the throttle, apply the brakes, and ____?", "answer": 0, "state": "co", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 13032}
{"candidates": ["In an unmarked crosswalk", "In a bicycle lane.", "Within three feet of a private driveway."], "question": "Which of the following items is not a suggested tip when trying to keep your group together while riding.", "answer": 0, "state": "co", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 13089}
{"candidates": ["Use hands-free devices so you can keep both hands on the steering wheel.", "Keep your phone within easy reach so you won't need to take your eyes off the road.", "Review the number before answering a call."], "question": "If you are swerving, you should brake ____ .", "answer": 0, "state": "co", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 13091}
{"candidates": ["Your younger brother", "Your parent(s)", "Your 18 year old friend"], "question": "After you have held a license for 6 months, which one of the following passengers cannot be in the vehicle when you are driving?", "answer": 2, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14512}
{"candidates": ["10 feet", "15 feet", "5 feet"], "question": "You may not park within how many feet of a fire hydrant?", "answer": 0, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14526}
{"candidates": ["Speed up to provide more room for the vehicle behind to pass", "Turn right from any lane", "Turn from the right lane"], "question": "To make a right turn, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14528}
{"candidates": ["They prevent a \"human collision\" by holding you in place", "They are not necessary if your vehicle has an air bag", "They keep you from being thrown from the vehicle in the event of an accident"], "question": "The following statements regarding the use of seat belts are true with the exception of", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14529}
{"candidates": ["Your ability to judge speed and control will be impaired", "Your tires will start to glide over the water", "Your own spray will obscure the vision of other drivers"], "question": "If you drive too fast on a wet road, there is danger that:", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14532}
{"candidates": ["The out-of-state license which the driver possesses has not expired for more than 2 years.", "The out-of-state license which the driver possesses has not expired for more than 3 years.", "The out-of-state license which the driver possesses has not expired for more than 4 years."], "question": "Which of the following are requirements for new residents who have a valid license in another state but must get a Connecticut driver's license?", "answer": 0, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14551}
{"candidates": ["Until their 18th birthday", "When their parents are in the car", "When they have their seat belt fastened"], "question": "When can drivers ages 16 or 17 use a cell phone while driving?", "answer": 0, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14552}
{"candidates": ["2-3 seconds", "3-4 seconds", "1-2 seconds"], "question": "If you see a distracted driver, you should give that distracted driver plenty of room and maintain a safe following distance of:", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14555}
{"candidates": ["Under 1 year of age weighing 20 pounds or less", "weighing 25 pounds or less", "1 year of age weighing 30 pounds or less"], "question": "An approved rear-facing child restraint system is required for any child:", "answer": 0, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14565}
{"candidates": ["When you are passing a driver who starts to turn in your lane.", "Greeting a friend.", "When a driver doesn't react quickly enough at a green light."], "question": "In which of the following situations is it NOT appropriate give a light tap on your horn?", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14575}
{"candidates": ["During rush hour traffic if there are no bicyclists in the bike lane.", "When you are within 200 feet of a cross street where you plan to turn right.", "When you want to pass a driver ahead of you who is turning right."], "question": "In the absence of lane markings or signs to control turning, what should you do?", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14581}
{"candidates": ["Sound your horn and maintain speed", "Slow down and pass with caution", "Speed up to clear the area quickly"], "question": "You see pedestrians near the road. You should:", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14586}
{"candidates": ["Release your seat belt", "Press your head against the head restraint", "Brace yourself"], "question": "If you are about to be hit from the rear, what should you NOT do?", "answer": 0, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14591}
{"candidates": ["Not sure.", "You have the right of way.", "Traffic already inside of it has the right of way."], "question": "When entering a roundabout or circular intersection, who has right of way, you or those already in the roundabout?", "answer": 2, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14607}
{"candidates": ["Pull over to the right and stop", "Slow down and keep moving", "Maintain your speed"], "question": "There's an emergency vehicle with flashing lights and siren coming. You should:", "answer": 0, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14614}
{"candidates": ["Unless they conflict with existing signs, signals, or laws.", "At all times.", "Only if you see orange cones on the road ahead."], "question": "Which of the following is not recommended when dealing with risks from others while on the road.", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14641}
{"candidates": ["Maintain speed and position", "Change lanes to the left", "Slow down"], "question": "To avoid merging traffic from the right, the best thing to do is:", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14646}
{"candidates": ["3 months", "6 months", "12 months"], "question": "Passenger restrictions apply to operator's license holders who have received their license on or after August 1, 2008 for what length of time?", "answer": 2, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14653}
{"candidates": ["Traffic patterns usually remain the same", "You do not need to obey traffic signs", "Traffic patterns can change daily"], "question": "When driving through a work zone", "answer": 2, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14655}
{"candidates": ["45 days", "30 days", "60 days"], "question": "If you are 16 or 17 years old and are convicted of speeding over 20 miles over the speed limit under the new law, your license will be suspended for:", "answer": 2, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14680}
{"candidates": ["6 months", "18 months", "9 months"], "question": "If you are 16 or 17 years old and arrested for a first time DUI offense and a police officers asks you to take a breath test and you refuse, your license will be suspended for:", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14686}
{"candidates": ["11pm to 5am", "10pm to 6am", "12am to 5am"], "question": "As of August1, 2008, what is the night time curfew for 16 and 17 year olds", "answer": 0, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14710}
{"candidates": ["Must share a traffic lane with another vehicle", "Have the right to use a complete traffic lane", "Are easy to see and determine what they will do"], "question": "Motorcycle/scooter/moped operators:", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14712}
{"candidates": ["You should drive 15mph faster than the posted speed limit", "You should obey the normal speed limit", "You should drive 15mph slower than the posted speed limit"], "question": "If there are no reduced speed limit signs clearly posted within a work zone:", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14735}
{"candidates": ["30", "60", "90"], "question": "Applicants over the age of 18 must hold a learner's permit for how many days before taking the road test?", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14760}
{"candidates": ["Are generally not enforced", "Can be double normal fines", "Can be argued in court"], "question": "Fines for speeding or other illegal behavior in work zones:", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14762}
{"candidates": ["21", "18", "16"], "question": "You must be at least ____ years old to obtain a commercial driver's license.", "answer": 0, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14787}
{"candidates": ["You are 50 feet ahead of the vehicle", "You can see both headlights of the vehicle in your rearview mirror", "You are one vehicle length ahead"], "question": "After passing, you should move back to the right when:", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14792}
{"candidates": ["3", "5", "4"], "question": "Your driver's license is valid for ____ years, expiring on your birthday.", "answer": 2, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14847}
{"candidates": ["You can't see far enough ahead to pass", "There are oncoming cars passing in your direction", "Passing is only permitted in daylight hours"], "question": "Signs or lane markings that indicate a No Passing Zone tell you that:", "answer": 0, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14852}
{"candidates": ["Use only the lap belt", "Use only the shoulder belt", "Use both the lap and shoulder belt"], "question": "If your vehicle has a two part safety belt system you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14853}
{"candidates": ["They brake more slowly than motor vehicles", "They do not follow the same rules as motor vehicles", "A motorcycle can stop much faster than a standard vehicle"], "question": "It is dangerous to follow a motorcycle too closely because:", "answer": 2, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14859}
{"candidates": ["32%", "22%", "12%"], "question": "What percentage of traffic accidents in which someone dies is alcohol involved in?", "answer": 0, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14880}
{"candidates": ["Increased traffic congestion on roads.", "All the others.", "A general decline in courtesy and civility."], "question": "Of the following, which are common reasons for aggressive driving?", "answer": 2, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14909}
{"candidates": ["1/2", "1/4", "1/3"], "question": "While driving on packed show you should reduce your speed by", "answer": 0, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14946}
{"candidates": ["15 feet", "10 feet", "25 feet"], "question": "You may not park within how many feet of a stop sign?", "answer": 2, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14947}
{"candidates": ["Pull off the road", "Maintain your speed and position", "Slow down and let then safely return to the drive lane"], "question": "While being passed in a no passing zone you should", "answer": 2, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14972}
{"candidates": ["Applying your brakes", "Letting go of the steering wheel", "Pressing your head firmly against the head restraint"], "question": "If you are about to be hit from the rear, you should consider each of the following with the exception of:", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14979}
{"candidates": ["Motorcycle", "Pickup trucks", "SUVs"], "question": "What types of vehicles CANNOT be operated with a class D license?", "answer": 0, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 14995}
{"candidates": ["Make the turn from the left lane", "Make the turn from the center lane", "Make the turn from any lane, providing you signal well in advance"], "question": "To make a left turn, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 15038}
{"candidates": ["Text-messaging device", "Cell phone", "Both cell phone and text messaging device"], "question": "Drivers who are 16 or 17 years of age are not permitted to use any type of", "answer": 2, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 15039}
{"candidates": ["Driver's license suspension", "All the others", "Possible jail time"], "question": "If you fail a blood, breath or urine test, what will happen?", "answer": 0, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 15087}
{"candidates": ["4 and 11", "9 and 3", "12 and 9"], "question": "Referring to the steering wheel as a clock face, the normal hand position for driving should be:", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 15094}
{"candidates": ["A 10 day suspension", "A 30 day suspension", "A $500 fine"], "question": "The penalty for 16/17 old driver convicted of violating the electronic device law will result:", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "permit", "id": 15095}
{"candidates": ["Merge into another lane and try to go around the traffic.", "Stay out of the intersection until traffic clears.", "Enter the intersection and wait until traffic clears."], "question": "You should wear a jacket even in warm weather to prevent what from happening?", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 15171}
{"candidates": ["Get you to your destination much faster and safer.", "Increase your chances of an accident.", "Help prevent traffic congestion."], "question": "Helmets with a label from what foundation give an assurance of quality?", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 15176}
{"candidates": ["Turned to the right (away from the street).", "Turned to the left (toward the street).", "Parallel with the pavement."], "question": "A motorcycle's brake light is not as noticeable as a full sized car's brake light, it is suggested you do what to help others notice your brake light while on the road?", "answer": 0, "state": "ct", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 15199}
{"candidates": ["Make sure the pedestrian sees you, but continue driving.", "Stop and let the pedestrian cross the street.", "Carefully drive around the pedestrian."], "question": "Which of the following items do you not need to do when carrying passengers or cargo on your motorcycle?", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 15235}
{"candidates": ["Review the number before answering a call.", "Use hands-free devices so you can keep both hands on the steering wheel.", "Keep your phone within easy reach so you won't need to take your eyes off the road."], "question": "What should you do if you are experiencing a stuck throttle?", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 15236}
{"candidates": ["Keep the instrument panel lights bright to be more visible to other\tdrivers.", "Drive slowly enough so you can stop within the area lighted by your headlights.", "Turn on your high beam headlights to better see the vehicles ahead of you."], "question": "On a motorcycle with a sidecar, which of the following can cause a skid?", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 15264}
{"candidates": ["If the vehicle ahead of you is turning left.", "Under no circumstances", "If the shoulder is wide enough to accommodate your vehicle"], "question": "Which of the following is a consequence of a conviction for alcohol or drugs?", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 15295}
{"candidates": ["Increase your chances of an accident.", "Get you to your destination much faster and safer.", "Help prevent traffic congestion."], "question": "Which of the following should your lane position not allow?", "answer": 0, "state": "ct", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 15322}
{"candidates": ["Assume the other driver will maintain a constant speed.", "Assume the other driver will let you pass if you use your turn signal.", "Not assume the other driver will make space for you to return to your lane."], "question": "What sort of people are immune or resistant to the effects of drugs or alcohol?", "answer": 2, "state": "ct", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 15379}
{"candidates": ["Stop and let him/her finish crossing the street.", "Slow down as you pass him/her.", "Make eye contact and then pass him/her."], "question": "In order to meet the specifications of a three-wheel vehicle, the turning diameter of a vehicle at its widest point must be what?", "answer": 0, "state": "ct", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 15385}
{"candidates": ["Next to the solid line may pass.", "Next to the broken line may pass.", "In both directions may pass."], "question": "What will occur if the front tire goes flat?", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 15386}
{"candidates": ["When you entered the intersection on the green light.", "Under no circumstances.", "During rush hour traffic."], "question": "What should a motorcyclist do if a dog approaches the motorcycle?", "answer": 1, "state": "ct", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 15417}
{"candidates": ["Stop and let him/her finish crossing the street.", "Make eye contact and then pass him/her.", "Slow down as you pass him/her."], "question": "In what year did new motorcycles sold in the USA start automatically turning on lights when running?", "answer": 0, "state": "ct", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 15439}
{"candidates": ["Within 5-10 seconds.", "Within the distance lighted by your parking lights.", "Within the distance you can see ahead."], "question": "An adult with a blood alcohol concentration (BAC) of what amount is considered intoxicated?", "answer": 2, "state": "ct", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 15476}
{"candidates": ["Look to the sides of your vehicle to see what is coming.", "Stop, listen, and proceed cautiously.", "Slowly pass vehicles that seem to be stopped for no reason."], "question": "What should you do when entering a curve?", "answer": 0, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17083}
{"candidates": ["Obey the traffic signal", "Obey the traffic officer", "Do what the vehicle in front of you does"], "question": "If a traffic signal light is green and a police officer signals you to stop, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17093}
{"candidates": ["Try to fight it", "Take a break", "Take some \u201cstay-awake\u201d drugs"], "question": "If you become drowsy while driving, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17097}
{"candidates": ["Negligence is accidental, while recklessness is intentional.", "Negligence is intentional, while recklessness is accidental.", "They are the same."], "question": "What is the difference between negligent driving and reckless driving?", "answer": 0, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17109}
{"candidates": ["Yield to pedestrians only in the intersection.", "Yield to any vehicle, bicycle, or pedestrian in the intersection.", "Wait four seconds before proceeding."], "question": "If your vehicle is disabled, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17287}
{"candidates": ["Stop light", "Light is about to turn green", "Stop sign"], "question": "A flashing red traffic light at an intersection means the same as a:", "answer": 2, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17299}
{"candidates": ["Within 20 days", "Within 5 days", "Within 10 days"], "question": "If you move, how long do you have to notify the DMV of your change of address?", "answer": 2, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17316}
{"candidates": ["10", "8", "12"], "question": "What is the minimum hours of night driving one must have to obtain a full driver's license?", "answer": 0, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17318}
{"candidates": ["The Judicial Branch", "The Executive Branch", "The Legislative Branch"], "question": "What part of federal government is the Selective Service System part of?", "answer": 1, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17349}
{"candidates": ["Males between the ages of 18-25", "Males between the ages of 20-25", "Males between the ages of 18-30"], "question": "Who is required to register with the Selective Service?", "answer": 0, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17437}
{"candidates": ["Traffic signals", "All of District of Columbia\u2019s traffic laws", "Lane markings"], "question": "If you choose to drive in the District of Columbia, you assume the responsibility and agree to obey ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17524}
{"candidates": ["Stop at the end of the ramp to wait for a gap", "Maintain speed and force other drivers to make a gap", "Slow down on the ramp to wait for a gap"], "question": "If you have to wait for a space to enter a freeway:", "answer": 2, "state": "dc", "type": "permit", "id": 17599}
{"candidates": ["No more than one car length behind the truck so the driver can see you.", "Closely behind the truck in bad weather because the driver can see farther ahead.", "Farther behind the truck than you would for a passenger vehicle."], "question": "Why is it a good idea to keep the group you are riding with small in size?", "answer": 2, "state": "dc", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 17767}
{"candidates": ["Only if you or the other driver is injured.", "Only if you are at fault.", "If there is property damage in excess of $750 or if there are any injuries."], "question": "How must you equip your motorcycle to accommodate carrying a passenger?", "answer": 2, "state": "dc", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 17976}
{"candidates": ["Slow down or stop, if necessary, and then make the turn.", "Signal and turn immediately.", "Stop before entering the right lane and let all other traffic go first."], "question": "It is important to use your mirrors in which of the following situations?", "answer": 0, "state": "dc", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 18037}
{"candidates": ["Start to prepare to slow down", "Sound a sharp blast of your horn", "Flash your head lights"], "question": "If a child is about to run into the street, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19411}
{"candidates": ["You may not turn in that direction", "You can turn in that direction", "You can turn in that direction after you come to a complete stop"], "question": "A green arrow on a traffic light means:", "answer": 1, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19412}
{"candidates": ["Other drivers tend to pull behind large vehicles before they try to pass them", "If you follow too closely, you will get caught in the vehicle's slipstream", "You need the extra room to see around the vehicle and to the sides"], "question": "You should allow for an extra cushion of space when following large vehicles because:", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19415}
{"candidates": ["Delaware Driver Manual", "BBC", "Fox"], "question": "What should you review for information before starting your vehicle?", "answer": 0, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19462}
{"candidates": ["On a lighted street.", "In fog.", "On a freeway."], "question": "It is necessary to use your low beams any time you are:", "answer": 1, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19478}
{"candidates": ["When following other vehicles", "As little as possible", "Except when there are oncoming vehicles"], "question": "Use your high beam headlights at night:", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19480}
{"candidates": ["Within 30 days", "Within 60 days", "Within 90 days"], "question": "If you move to the state of Delaware, you must apply for a Delaware state license in what time frame?", "answer": 1, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19495}
{"candidates": ["1", "2", "3"], "question": "Within how many days after legally changing your name must you personally go to an office of the Division of Motor Vehicles?", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19496}
{"candidates": ["Within 15 days ", "Within 30 days", "Within 7 days"], "question": "After you have changed addresses, when should you notify the DMV?", "answer": 1, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19523}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "Blood pressure medications.", "Sleep medications."], "question": "What kind of drugs can make drivers drowsy?", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19526}
{"candidates": ["Speed up to increase the distance from the car behind", "Apply your brakes to slow down, then resume speed", "Reduce speed slowly to encourage the tailgater to drive around you"], "question": "If you are being followed too closely on a two lane road:", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19535}
{"candidates": ["You must have a minimum visual acuity in both eyes better than 20/200 (best corrected).", "You must have a minimum visual acuity in at least one eye better than 20/200 (best corrected).", "You must have a minimum visual acuity in at least one eye better than 20/200 without corrective lenses."], "question": "To pass the vision screening test, you must have what vision with or without corrective lenses?", "answer": 1, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19555}
{"candidates": ["Because it takes 1/4 mile to stop completely", "Because it helps you keep up with traffic", "In order to avoid last-minute braking or sudden turns"], "question": "On the highway, you should look well down the road:", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19559}
{"candidates": ["A solid white line", "A solid yellow line", "A dashed yellow line"], "question": "What pavement marking indicates that you are allowed to pass?", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19582}
{"candidates": ["You should double the following distance to a minimum of 4 seconds.", "You should double the following distance to a minimum of 8 seconds.", "You should double the following distance to a minimum of 6 seconds."], "question": "Which of the following is true of speed limits in poor visibility or driving conditions?", "answer": 0, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19583}
{"candidates": ["To inform them that part of the road or street ahead of them is closed.", "To direct drivers into certain traffic lanes.", "All the others."], "question": "In work zones, what does a large flashing arrow panel sign mean?", "answer": 1, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19585}
{"candidates": ["Signaling a right turn", "Turning into your lane", "Going very slowly"], "question": "If you are passing another car, you should sound your horn when the car is:", "answer": 1, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19590}
{"candidates": ["When following a passenger car", "When following a station wagon", "When following drivers whose view to the rear is blocked"], "question": "You should allow an extra cushion of space:", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19598}
{"candidates": ["A maximum of 50 feet and a minimum of 15 feet from the nearest railroad track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 100 feet from the nearest track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 50 feet from the nearest track"], "question": "Which of the following is not a required occasion for headlight use?", "answer": 0, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19613}
{"candidates": ["120 days after that.", "Expiration date is indicated on your sticker and registration card.", "90 days after that."], "question": "Your registration expires when, relating to the license plate tags affixed to your vehicle?", "answer": 1, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19614}
{"candidates": ["Driving any vehicle that does not require a motorcycle or commercial license.", "Driving a commercial vehicle.", "Driving a motorcycle."], "question": "A class D operator's license is for:", "answer": 0, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19645}
{"candidates": ["May be restrained at the parent's discretion", "Must be restrained always", "Must be restrained only when driving on freeways"], "question": "Children under the age of 16 years old:", "answer": 1, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19656}
{"candidates": ["Stay off the brakes", "Apply the brakes lightly", "Pump the brakes"], "question": "If your car begins to skid out of control:", "answer": 0, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19680}
{"candidates": ["Going down long gradual hills", "On long gradual curves", "Going up long or steep hills"], "question": "Large trucks are most likely to lose speed:", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19681}
{"candidates": ["Moving into the right lane and drive slowly until it has passed.", "Pulling off the road, or as near to the right as possible.", "Speeding up to clear traffic."], "question": "You must yield the right-of-way to an emergency vehicle by:", "answer": 1, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19711}
{"candidates": ["25 mph", "20 mph", "30 mph"], "question": "Unless otherwise posted, the speed limit in residential areas is:", "answer": 0, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19722}
{"candidates": ["100", "200", "300"], "question": "How many feet away should you move from a vehicle if the fire in a vehicle becomes out of control?", "answer": 0, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19731}
{"candidates": ["As soon as the train has passed", "Only when the train is well down the track", "Only when the train is out of sight"], "question": "When crossing double railroad tracks, you may cross:", "answer": 1, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19748}
{"candidates": ["Closer to the car ahead than normal", "Farther from the car ahead than normal", "A normal distance from the car ahead"], "question": "If the road is slippery, you should keep a following distance that is:", "answer": 1, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19805}
{"candidates": ["Emergency contact information may be submitted online", "Emergency contact information may be submitted on the Next of Kin/Emergency Contact form", "All the others"], "question": "To register for Delaware's next of kin registry, you should do what?", "answer": 0, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19819}
{"candidates": ["Slow down by shifting to the lower gear", "Slowly ease your foot off the gas pedal", "Slow down by pumping the brakes quickly and firmly"], "question": "If it feels as if your tires have lost contact with the surface of the road, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19834}
{"candidates": ["Who is at fault for Right-of-Way crashes", "Nothing about the Right-of-Way", "Who must yield the Right-of-Way"], "question": "Delaware law and the Driver's Manual do not say who has the Right-of-Way. They do say:", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19836}
{"candidates": ["If your are speeding", "If your license expires", "If you violate driving laws"], "question": "When may the state of Delaware suspend a driver license?", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19855}
{"candidates": ["A dairy truck", "A cattle truck", "A school bus"], "question": "One vehicle that is required to stop for railroad crossings is:", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19860}
{"candidates": ["Immediately", "Within 24 hours", "Within 1 week"], "question": "You are involved in a personal injury accident. You must report the accident:", "answer": 0, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19862}
{"candidates": ["To warn others of bad conditions", "To see the road ahead", "So others can see you"], "question": "Use your headlights on rainy, snowy, or foggy days:", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19865}
{"candidates": ["Only if you are not insured.", "Only if it was your fault.", "No matter who was at fault"], "question": "You must make a report after an accident when damage to one of the vehicles is over $500:", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19886}
{"candidates": ["8;50lbs", "7;66lbs", "8;66lbs"], "question": "Children under what age and/or weight must use a child safety seat or booster seat?", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19944}
{"candidates": ["Drive in the lane closest to oncoming traffic.", "Speed up to get off the road quickly.", "Increase your following distance."], "question": "If bad weather makes it hard for you to see, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19951}
{"candidates": ["24 months", "12 months", "6 months"], "question": "How many months is the learner's permit issued for?", "answer": 0, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19968}
{"candidates": ["15 mph", "25 mph", "20 mph"], "question": "The speed limit in school zones is:", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 19982}
{"candidates": ["If your wiper blades are very cold, moisture will make them crack", "When fluid is cold it can scratch your windshield", "It will keep the washer fluid from freezing"], "question": "Use antifreeze washer fluid because:", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "permit", "id": 20007}
{"candidates": ["Be over 21 years of age", "Be a licensed driver", "Not have any traffic violations on their driving record"], "question": "To get a motorcycle endorsement, the applicant must:", "answer": 1, "state": "de", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 20106}
{"candidates": ["15", "5", "10"], "question": "Under the influence of alcohol, what is the first thing affected first?", "answer": 1, "state": "de", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 20120}
{"candidates": ["1", "3", "2"], "question": "You should allow a minimum of how many seconds between you and the vehicle in front?", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 20138}
{"candidates": ["Look only at the car in front of you while driving.", "Always put one car length between you and the car ahead.", "Keep your eyes moving to look for possible hazards."], "question": "While driving your motorcycle you notice a dog begin to chase you. What should you do?", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 20149}
{"candidates": ["Drive slowly enough so you can stop within the area lighted by your headlights.", "Turn on your high beam headlights to better see the vehicles ahead of you.", "Keep the instrument panel lights bright to be more visible to other\tdrivers."], "question": "Considering a crash that happens in traffic, ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "de", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 20150}
{"candidates": ["One-quarter", "Three-quarter", "Full face"], "question": "Which of the following is not a type of helmet?", "answer": 0, "state": "de", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 20199}
{"candidates": ["If the vehicle ahead of you is turning left.", "If the shoulder is wide enough to accommodate your vehicle", "Under no circumstances"], "question": "What is the best protection you can have as a rider?", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 20209}
{"candidates": [".02 percent", ".08 percent", ".1 percent"], "question": "The legal limit to be considered intoxicated is a Blood Alcohol Concentration of:", "answer": 1, "state": "de", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 20244}
{"candidates": ["Search, Evaluate, Execute", "Scan, Enter, Exit", "Slow, Exceed, Error"], "question": "Experienced riders are aware of what\u2019s around them. To do this, they use the SEE strategy. What does SEE stand for?", "answer": 0, "state": "de", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 20260}
{"candidates": ["Should drive slower than other traffic for 200 feet.", "Should wait for the first two vehicles to pass, then drive into the lane.", "Need a large enough gap to get up to the speed of traffic."], "question": "How long does it take alcohol that is consumed to reach the brain and start to affect the drinker?", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 20271}
{"candidates": ["Loading zone for passengers or mail only.", "Loading zone for freight only.", "Loading zone for freight or passengers."], "question": "What hand signal should you use if you want to advise vehicles that you are going to stop?", "answer": 0, "state": "de", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 20299}
{"candidates": ["Stop, then proceed when safe.", "Slow down or stop, only if necessary.", "Stop before entering the intersection and let all other traffic go first."], "question": "What is the hand signal for speed up?", "answer": 0, "state": "de", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 20328}
{"candidates": ["Other drivers when they want to slow down.", "The truck driver to stop the vehicle.", "Other drivers when merging onto a freeway."], "question": "Your chances of being involved in a crash increase whenever you ride across what?", "answer": 1, "state": "de", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 20358}
{"candidates": ["Farther behind the truck than you would for a passenger vehicle.", "No more than one car length behind the truck so the driver can see you.", "Closely behind the truck in bad weather because the driver can see farther ahead."], "question": "If a child is riding with an adult, they should be placed ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "de", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 20422}
{"candidates": ["May be crossed to enter or exit a private driveway.", "May not be crossed for any reason.", "Should be treated as a separate traffic lane."], "question": "If a rider wishes to ride a three-wheel vehicle, they need to ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "de", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 20447}
{"candidates": ["Only if you see orange cones on the road ahead.", "Unless they conflict with existing signs, signals, or laws.", "At all times."], "question": "In order to get your license, you have to pass a ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "de", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 20451}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "Slow down and use caution when approaching animals.", "Use caution and be alert when driving on roadways making with deer crossing signs."], "question": "Which of the following can reduce your chances of colliding with an animal?", "answer": 0, "state": "fl", "type": "permit", "id": 21907}
{"candidates": ["Follow the emergency vehicles.", "Pull over to the closest edge of the roadway immediately and stop until the emergency vehicle has passed.", "Speed up."], "question": "When law enforcement vehicles, fire engines, and other emergency vehicles are using their sirens and/or flashing their lights you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "fl", "type": "permit", "id": 21935}
{"candidates": ["2,500 pounds", "2,000 pounds", "3,000 pounds"], "question": "A vehicle weighing less than how many pounds does not require a VIN verification?", "answer": 1, "state": "fl", "type": "permit", "id": 21991}
{"candidates": ["40", "20", "30"], "question": "Over ____ percent of children who die in car accidents are not properly restrained.", "answer": 1, "state": "fl", "type": "permit", "id": 22001}
{"candidates": ["24", "72", "48"], "question": "How many hours does a sexual offender have to register at a driver's license office?", "answer": 2, "state": "fl", "type": "permit", "id": 22058}
{"candidates": ["Blind spots can be checked by looking in your rear view mirrors.", "Large trucks have bigger blind spots than most passenger vehicles.", "They are eliminated if you have one outside mirror on each side of the vehicle."], "question": "All these are situations in which drivers must stop for pedestrians except:", "answer": 1, "state": "fl", "type": "permit", "id": 22088}
{"candidates": ["Slow to 25 MPH and pass cautiously.", "Stop as long as the red lights are flashing.", "Stop, then proceed when you think all of the children have exited the bus."], "question": "When applying for a Florida driver license, what are acceptable forms of proof of social security number?", "answer": 1, "state": "fl", "type": "permit", "id": 22118}
{"candidates": ["Under no circumstances.", "During rush hour traffic.", "When you entered the intersection on the green light."], "question": "Which is true about loads that project (stick out) 4 feet or more past the rear of the vehicle?", "answer": 0, "state": "fl", "type": "permit", "id": 22119}
{"candidates": ["10 to 15 seconds", "5 to 10 seconds", "15 to 20 seconds"], "question": "Which of the following is allowed on Florida expressways?", "answer": 0, "state": "fl", "type": "permit", "id": 22208}
{"candidates": ["Traffic on the street moves to the left.", "Traffic on the street moves to the right.", "A sign permits the turn."], "question": "Which of the following does a roundabout do?", "answer": 0, "state": "fl", "type": "permit", "id": 22263}
{"candidates": ["Get out of your vehicle or approach the officer.", "Pull over in a way.", "Remain in your vehicle while the officer approaches. "], "question": "Which of the following should you do if you are pulled over by a police office?", "answer": 2, "state": "fl", "type": "permit", "id": 22264}
{"candidates": ["your physical/residential address", "your name", "your name; your physical/residential address"], "question": "When renewing your license, if you have changed your address you will need to show ____ documents proving the address change.", "answer": 2, "state": "fl", "type": "permit", "id": 22297}
{"candidates": ["No more than one car length behind the truck so the driver can see you.", "Farther behind the truck than you would for a passenger vehicle.", "Closely behind the truck in bad weather because the driver can see farther ahead."], "question": "When you are purchasing a new protective helmet, you need to ensure your helmet ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "fl", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 22361}
{"candidates": ["At least 30 feet but not more than 100 feet from the nearest track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 50 feet from the nearest track", "A maximum of 50 feet and a minimum of 15 feet from the nearest railroad track"], "question": "What must you possess in order to enroll in the Basic Rider Course?", "answer": 2, "state": "fl", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 22395}
{"candidates": ["Signal for 100 feet before turning.", "Move toward the left side of your lane.", "Avoid driving in the bicycle lane."], "question": "If a group riding in a formation want to complete a pass of another vehicle, how many riders should complete the pass at the same time?", "answer": 0, "state": "fl", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 22400}
{"candidates": ["Slow down and cross the intersection carefully.", "Stop before entering the intersection as long as you can do so safely.", "Stop. Yield to all cross traffic before crossing the intersection."], "question": "It is harder for other motorists to see motorcycles on the road due to their size, which of the following will increase your visibility to other motorists?", "answer": 0, "state": "fl", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 22405}
{"candidates": ["The other side of the road is a solid line.", "Your side of the road is a broken line.", "The other side of the road is a broken line."], "question": "Before you ride your motorcycle you should do a complete check to make sure everything is working properly. Which of the following areas is not necessary to check?", "answer": 1, "state": "fl", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 22413}
{"candidates": ["Leave a note on the vehicle.", "Both of the above.", "Report the accident without delay to the city police or, in unincorporated areas, to the CHP."], "question": "A chain which ____ or ____ while you're riding can lock the rear wheel and cause your cycle to slip.", "answer": 1, "state": "fl", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 22414}
{"candidates": ["On a one-way street on a green arrow.", "Across two sets of solid double, yellow lines.", "When there are no vehicles approaching nearby."], "question": "Which of the following should you not do if you are riding with passengers on your motorcycle?", "answer": 2, "state": "fl", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 22422}
{"candidates": ["Directly before and after school hours.", "You must always obey school crossing-guards.", "There are children present."], "question": "Under what conditions are you legally allowed to not wear a helmet on a motorcycle?", "answer": 1, "state": "fl", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 22441}
{"candidates": ["You do not have room on the other side to completely cross the tracks.", "You transport two or more young children in a passenger vehicle.", "The railroad crossing is located in a city or town that has frequent train traffic."], "question": "The Florida Rider Training Program offers a ____ course that provides instruction on safe and responsible motorcycle riding.", "answer": 0, "state": "fl", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 22446}
{"candidates": ["Unless they conflict with existing signs, signals, or laws.", "At all times.", "Only if you see orange cones on the road ahead."], "question": "Your chances of being involved in a crash increases whenever you ride across ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "fl", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 22464}
{"candidates": ["Avoid making fast turns and fast stops.", "Test your tires\u2019 traction while going uphill.", "Decrease the distance you look ahead of your vehicle."], "question": "In order to increase your visibility at night, you should ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "fl", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 22483}
{"candidates": ["A speed which matches the flow of traffic.", "A speed just below the posted speed limit.", "The posted speed limit."], "question": "When riding over railroad tracks, it's generally safer to ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "fl", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 22488}
{"candidates": ["Slow down because the lane ends ahead.", "Be prepared for workers and equipment ahead.", "Change lanes and maintain your current speed."], "question": "If someone is following too closely to you what should you do?", "answer": 1, "state": "fl", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 22489}
{"candidates": ["The lane in the center of the road.", "Any lane (as long as it is safe)", "The lane closest to the left curb"], "question": "Which of the following is a reason to avoid driving alongside cars while operating a motorcycle?", "answer": 2, "state": "fl", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 22504}
{"candidates": ["You consent to have a blood sample taken if an officer stops you for driving recklessly.", "You must sign a statement that you will not drive a motor vehicle after drinking more than three drinks.", "You agree to be tested for the amount of alcohol in your blood, if you are arrested for drunk or impaired driving."], "question": "The Georgia Implied Consent Law means that:", "answer": 2, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 23946}
{"candidates": ["60 miles per hour.", "55 miles per hour.", "70 miles per hour."], "question": "The maximum speed limit on a rural Interstate Highway is:", "answer": 2, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 23972}
{"candidates": ["Slowly pass vehicles that seem to be stopped for no reason.", "Look to the sides of your vehicle to see what is coming.", "Stop, listen, and proceed cautiously."], "question": "Which of the following indicates the ability to pass?", "answer": 1, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 23989}
{"candidates": ["The other vehicle is making or about to make a left turn, when a lane is provided to pass on the right.", "Both answers.", "When traveling on a multi-lane highway carrying two or more lanes of traffic in the same direction."], "question": "You may pass on the right of another vehicle when:", "answer": 1, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 24032}
{"candidates": ["Any resident who wishes to operate agricultural vehicles, military vehicles, and firefighting apparatus or emergency vehicles.", "Any resident who wishes to operate a Class A or B motor vehicle who is not required to possess a commercial driver's license.", "All the others."], "question": "When do you have to take a driving test for Class E and F Non-Commercial?", "answer": 1, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 24054}
{"candidates": ["Use your high beam headlights until you are within 10 feet of the vehicle ahead.", "Use your high beam headlights.", "Keep your headlights on low beam."], "question": "When driving behind another vehicle at night, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 24063}
{"candidates": ["Turn on your high beam headlights to better see the vehicles ahead of you.", "Drive slowly enough so you can stop within the area lighted by your headlights.", "Keep the instrument panel lights bright to be more visible to other\tdrivers."], "question": "Which text below would you expect to find on a guide sign?", "answer": 1, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 24086}
{"candidates": ["When it first starts to rain", "When the rain is about to stop", "When the rain is most heavy"], "question": "When is the highest risk of skidding during rainfall?", "answer": 0, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 24088}
{"candidates": ["Hold the steering wheel firmly; release the gas pedal; and gently apply the brakes. Return to the pavement when the vehicle has slowed enough to allow roll steer back onto the highway safely.", "Release the gas pedal and turn the front wheels slightly to the left to edge the car back on the pavement.", "Apply the brakes and turn the front wheels sharply to the left."], "question": "You have allowed the wheels of your vehicle to run off the edge of the pavement. You should:", "answer": 0, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 24097}
{"candidates": ["Upcoming vehicles", "Pedestrians", "Any vehicles"], "question": "Drivers must yield to any ____ before making a right turn at a green light.", "answer": 1, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 24113}
{"candidates": ["Look both ways and make sure that the oncoming lanes are clear.", "Turn on the left turn signal before you make the turn and slow down.", "All the others."], "question": "What should drivers do when making a left turn?", "answer": 1, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 24146}
{"candidates": ["Get out of your car and walk for help.", "Stand behind your car to warn traffic that you have stopped.", "Raise the hood to indicate trouble, and wait in your car for help."], "question": "If you have to stop on the shoulder of a freeway because of an emergency, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 24153}
{"candidates": ["When your actions may not result in a traffic citation.", "When entering or exiting driveways.", "When you can help reduce traffic congestion."], "question": "When can motorists cross over bicycle lanes?", "answer": 1, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 24201}
{"candidates": ["When you want to pass a driver ahead of you who is turning right.", "When you are within 200 feet of a cross street where you plan to turn right.", "During rush hour traffic if there are no bicyclists in the bike lane."], "question": "When is passing prohibited on a two lane road?", "answer": 1, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 24202}
{"candidates": ["Anytime you want.", "Only when it is safe to do so.", "As long as you can finish the pass."], "question": "When may a motorist change lanes on a multi-lane highway and pass slower moving vehicles?", "answer": 1, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 24205}
{"candidates": ["Are irresponsible drivers ", "Fail to satisfy a claim for damage resulting from a motor vehicle crash", "All the others"], "question": "The purpose of the Safety Responsibility Law is to suspend license of drivers who:", "answer": 0, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 24224}
{"candidates": ["3", "4", "5"], "question": "Georgia law dictates a driver must allow, if feasible, a minimum of ____ ft. when passing a bicyclist.", "answer": 0, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 24232}
{"candidates": ["Urban areas", "All the others.", "School zones"], "question": "Where should you be careful to look for pedestrians?", "answer": 2, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 24264}
{"candidates": ["Carefully drive around the pedestrian.", "Stop and let the pedestrian cross the street.", "Make sure the pedestrian sees you, but continue driving."], "question": "Tolled lanes in Georgia require what from motorists?", "answer": 1, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 24290}
{"candidates": ["Mandatory", "Necessary", "Voluntary"], "question": "When you obtain your driver's license or permit, you will have the opportunity to make a $1 ____ donation to Georgia's Blindness Education, Screening, and Treatment program.", "answer": 2, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 24292}
{"candidates": ["40 miles per hour", "45 miles per hour", "35 miles per hour"], "question": "Water on the road can cause a vehicle to hydroplane. Your car may hydroplane at speeds as low as:", "answer": 2, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 24303}
{"candidates": ["Notify the Secretary of State's Office.", "Render aid to the injured.", "Notify your insurance agent."], "question": "If you are involved in an accident, one of the immediate requirements is to:", "answer": 1, "state": "ga", "type": "permit", "id": 24324}
{"candidates": ["Turned to the left (toward the street).", "Parallel with the pavement.", "Turned to the right (away from the street)."], "question": "In extreme hot weather, what should be done to mitigate the risks posed by such weather?", "answer": 2, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24435}
{"candidates": ["If there is property damage in excess of $750 or if there are any injuries.", "Only if you or the other driver is injured.", "Only if you are at fault."], "question": "When riding in groups you should ride ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24438}
{"candidates": ["Slow down or stop, only if necessary.", "Stop, then proceed when safe.", "Stop before entering the intersection and let all other traffic go first."], "question": "What is a Georgia PeachPass?", "answer": 1, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24465}
{"candidates": ["When there are no vehicles approaching nearby.", "On a one-way street on a green arrow.", "Across two sets of solid double, yellow lines."], "question": "How should a rider plan an escape route?", "answer": 0, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24470}
{"candidates": ["Your arms should be used to hold you up", "Your arms should be used to steer the motorcycle", "You should have to stretch to reach the handgrips"], "question": "When positioning your body on the motorcycle:", "answer": 1, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24478}
{"candidates": ["The railroad crossing is located in a city or town that has frequent train traffic.", "You do not have room on the other side to completely cross the tracks.", "You transport two or more young children in a passenger vehicle."], "question": "Which of these is related to your riding posture?", "answer": 1, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24490}
{"candidates": ["Avoid making fast turns and fast stops.", "Decrease the distance you look ahead of your vehicle.", "Test your tires\u2019 traction while going uphill."], "question": "Carrying additional cargo or passengers will alter what on the motorcycle?", "answer": 0, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24491}
{"candidates": ["You transport two or more young children in a passenger vehicle.", "The railroad crossing is located in a city or town that has frequent train traffic.", "You do not have room on the other side to completely cross the tracks."], "question": "What is an escape route?", "answer": 2, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24498}
{"candidates": ["Between 65 mph and 70 mph.", "70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic.", "No faster than 65 mph."], "question": "If you are parking your motorcycle on the roadside what can you do to prevent your bike from rolling?", "answer": 2, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24499}
{"candidates": ["Use hands-free devices so you can keep both hands on the steering wheel.", "Keep your phone within easy reach so you won't need to take your eyes off the road.", "Review the number before answering a call."], "question": "Which one of these statements is untrue about other drivers sharing the road with a motorcyclist?", "answer": 0, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24500}
{"candidates": ["Assume the other driver will maintain a constant speed.", "Assume the other driver will let you pass if you use your turn signal.", "Not assume the other driver will make space for you to return to your lane."], "question": "What is an example of a three-wheel vehicle with its associated track?", "answer": 2, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24501}
{"candidates": ["You can frustrate the other drivers and make them angry.", "Your actions cannot result in a traffic citation.", "You help reduce traffic congestion."], "question": "Two-wheel motorcycles and three-wheel vehicles differ mostly in how ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24525}
{"candidates": ["The other side of the road is a broken line.", "The other side of the road is a solid line.", "Your side of the road is a broken line."], "question": "If your front tire goes flat, how will your steering wheel feel?", "answer": 2, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24529}
{"candidates": ["When you are within 200 feet of a cross street where you plan to turn right.", "When you want to pass a driver ahead of you who is turning right.", "During rush hour traffic if there are no bicyclists in the bike lane."], "question": "What is considering the most difficult angle to start a motorcycle?", "answer": 0, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24531}
{"candidates": ["Fail a smog test for your vehicle.", "Get a new prescription for lenses or contacts.", "Sell or transfer your vehicle."], "question": "When should you adjust your speed when riding in a curve?", "answer": 2, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24549}
{"candidates": ["The lane closest to the left curb", "The lane in the center of the road.", "Any lane (as long as it is safe)"], "question": "Your visibility to other motorists is greatly reduced while riding at night. Which of the following should you do to compensate for the reduced visibility?", "answer": 0, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24553}
{"candidates": ["Be prepared for workers and equipment ahead.", "Change lanes and maintain your current speed.", "Slow down because the lane ends ahead."], "question": "Which of the following is a responsibility of a rider?", "answer": 0, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24554}
{"candidates": ["Any vehicle with 3 or more axles or weighing more than 4,000 pounds.", "Motor homes or pickup trucks towing a boat trailer.", "Tank trucks marked with hazardous materials placards."], "question": "When accelerating, you need steer ____ in the ____ direction of the sidecar.", "answer": 2, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24555}
{"candidates": ["May be crossed to enter or exit a private driveway.", "May not be crossed for any reason.", "Should be treated as a separate traffic lane."], "question": "What does the abbreviation HOV stand for?", "answer": 1, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24557}
{"candidates": ["Directly before and after school hours.", "There are children present.", "You must always obey school crossing-guards."], "question": "What is the primary way you stop quickly to avoid collisions if you have a sidecar attached to your motorcycle?", "answer": 2, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24558}
{"candidates": ["No more than 25 inches higher than", "No more than 10 inches higher than", "The same height as"], "question": "Handlebars should be ____ the rider\u2019s seat.", "answer": 0, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24571}
{"candidates": ["Headlights.", "Parking lights", "Interior lights"], "question": "Which of the following applies when trying to obtain your motorcycle license in the state of Georgia?", "answer": 0, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24591}
{"candidates": ["The handlebars should be above your head, when you are seated.", "When standing next to the motorcycle, the seat should be no more than 10 inches above your waist", "Your feet should reach the ground while you are seated on the motorcycle."], "question": "How can you tell if your motorcycle fits you?", "answer": 2, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24602}
{"candidates": ["Only passengers, not the driver, can have open containers of alcohol", "Only passengers in the back seat can have open containers of alcohol", "No one may have open containers of alcohol"], "question": "Under Georgia law, in the passenger area of a vehicle____", "answer": 2, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24638}
{"candidates": ["Blind spots can be checked by looking in your rear view mirrors.", "Large trucks have bigger blind spots than most passenger vehicles.", "They are eliminated if you have one outside mirror on each side of the vehicle."], "question": "Which of the following are recommended you do when riding in a group to provide safety for the group as well as other motorists?", "answer": 1, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24646}
{"candidates": ["0.08", "0.02", "0.04"], "question": "The BAC level for DUI for persons under 21 has been established at", "answer": 1, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24699}
{"candidates": ["You must always obey school crossing-guards.", "Directly before and after school hours.", "There are children present."], "question": "When your bike is loaded with passengers or cargo it will need more what to stop?", "answer": 0, "state": "ga", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 24702}
{"candidates": ["To shift an automotive vehicle into a higher gear.", "Not sure.", " Manually downshifting an automatic transmission into a lower gear slows the vehicle. "], "question": "What is downshifting?", "answer": 2, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26201}
{"candidates": ["Only if you see orange cones on the road ahead.", "At all times.", "Unless they conflict with existing signs, signals, or laws."], "question": "What is the purpose of flashing arrow panels in work zones?", "answer": 1, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26228}
{"candidates": ["Green", "White", "Red"], "question": "What color and markings do directional signs typically have?", "answer": 0, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26311}
{"candidates": ["Stop as long as the red lights are flashing.", "Stop, then proceed when you think all of the children have exited the bus.", "Slow to 25 MPH and pass cautiously."], "question": "Bicyclists may ride on the sidewalk as long as they stay at what speed?", "answer": 0, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26314}
{"candidates": ["10 inches", "18 inches", "24 inches"], "question": "When parallel parked, the vehicle's curbside wheels should be within ____ of the curb.", "answer": 1, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26316}
{"candidates": ["School bus", "All the others.", "Large truck"], "question": "Which of the following vehicles requires specifically special driving skill, attentiveness and consideration?", "answer": 2, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26317}
{"candidates": ["Reconstructed", "Sold", "Bought"], "question": "Vehicles that have been ____ may be required to comply with county reconstructed vehicle inspection requirements.", "answer": 0, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26343}
{"candidates": ["Purple", "Orange or neon green", "Black and green"], "question": "What color vests do most flag persons wear?", "answer": 1, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26345}
{"candidates": ["Sending a text message", "Talking on a cell phone", "All the other."], "question": "Which of the following can distract you while driving?", "answer": 0, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26347}
{"candidates": ["45%", "30%", "28%"], "question": "Alcohol is a factor in what percentage of fatal motor vehicle accidents?", "answer": 2, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26377}
{"candidates": ["Carefully drive around the pedestrian.", "The practice of drivers who consciously reduce the dangers associated with driving.", "Stop and let the pedestrian cross the street."], "question": "What is the basic idea of defensive driving?", "answer": 1, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26407}
{"candidates": ["Letters RR", "an X with the letter R", "An X with the letters RR"], "question": "What letters are painted on the traffic lane before a railroad crossing?", "answer": 2, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26433}
{"candidates": ["Failure to ensure adequate visibility.", "An aggressive driving attitude and making rude gestures.", "Incorrect seating position."], "question": "Which of the following bad driving habits is a result of impatience?", "answer": 1, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26436}
{"candidates": ["To the left", "To the middle", "To the right"], "question": "If you have parked downhill, with or without a curb, you should turn your front wheels ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26494}
{"candidates": ["Give warnings.", "Direct the way.", "Provide valuable information to drivers and other road users."], "question": "What is the purpose of a traffic sign?", "answer": 2, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26553}
{"candidates": ["Left-lane", "Right-lane", "In the middle"], "question": "A motorcyclist needs to position himself in the lane ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26554}
{"candidates": ["Ship", "Car, bus or truck ", "Bicycle"], "question": "The motor vehicle insurance law states that every owner of a ____ must have motor vehicle insurance in order to operate a vehicle in Hawaii.", "answer": 1, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26582}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "The rules of right-of-way", "No passing rules"], "question": "Questions on the motorcycle/motorscooter written examination include questions on what rules?", "answer": 2, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26611}
{"candidates": ["200 feet before changing", "150 feet before changing", "100 feet before changing"], "question": "When does a driver have to signal to indicate his intention to change lanes?", "answer": 2, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26612}
{"candidates": ["Tell that you may proceed only with caution.", "Tell that you must move only in the direction indicated by the green arrow when it is lighted.", "Tell that you must not use that lane."], "question": "Commonly, lighted arrow traffic signals are used to ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26667}
{"candidates": ["Red and white", "Yellow and white", "Orange and black"], "question": "Obstruction markings are typically what colors?", "answer": 0, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26669}
{"candidates": ["Review the number before answering a call.", "Keep your phone within easy reach so you won't need to take your eyes off the road.", "Use hands-free devices so you can keep both hands on the steering wheel."], "question": "Which of the following is something you should consider when planning a route for an upcoming trip?", "answer": 2, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26699}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "Exhaust system", "Brakes"], "question": "Which of the following is required equipment for motor vehicles that are operated on the highways of Hawaii?", "answer": 2, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26762}
{"candidates": ["As long as you got your license", "Whenever you drive", "Whenever you are in a car"], "question": "When is it necessary to carry a license?", "answer": 1, "state": "hi", "type": "permit", "id": 26786}
{"candidates": ["See the vehicle\u2019s headlights in your rear view mirror.", "Have passed the other vehicle\u2019s front bumper.", "Cannot see the vehicle directly to your right."], "question": "Which of following surfaces provide poor traction?", "answer": 0, "state": "hi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 26846}
{"candidates": ["One vehicle is traveling faster or slower than the flow of traffic.", "All vehicles are traveling about the same speed.", "One lane of traffic is traveling faster than the other lanes."], "question": "Why should a motorcyclist avoid operating directly alongside another rider?", "answer": 0, "state": "hi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 26847}
{"candidates": ["Stop. Yield to all cross traffic before crossing the intersection.", "Slow down and cross the intersection carefully.", "Stop before entering the intersection as long as you can do so safely."], "question": "How much can you be fined if you cannot present to a police officer a valid proof of insurance?", "answer": 1, "state": "hi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 26879}
{"candidates": ["Turned to the left (toward the street).", "Turned to the right (away from the street).", "Parallel with the pavement."], "question": "How do heavy passengers affect your motorcycle?", "answer": 1, "state": "hi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 26881}
{"candidates": ["High beams.", "Low beams.", "Fog lights only."], "question": "To stop quickly, you should ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "hi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 26882}
{"candidates": ["If the vehicle ahead of you is turning left.", "If the shoulder is wide enough to accommodate your vehicle", "Under no circumstances"], "question": "What is an easy check to make sure a motorcycle is a right fit for you?", "answer": 2, "state": "hi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 27001}
{"candidates": ["Any 3-axle vehicle regardless of the weight.", "A 3-axle vehicle if the Gross Vehicle Weight is less than 6,000 pounds.", "A vehicle pulling two trailers."], "question": "During the cone weave, the rider starts weaving to the ____ of the first cone.", "answer": 1, "state": "hi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 27091}
{"candidates": ["Look only at the car in front of you while driving.", "Keep your eyes moving to look for possible hazards.", "Always put one car length between you and the car ahead."], "question": "What is a \"wobble\"?", "answer": 1, "state": "hi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 27116}
{"candidates": ["Must stay in the right lane at all times while turning.", "May have to swing wide to complete the right turn.", "May complete its turn in either of the two lanes."], "question": "A motorcyclist should search his path of travel how many seconds ahead?", "answer": 1, "state": "hi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 27119}
{"candidates": ["On the side of the freeway in an emergency.", "Next to a red painted curb.", "Within 100 feet of an elementary school."], "question": "In an emergency situation, you should press the horn button ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "hi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 27145}
{"candidates": ["You can frustrate the other drivers and make them angry.", "Your actions cannot result in a traffic citation.", "You help reduce traffic congestion."], "question": "What should you do first if your throttle becomes stuck while you are riding?", "answer": 0, "state": "hi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 27209}
{"candidates": ["May be crossed to enter or exit a private driveway.", "May not be crossed for any reason.", "Should be treated as a separate traffic lane."], "question": "Riders should be alert to whether a curve ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "hi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 27239}
{"candidates": ["Yield to pedestrians only in the intersection.", "Yield to any vehicle, bicycle, or pedestrian in the intersection.", "Wait four seconds before proceeding."], "question": "Why are small groups of riders sometimes better than large groups of riders on crowded highways?", "answer": 1, "state": "hi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 27269}
{"candidates": ["Slow down and allow the other driver to pass safely.", "Stay to the right side.", "Speed up."], "question": "Which of the following should you not do while being passed?", "answer": 0, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 28697}
{"candidates": ["Avoid making fast turns and fast stops.", "Decrease the distance you look ahead of your vehicle.", "Test your tires\u2019 traction while going uphill."], "question": "When should you stop if you come upon a traffic accident?", "answer": 0, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 28699}
{"candidates": ["Brakes", "A siren", "Seat belts"], "question": "Which of the following is not required equipment?", "answer": 1, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 28700}
{"candidates": ["Gradually slow down.", "Turn on your emergency flashers.", "All the others."], "question": "What should a driver do in an event of an unexpected emergency?", "answer": 1, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 28724}
{"candidates": ["Quickly check your rear-view mirror.", "All the others.", "Ease up on the brake just before you come in contact with the animal."], "question": "During instances when it's impossible to slow down to safely avoid hitting an animal what should you do?", "answer": 0, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 28725}
{"candidates": ["2 months", "10 days", "15 days"], "question": "In Idaho you may request up to 2 extensions of your driver's license if you are temporarily out of state at the expiration of your license. How long, in months, is each extension available for?", "answer": 1, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 28726}
{"candidates": ["To the middle", "To the left", "To the right"], "question": "When parking downhill, turn your front wheels ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 28729}
{"candidates": ["To the left.", "To the right.", "You want to go."], "question": "If you begin to skid, you should steer in the direction ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 28730}
{"candidates": ["6 months", "8 months", "12 months"], "question": "How many days can you practice driving a motor vehicle for with a Class D Instruction Permit?", "answer": 0, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 28731}
{"candidates": ["Stop", "Safe to enter", "Proceed with caution"], "question": "In Idaho, what does a flashing red light on a traffic signal indicate?", "answer": 0, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 28761}
{"candidates": ["500 feet", "300 feet", "200 feet"], "question": "Idaho state law states that when making a U-turn near a hill or curve, how far legally must you be able to see in either direction in feet?", "answer": 0, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 28788}
{"candidates": ["The leased vehicle will be titled in the name of the leasing company.", "The leased vehicle will be titled in the name of the lessor (owner).", "The leased vehicle will be titled in the name of the insurance company."], "question": "If you are leasing a vehicle, who owns the title?", "answer": 1, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 28790}
{"candidates": ["Pedestrians can always ask the vehicles to give them the right-of-ways.", "Right-of-way is something to be given, not taken.", "Motor vehicles must yield to a pedestrian any time."], "question": "Which of the following is important to remember about right-of-ways in Idaho?", "answer": 1, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 28819}
{"candidates": ["2 seconds", "5 seconds", "4 seconds"], "question": "When driving behind a snowplow truck, you should be two car lengths behind for what incremental speed?", "answer": 0, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 28848}
{"candidates": ["Easy to spot.", "Not easy to be seen.", "Often careless."], "question": "You should be on alert for pedestrians because they are ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 28850}
{"candidates": ["May not be crossed for any reason.", "Should be treated as a separate traffic lane.", "May be crossed to enter or exit a private driveway."], "question": "What should you do if a driver follows too closely?", "answer": 0, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 28906}
{"candidates": ["The Non-Resident Violator Compact is a point system in which you receive one to four points for each moving traffic violation on your record.", "The Non-Resident Violator Compact is a United States interstate compact used by 44 states and Washington, D.C. to process traffic citations across state borders.", "The Non-Resident Violator Compact is an agreement among states to promote driver compliance with driving laws, ordinances, and Administrative actions in member states."], "question": "What is the non-resident violator compact?", "answer": 1, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 28939}
{"candidates": ["You should be aware of motorists attempting to merge and make room for them if possible.", "You should share the road with the motorists.", "You should proceed as quickly as possible to make rooms for the vehicle already in the freeway."], "question": "While on the entrance ramp of a freeway, you ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 28967}
{"candidates": ["Warning letter", "Imprisonment", "Fine"], "question": "Which of the following are graduated license penalties for operators under the age of 17 under Idaho law?", "answer": 0, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 29026}
{"candidates": ["Passing is allowed on the left.", "Passing is allowed from either direction.", "Passing is prohibited from either direction."], "question": "A dashed yellow line lane marking means what?", "answer": 1, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 29085}
{"candidates": ["Give way to any traffic on your immediate right inside the roundabout.", "Keep moving if the way is clear and drive with the flow of traffic.", "All the others."], "question": "If entering a roundabout intersection, you should ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 29198}
{"candidates": ["5", "2", "10"], "question": "How many seconds should you signal for before changing lanes?", "answer": 1, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 29230}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "Texting", "Tailgating"], "question": "What should you NOT do while driving?", "answer": 0, "state": "id", "type": "permit", "id": 29259}
{"candidates": ["The handle grips are higher than your head", "Your feet should reach the ground when you are seated", "The controls should be easy to operate"], "question": "A motorcycle fits you if it is all of the following except:", "answer": 0, "state": "id", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 29363}
{"candidates": ["No more than one car length behind the truck so the driver can see you.", "Closely behind the truck in bad weather because the driver can see farther ahead.", "Farther behind the truck than you would for a passenger vehicle."], "question": "The safest way to cross railroad tracks is to ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "id", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 29379}
{"candidates": ["No faster than 65 mph.", "Between 65 mph and 70 mph.", "70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic."], "question": "Which of the following precautions should be taken when carrying a large load of cargo?", "answer": 0, "state": "id", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 29380}
{"candidates": ["When you want to pass a driver ahead of you who is turning right.", "When you are within 200 feet of a cross street where you plan to turn right.", "During rush hour traffic if there are no bicyclists in the bike lane."], "question": "Most crashes happen during ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "id", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 29403}
{"candidates": ["Use hands-free devices so you can keep both hands on the steering wheel.", "Review the number before answering a call.", "Keep your phone within easy reach so you won't need to take your eyes off the road."], "question": "Wearing ____ can greatly help in decreasing the chances of not being seen on the road.", "answer": 0, "state": "id", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 29407}
{"candidates": ["Report the accident without delay to the city police or, in unincorporated areas, to the CHP.", "Leave a note on the vehicle.", "Both of the above."], "question": "Any passengers under the age of ____ must wear a DOT-approved helmet while riding with you.", "answer": 2, "state": "id", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 29437}
{"candidates": ["Your actions cannot result in a traffic citation.", "You help reduce traffic congestion.", "You can frustrate the other drivers and make them angry."], "question": "Which of the following should you not do if you are riding with a passenger?", "answer": 2, "state": "id", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 29498}
{"candidates": ["When you entered the intersection on the green light.", "Under no circumstances.", "During rush hour traffic."], "question": "If someone is following you closely, you should ____ before you slow down.", "answer": 1, "state": "id", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 29522}
{"candidates": ["Slow down or stop, if necessary, and then make the turn.", "Stop before entering the right lane and let all other traffic go first.", "Signal and turn immediately."], "question": "If you need to stop quickly, you should apply which brake?", "answer": 0, "state": "id", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 29527}
{"candidates": ["Slow down because the lane ends ahead.", "Change lanes and maintain your current speed.", "Be prepared for workers and equipment ahead."], "question": "When should you do head checks?", "answer": 2, "state": "id", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 29528}
{"candidates": ["After waiting for one complete cycle, you may proceed through a red light with caution, while yielding to other traffic", "After waiting for five cycles, you may back up and re-approach the area to try to trigger the signal", "You may flag down a police officer and tell them the light will not change"], "question": "If your motorcycle does not trigger a control device (stoplight), what should you do?", "answer": 0, "state": "id", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 29578}
{"candidates": ["Acceptable if you want to race the other driver", "Discouraged because it may put you in the other vehicle\u2019s blind spot", "Encouraged if you want to travel at the same speed as the other driver"], "question": "Riding alongside another vehicle is:", "answer": 1, "state": "id", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 29604}
{"candidates": ["Donor", "Decide", "Drive"], "question": "Many experienced drivers are aware of what is happening around them by practicing SIPDE, What does the D stand for in SIPDE?", "answer": 1, "state": "id", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 29631}
{"candidates": ["Must merge into the bicycle lane before turning.", "May not enter the bicycle lane.", "Should only merge into the bicycle lane if you stop before turning."], "question": "How many steps are there for better control while turning?", "answer": 0, "state": "id", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 29647}
{"candidates": ["Low beams.", "High beams.", "Fog lights only."], "question": "Most motorcycle crashes occur at ____ mph or less.", "answer": 0, "state": "id", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 29648}
{"candidates": ["Decrease the distance you look ahead of your vehicle.", "Test your tires\u2019 traction while going uphill.", "Avoid making fast turns and fast stops."], "question": "How many different levels of coverage choices are there when selecting helmet?", "answer": 2, "state": "id", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 29649}
{"candidates": ["Motor homes or pickup trucks towing a boat trailer.", "Tank trucks marked with hazardous materials placards.", "Any vehicle with 3 or more axles or weighing more than 4,000 pounds."], "question": "Idaho law requires all motorcycles to have which of the following components?", "answer": 1, "state": "id", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 29680}
{"candidates": ["Slow to 25 MPH and pass cautiously.", "Stop, then proceed when you think all of the children have exited the bus.", "Stop as long as the red lights are flashing."], "question": "In order to swerve to the right, what order should you press your hand grips?", "answer": 2, "state": "id", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 29705}
{"candidates": ["Not less than 100 feet before turning.", "Not less than 75 feet before turning.", "Not less than 50 feet before turning."], "question": "For what distance should a continuous turn signal be given when making a left or right turn in a business or residential district?", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31177}
{"candidates": ["Overheated engine", "Static electricity", "Hot weather"], "question": "Which of the following can cause an explosive fire hazard when fueling your vehicle?", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31196}
{"candidates": ["4", "3", "5"], "question": "An immediate family member living in the same household as a disabled person may obtain how many sets of license plates if the disabled person doesn't own a car?", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31197}
{"candidates": ["Slow down before you enter the curve.", "Come to a complete stop before you enter the curve.", "Speed up before you enter the curve."], "question": "What does a driver need to do before approaching a curve?", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31198}
{"candidates": ["You should come to a complete stop until the vehicle is far ahead of you.", "You should increase your following distance.", "You should keep up with the vehicle closely."], "question": "What should you do when following a large vehicle?", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31199}
{"candidates": ["Yield to oncoming traffic and complete the turn.", "Make sure it is clear, then back up from the intersection.", "Wait in the intersection until the light turns green."], "question": "How should a driver proceed if within an intersection waiting to make a left turn and the traffic signal light turns red?", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31209}
{"candidates": ["400 feet", "500 feet", "250 feet"], "question": "Within how many feet is a driver required to dim the high beams before meeting another vehicle?", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31233}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "Reckless driving", "Driving under influence"], "question": "Which of the following are offenses in which your driver's license may be revoked?", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31288}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "Persons with disabilities with specific qualifications.", "Senior citizens."], "question": "Who is eligible for a reduced-fee license plate?", "answer": 2, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31289}
{"candidates": ["between 15 and 50 feet", "between 5 and 10 feet", "10 feet"], "question": "All vehicles are required to stop within how many feet of the nearest rail of a railroad crossing when a train is approaching?", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31297}
{"candidates": ["Walk on the right side of the highway.", "Stay away from the shoulder.", "Walk on the shoulder as far from the roadway as possible."], "question": "If a highway does not have a sidewalk but has a shoulder, pedestrians should always:", "answer": 2, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31350}
{"candidates": ["On school days between 7 a.m. and 4 p.m. when children are present and signs are posted.", "On weekends.", "Only during recess."], "question": "When must a driver slow down for a school zone?", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31358}
{"candidates": ["Green", "Red", "Vertically"], "question": "Driver's licenses for persons under age 21 are printed ____ with distinct features.", "answer": 2, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31410}
{"candidates": ["For 90 days", "For 60 days", "For 120 days"], "question": "How long is your out of state driver's license valid once you have moved permanently to Illinois?", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31437}
{"candidates": ["Drag or street racing", "Illegally transporting alcohol twice in 12 months by a person over age 21", "Three reckless driving offenses in 12 months"], "question": "An individual\u2019s driving privileges may be suspended under which of the following conditions?", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31472}
{"candidates": ["Driving privileges or vehicle registration suspension and a minimum $150 fine.", "$30 fine and 14-day suspension of driving privileges.", "60-day suspension of driving privileges."], "question": "What is the penalty for being convicted of illegally passing a stopped school bus?", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "permit", "id": 31479}
{"candidates": ["They are eliminated if you have one outside mirror on each side of the vehicle.", "Blind spots can be checked by looking in your rear view mirrors.", "Large trucks have bigger blind spots than most passenger vehicles."], "question": "When should you use your mirrors while riding a motorcycle?", "answer": 2, "state": "il", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 31610}
{"candidates": ["At or near the same speed as the traffic on the freeway.", "5 to 10 MPH slower than the traffic on the freeway.", "The posted speed limit for traffic on the freeway."], "question": "What do you call it when you turn your head to look for other vehicles.", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 31618}
{"candidates": ["Yield to pedestrians only in the intersection.", "Wait four seconds before proceeding.", "Yield to any vehicle, bicycle, or pedestrian in the intersection."], "question": "When you need to leave the road, you should do which of the following?", "answer": 2, "state": "il", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 31638}
{"candidates": ["You transport two or more young children in a passenger vehicle.", "You do not have room on the other side to completely cross the tracks.", "The railroad crossing is located in a city or town that has frequent train traffic."], "question": "When carrying passengers what are some of the things you should instruct the to do?", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 31642}
{"candidates": ["Slow to 25 MPH and pass cautiously.", "Stop as long as the red lights are flashing.", "Stop, then proceed when you think all of the children have exited the bus."], "question": "How heavy should a carried load be?", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 31644}
{"candidates": ["Carefully drive around the pedestrian.", "Make sure the pedestrian sees you, but continue driving.", "Stop and let the pedestrian cross the street."], "question": "How should you approach grooves and gratings?", "answer": 2, "state": "il", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 31646}
{"candidates": ["Traffic on the street moves to the right.", "Traffic on the street moves to the left.", "A sign permits the turn."], "question": "Which gear should you be in while you are stopped?", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 31673}
{"candidates": ["Should wait for the first two vehicles to pass, then drive into the lane.", "Need a large enough gap to get up to the speed of traffic.", "Should drive slower than other traffic for 200 feet."], "question": "When should you check the condition of your motorcycle?", "answer": 1, "state": "il", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 31708}
{"candidates": ["Stop before entering the right lane and let all other traffic go first.", "Signal and turn immediately.", "Slow down or stop, if necessary, and then make the turn."], "question": "What is keeping a distance from other driver's called?", "answer": 2, "state": "il", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 31729}
{"candidates": ["Both of the above.", "Leave a note on the vehicle.", "Report the accident without delay to the city police or, in unincorporated areas, to the CHP."], "question": "Which of the following is NOT required for a motorcycle to be street legal?", "answer": 0, "state": "il", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 31732}
{"candidates": ["A small heart", "A small water drop", "Nothing special"], "question": "If you become an organ donor, what will be printed on the front of your driver's license or identification card?", "answer": 0, "state": "in", "type": "permit", "id": 33197}
{"candidates": ["15", "13", "18"], "question": "What is the maximum length of any one vehicle size limitation for commercial vehicles without a special permit in feet?", "answer": 1, "state": "in", "type": "permit", "id": 33251}
{"candidates": ["6 points", "2 points", "4 points"], "question": "What is the point value for a speeding violation of speeding at least 35 mph over the speed limit?", "answer": 0, "state": "in", "type": "permit", "id": 33308}
{"candidates": ["200", "300", "250"], "question": "When changing lanes to prepare for a turn, do so at least ____ feet before the turn.", "answer": 0, "state": "in", "type": "permit", "id": 33310}
{"candidates": ["8.5 feet", "12 feet", "10.5 feet"], "question": "How many feet does a vehicle traveling at 35 mph travel in one second?", "answer": 2, "state": "in", "type": "permit", "id": 33341}
{"candidates": ["Motor homes or pickup trucks towing a boat trailer.", "Tank trucks marked with hazardous materials placards.", "Any vehicle with 3 or more axles or weighing more than 4,000 pounds."], "question": "Which of the following are good items to have in a winter survival kit, in the case you're stranded or otherwise need emergency items?", "answer": 1, "state": "in", "type": "permit", "id": 33370}
{"candidates": ["An Indiana resident who is at least 16 years of age and has held a valid driver\u2019s license for more than one year.", "An Indiana resident who is at least 18 years of age and has held a valid driver\u2019s license for more than one year.", "An Indiana resident who is at least 18 years of age and has held a valid driver\u2019s license for more than three years."], "question": "Who can be issued an Indiana Chauffeur's license?", "answer": 1, "state": "in", "type": "permit", "id": 33373}
{"candidates": ["All of the mentioned.", "Driving with the windows down on a cold night.", "Driving too slow and weaving."], "question": "Which of the following could be a sign of an impaired driver?", "answer": 1, "state": "in", "type": "permit", "id": 33398}
{"candidates": ["After you receive your driver's license.", "After passing the motorcycle knowledge exam.", "When you renew your license."], "question": "When are you allowed to add a motorcycle endorsement to a license in Indiana?", "answer": 1, "state": "in", "type": "permit", "id": 33425}
{"candidates": ["A non-SecureID driver's license or identification card indicates you have not provided the documentation necessary to validate your identity, lawful status, Social Security number, or Indiana residency.", "A non-SecureID driver's license or identification card indicates you have provided the documentation necessary to validate your identity, lawful status, Social Security number, or Indiana residency.", "A non-SecureID driver's license or identification card indicates you did not pass the DMV test to legally drive on the road."], "question": "What is a non-secureID?", "answer": 0, "state": "in", "type": "permit", "id": 33431}
{"candidates": ["Computer-generated bill from a utility company, credit card company, doctor, or hospital, issued within 60 days of the application date and containing your name and residential address.", "All the others.", "Bank statement or bank transcription receipt dated within 60 days of the application date and containing your name and residential address."], "question": "Which of the following is a document you can use to prove your Indiana residency?", "answer": 0, "state": "in", "type": "permit", "id": 33579}
{"candidates": ["A speed which matches the flow of traffic.", "A speed just below the posted speed limit.", "The posted speed limit."], "question": "What is the correct combination of signs and questions you may miss, as a maximum, to still pass the Indiana learner's permit or driver's license test?", "answer": 0, "state": "in", "type": "permit", "id": 33634}
{"candidates": ["It has met federal standards.", "It is more secure than what was previously issued.", "The owner has become a organ donor."], "question": "Indiana driver licenses feature a gold star to indicate what?", "answer": 0, "state": "in", "type": "permit", "id": 33637}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "Minimum Speed", "Do Not Enter"], "question": "Which of the following is an example of a traffic regulation sign?", "answer": 2, "state": "in", "type": "permit", "id": 33695}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "Renew by phone", "Renew by mail"], "question": "Which of the following options requires that you replace your credential at a license branch as opposed to being able to do it online?", "answer": 2, "state": "in", "type": "permit", "id": 33696}
{"candidates": ["Stop before entering the intersection as long as you can do so safely.", "Slow down and cross the intersection carefully.", "Stop. Yield to all cross traffic before crossing the intersection."], "question": "What helps you remind yourself of important components to check before you leave on a group ride?", "answer": 1, "state": "in", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 33750}
{"candidates": ["Parallel with the pavement.", "Turned to the right (away from the street).", "Turned to the left (toward the street)."], "question": "Riders who know what they are doing rarely ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "in", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 33754}
{"candidates": ["Signal for 100 feet before turning.", "Avoid driving in the bicycle lane.", "Move toward the left side of your lane."], "question": "If you see a larger animal such as an elk or bear, what should you do?", "answer": 0, "state": "in", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 33755}
{"candidates": ["Carefully drive around the pedestrian.", "Stop and let the pedestrian cross the street.", "Make sure the pedestrian sees you, but continue driving."], "question": "Most riders are riding slower than ____ mph when a crash occurs.", "answer": 1, "state": "in", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 33756}
{"candidates": ["A speed which matches the flow of traffic.", "A speed just below the posted speed limit.", "The posted speed limit."], "question": "Wearing some sort of ____ is recommended to prevent bugs, debris, and rocks from flying up and hitting the driver.", "answer": 0, "state": "in", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 33812}
{"candidates": ["Loading zone for freight or passengers.", "Loading zone for passengers or mail only.", "Loading zone for freight only."], "question": "A driver with a BAC level of over ____ is considered intoxicated and cannot operate a vehicle.", "answer": 1, "state": "in", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 33933}
{"candidates": ["Merge into another lane and try to go around the traffic.", "Enter the intersection and wait until traffic clears.", "Stay out of the intersection until traffic clears."], "question": "Riders must know how to brake and also ____ in order to avoid a crash.", "answer": 2, "state": "in", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 33965}
{"candidates": ["50", "100", "75"], "question": "Alcohol can enter the bloodstream within ____ of consumption.", "answer": 1, "state": "in", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 34021}
{"candidates": ["The truck driver to stop the vehicle.", "Other drivers when merging onto a freeway.", "Other drivers when they want to slow down."], "question": "How should the passenger sit while riding on a motorcycle with a sidecar?", "answer": 0, "state": "in", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 34025}
{"candidates": ["Assume the other driver will maintain a constant speed.", "Not assume the other driver will make space for you to return to your lane.", "Assume the other driver will let you pass if you use your turn signal."], "question": "If you are struck by a flying object while driving, you should do what?", "answer": 1, "state": "in", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 34026}
{"candidates": ["The lane closest to the left curb", "The lane in the center of the road.", "Any lane (as long as it is safe)"], "question": "What are the two primary skills that are important to avoiding a crash?", "answer": 0, "state": "in", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 34055}
{"candidates": ["Military Service License", "Commercial Driver\u2019s License", "Restricted Commercial Driver\u2019s License"], "question": "Which of the following is not a type of driver's license?", "answer": 0, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35484}
{"candidates": ["On the back of your license. ", "On the corner of your license. ", "On the face of your license. "], "question": "Where would the medical advance directive be located if the driver requests it?", "answer": 2, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35515}
{"candidates": ["300 feet", "200 feet", "100 feet"], "question": "In speed zones of 45 mph or less, you must signal your turn continuously during the last ____feet before turning.", "answer": 2, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35521}
{"candidates": ["Be ready to change your speed to the speed of traffic.", "Stay in the left lane and drive at the speed limit.", "Pass slow-moving vehicles on curves if they are slowing down."], "question": "Because there is often slow-moving traffic on county highways, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35555}
{"candidates": ["Education information", "Residency document", "Social Security number"], "question": "Which of the following information should you bring when getting your license number?", "answer": 2, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35575}
{"candidates": ["21", "26", "30"], "question": "What is the maximum age for a male that a driver's license application will serve as consent to be registered the United States Selective Service System?", "answer": 1, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35604}
{"candidates": ["keeps the brakes from freezing", "locks the front wheels causing loss of steering", "helps you stop sooner"], "question": "Continuous hard braking on ice and snow often:", "answer": 1, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35616}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "It is illegal in Iowa to drive with an open container of beer or any other alcoholic beverage.", "Open container law applies to both drivers and passengers."], "question": "Which of the following is true of the open container law in Iowa?", "answer": 0, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35663}
{"candidates": ["Use your high beams", "Use your low beams", "Slow down"], "question": "What is the most important part of your vehicle when driving in bad weather?", "answer": 2, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35719}
{"candidates": ["Drive side by side with the train.", "Stop and proceed only when the gates are raised and the lights have stopped flashing.", "Drive around the gates after stopping."], "question": "If the gates at a railroad crossing are down and red lights are flashing, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35735}
{"candidates": ["Yield right-of-way signs.", "Slow-moving vehicles.", "Dangerous intersections."], "question": "This symbol is used for:", "answer": 1, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35736}
{"candidates": ["The vehicle you are following has a slow-moving vehicle symbol.", "You are within 100 feet of an intersection or railroad crossing.", "You would be required to pass to the right of a left turning vehicle. - See more at:"], "question": "Passing is prohibited when:", "answer": 1, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35759}
{"candidates": ["Changing gears.", "Signaling to other motorists that the bus will soon be stopping to load or unload school children.", "Preparing to make a turn."], "question": "You see a school bus with flashing amber (yellow) lights. What is the bus driver doing?", "answer": 1, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35761}
{"candidates": ["Close to the right hand side of the road.", "Close to the center line.", "On the left of the center line."], "question": "When preparing to make a left turn from a two-way street, you should drive:", "answer": 1, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35783}
{"candidates": ["Turn your steering wheel to the right to correct the skid.", "Not turn your steering wheel until you are through skidding.", "Turn your steering wheel to the left to correct the skid."], "question": "If the rear of your vehicle is skidding to the left, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35813}
{"candidates": ["60 days", "90 days", "30 days"], "question": "How many days do you have to report an address change to the DOT?", "answer": 2, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35837}
{"candidates": ["A moving traffic violation", "Any accident", "An accident that has injury "], "question": "A moped permit will be canceled if you were involved in ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35866}
{"candidates": ["Equal to $50,000", "Equal to $65,000", "Equal to $55,000"], "question": "If you choose to file a surety bond as proof of fiscal responsibility, how much must the bond be for?", "answer": 2, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35870}
{"candidates": ["Stop and yield the right of way.", "Stop and wait for the green light.", "Slow and go with caution."], "question": "A flashing red light at an intersection means:", "answer": 0, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35876}
{"candidates": ["500 feet.", "300 feet.", "100 feet."], "question": "Headlights are required, day or night, when visibility is less than:", "answer": 0, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35882}
{"candidates": ["Amber lights flash at the top of the bus, the bus stops as red lights flash, a stop arm goes out and the door opens for the school children.", "The bus driver activates red flashing lights at the top of the bus, and then activates amber flashing lights when the children are unloaded or seated.", "The bus driver may do any sequence he or she desires."], "question": "Which is the correct sequence of events as a school bus driver prepares to stop to load or unload children?", "answer": 0, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35883}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "To improve balance, a drivers right arm can be draped over the back of the seat.", "To back up, turn to your right so you can see through the back window."], "question": "What should you do to check what is behind you while backing?", "answer": 2, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35928}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "An arrested driver may be asked to submit to a chemical test to determine the alcohol content in his/her blood.", "Refusal to submit to chemical testing will result in the driver's driving privileges being withdrawn."], "question": "According to the Iowa Implied Consent Law for both resident and nonresident drivers:", "answer": 0, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35935}
{"candidates": ["Make sure your vehicle is visible to drivers approaching from either direction.", "Park with your back-up lights on.", "Park 5 feet from the curb."], "question": "If you must park your vehicle in an area not usually used for parking:", "answer": 0, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 35966}
{"candidates": ["Any traffic on your immediate right inside the roundabout ", "Any vehicle leaving the roundabout", "Any vehicle entering the roundabout"], "question": "Who has the right of way in a roundabout?", "answer": 0, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 36044}
{"candidates": ["Lending their license to another individual", "Using a suspended, revoked, or terminated driver\u2019s license", "Surrender a license that\u2019s been suspended, revoked, or terminated"], "question": "Which of the following is not an unlawful use of your driver's license?", "answer": 1, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 36105}
{"candidates": ["100 feet", "150 feet", "300 feet"], "question": "How many feet ahead before a turn must you use your turn signal if the speed limit is greater than 45 mph?", "answer": 2, "state": "ia", "type": "permit", "id": 36133}
{"candidates": ["Keep your eyes moving to look for possible hazards.", "Look only at the car in front of you while driving.", "Always put one car length between you and the car ahead."], "question": "When is it okay to turn your headlight off when running?", "answer": 0, "state": "ia", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 36250}
{"candidates": ["Farther behind the truck than you would for a passenger vehicle.", "Closely behind the truck in bad weather because the driver can see farther ahead.", "No more than one car length behind the truck so the driver can see you."], "question": "What should you do if you are approached by a dog while riding your motorcycle?", "answer": 0, "state": "ia", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 36252}
{"candidates": ["A vehicle pulling two trailers.", "A 3-axle vehicle if the Gross Vehicle Weight is less than 6,000 pounds.", "Any 3-axle vehicle regardless of the weight."], "question": "If you are riding in a group, at what number should you divide into smaller groups?", "answer": 1, "state": "ia", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 36312}
{"candidates": ["The first rain after a dry spell.", "After it has been raining for awhile.", "During a heavy downpour."], "question": "Which of the following is an example of a slippery surface?", "answer": 0, "state": "ia", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 36314}
{"candidates": ["Stop, listen, and proceed cautiously.", "Look to the sides of your vehicle to see what is coming.", "Slowly pass vehicles that seem to be stopped for no reason."], "question": "Where should you position your knees to help balance your bike.", "answer": 1, "state": "ia", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 36402}
{"candidates": ["5 to 10 MPH slower than the traffic on the freeway.", "The posted speed limit for traffic on the freeway.", "At or near the same speed as the traffic on the freeway."], "question": "If your ride over a rain groove or bridge grate it may cause your bike to do what?", "answer": 2, "state": "ia", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 36460}
{"candidates": ["Any vehicle with 3 or more axles or weighing more than 4,000 pounds.", "Tank trucks marked with hazardous materials placards.", "Motor homes or pickup trucks towing a boat trailer."], "question": "Which two tests must you pass to obtain your motorcycle license?", "answer": 1, "state": "ia", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 36492}
{"candidates": ["Slowly pass vehicles that seem to be stopped for no reason.", "Look to the sides of your vehicle to see what is coming.", "Stop, listen, and proceed cautiously."], "question": "To be effective at protecting the motorcycle operator from hazards, proper face and eye protection must have which of the following attributes:", "answer": 1, "state": "ia", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 36549}
{"candidates": ["Fog lights only.", "High beams.", "Low beams."], "question": "What should you do to minimize your risks in regards to alcohol?", "answer": 2, "state": "ia", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 36643}
{"candidates": ["Slow down and use caution", "Speed up to scare them away", "Swerve to avoid the animal"], "question": "When approaching animals that are standing near the roadway:", "answer": 0, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38036}
{"candidates": ["Share a traffic lane with a vehicle", "Use the shoulder of a roadway", "Use a complete traffic lane"], "question": "Motorcycle operators have the right to:", "answer": 2, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38054}
{"candidates": ["From 5 a.m. to 9 p.m.", "From 6 a.m. to 10 p.m.", "From 5 a.m. to 8 p.m."], "question": "At age 16, the licensee may drive between which hours during the day?", "answer": 0, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38072}
{"candidates": ["Stop your vehicle on the roadway", "Check to make sure it is not too deep and then cross carefully", "Turn around and find another route to get to your destination"], "question": "If you see a flooded roadway ahead:", "answer": 2, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38090}
{"candidates": ["Kansas traffic laws and road signs", "Basic skills in operating a motor vehicle in traffic", "Vision test"], "question": "The written test contains questions about what?", "answer": 0, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38098}
{"candidates": ["Operate a motor vehicle when supervised by another driver over age of 21", "Observe another driver operate a motor vehicle", "Operate a motor vehicle without supervision"], "question": "An Instructional Permit allows you to:", "answer": 0, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38104}
{"candidates": ["Never expire", "Expire on your birthday", "Expire after five years of issuance"], "question": "Your Driver\u2019s License will:", "answer": 1, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38107}
{"candidates": ["May be more appropriate when towing or backing in tight areas", "Can be adjusted by leaning your head to the left/right until it touches the driver side window and the rear fender is just visible.", "Adds 12 to 16 degrees additional viewing area to each side of the vehicle."], "question": "The traditional mirror setting:", "answer": 0, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38139}
{"candidates": ["Red", "Green", "Yellow"], "question": "What colors are dangerous or unusual condition signs?", "answer": 2, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38158}
{"candidates": ["15 to 20 seconds", "10 to 15 seconds", "5 to 10 seconds"], "question": "On the highway, how many seconds are an appropriate distance to keep between your vehicle and the one in front?", "answer": 1, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38189}
{"candidates": ["Expect the child to be in total control of the bicycle", "Expect the unexpected", "Beep your horn"], "question": "If a bicycle rider near you is a child:", "answer": 1, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38196}
{"candidates": ["Make sure the parking brake is set", "Turn the low beam headlights on", "Place your foot on the accelerator"], "question": "Before you start the vehicle:", "answer": 0, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38205}
{"candidates": ["When pedestrians are crossing at a green light", "When pedestrians are using crosswalks and crossing at intersections", "Anytime when seeing a pedestrian"], "question": "When must drivers yield for pedestrians?", "answer": 1, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38216}
{"candidates": ["90%", "15%", "50%"], "question": "The impact of a crash is how much greater going 40 mph rather than 20 mph.", "answer": 0, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38217}
{"candidates": ["3 to 4 second gap in traffic", "2 to 3 second gap in traffic", "4 to 5 second gap in traffic"], "question": "When changing lanes identify a:", "answer": 2, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38223}
{"candidates": ["Lane change signs", "Warnings", "Traffic signals"], "question": "Diamond shaped serves as a sign that indicates:", "answer": 1, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38244}
{"candidates": ["Orange and white", "Orange and black", "Red and white"], "question": "What is the correct color combination for construction and maintenance signs in Kansas?", "answer": 1, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38277}
{"candidates": ["Red", "Green", "White"], "question": "What type of color is a sign that is providing directional information?", "answer": 1, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38278}
{"candidates": ["30 mph", "20 mph", "40 mph"], "question": "When you cannot see any farther than 100 feet ahead due to rain, snow, blowing dust, smoke or thick fog then you cannot safely drive faster than:", "answer": 0, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38289}
{"candidates": ["Pennant shaped", "Diamond shaped", "Triangle shaped"], "question": "What shape is a no passing zone sign?", "answer": 0, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38304}
{"candidates": ["Cannot see the vehicle directly to your right.", "Have passed the other vehicle\u2019s front bumper.", "See the vehicle\u2019s headlights in your rear view mirror."], "question": "Kansas law requires that you keep a safe distance between your vehicle and the vehicle in front of you. The Kansas Driver's Handbook suggests you follow what rule for measuring a safe following distance?", "answer": 2, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38334}
{"candidates": ["18", "21", "14"], "question": "If you are under ____, an instructional permit, farm permit, or driver's license cannot be issued to you unless your application is signed by your parent or guardian.", "answer": 2, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38338}
{"candidates": ["Press on the brake pedal repeatedly", "Gradually press on the brake pedal", "Press on the brake pedal as hard as you can"], "question": "If your vehicle has an anti-lock braking system and you need to stop quickly:", "answer": 2, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38341}
{"candidates": ["Must reside on a farm OR be employed for compensation on a farm", "All the others.", "A farm is at least 20 acres used in agricultural operations"], "question": "A farm permit requires what?", "answer": 0, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38457}
{"candidates": ["Stop in a safe parking area and then make the call", "Use a hands-free device so you can keep both hands on the steering wheel", "Carefully use your cell phone, but do not talk for a long time"], "question": "If you are driving and you need to use your cell phone it is best to:", "answer": 0, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38463}
{"candidates": ["Left hand between 10 and 11 o\u2019clock and right hand between 1 and 2 o\u2019clock", "Left hand between 7 and 8 o\u2019clock and right hand between 4 and 5 o\u2019clock", "Left hand between 9 and 10 o\u2019clock and right hand between 2 and 3 o\u2019clock"], "question": "Where should your hands be placed on the steering wheel when using hand-to-hand steering?", "answer": 1, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38464}
{"candidates": ["Operate vehicles with a gross vehicle weight rating of less than 26,001 pounds", "Operate vehicles with a gross vehicle weight rating of more than 26,001 pounds", "Operate any motor vehicle, regardless of size or weight"], "question": "With a Class C Driver\u2019s License you may:", "answer": 0, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38495}
{"candidates": ["The back seat", "In either the front or back seat", "The front seat"], "question": "Where should you place a child under 12 years old in a vehicle equipped with air bags?", "answer": 0, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38526}
{"candidates": ["Your wheels should be turned away from the curb", "Your wheels should be turned toward the curb", "Your wheels should face straight ahead"], "question": "When parking your vehicle facing uphill with a curb:", "answer": 0, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38528}
{"candidates": ["The driver to the left should be given the right-of-way", "The driver reaching the intersection first should be given the right-of-way", "The driver to the right should be given the right-of-way"], "question": "At a 4-way stop:", "answer": 1, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38556}
{"candidates": ["Do not need to be worn if your vehicle is equipped with air bags", "Only need to be worn when driving on long trips", "Must be worn at all times"], "question": "Safety belts:", "answer": 2, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38558}
{"candidates": ["Anytime.", "There is no need to stop for pedestrians.", "When pedestrians are on the crosswalk."], "question": "If there is no traffic controls in place, drivers must slow down or stop for pedestrians when?", "answer": 2, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38606}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "As you drive down the entrance ramp, alternate between checking your left side mirror and your blind spot to see if there are other vehicles approaching in the right lane of the interstate. ", "Merge left from the entrance ramp into the right lane."], "question": "Which of the following should you do when leaving the interstate?", "answer": 2, "state": "ks", "type": "permit", "id": 38632}
{"candidates": ["Interior lights", "Headlights.", "Parking lights"], "question": "You should use your mirrors ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "ks", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 38689}
{"candidates": ["Increase your chances of an accident.", "Help prevent traffic congestion.", "Get you to your destination much faster and safer."], "question": "When a vehicle is merging into your lane, what actions should you take to avoid a hazardous situation?", "answer": 0, "state": "ks", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 38690}
{"candidates": ["During rush hour traffic.", "When you entered the intersection on the green light.", "Under no circumstances."], "question": "At what size should you consider dividing your group into two or more smaller ones?", "answer": 2, "state": "ks", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 38720}
{"candidates": ["Loading zone for passengers or mail only.", "Loading zone for freight or passengers.", "Loading zone for freight only."], "question": "How should you react if you get struck by a flying object?", "answer": 0, "state": "ks", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 38721}
{"candidates": ["At all times.", "Unless they conflict with existing signs, signals, or laws.", "Only if you see orange cones on the road ahead."], "question": "When an engine locks up or \"freezes\" it is called and \"engine seizure\" and it can cause a motorcycle operator to lose control of the vehicle. What procedure should a motorcycle operator do when an engine is showing symptoms of seizing up?", "answer": 0, "state": "ks", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 38810}
{"candidates": ["Yes, it is a good defensive driving technique.", "No, you can block traffic when you drive too slowly.", "Yes, it is always safer than driving faster than other traffic."], "question": "In what position should you stay whenever you are passing parked cars?", "answer": 1, "state": "ks", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 38813}
{"candidates": ["Stop and let him/her finish crossing the street.", "Make eye contact and then pass him/her.", "Slow down as you pass him/her."], "question": "Each year, ____ motorcyclists are killed.", "answer": 0, "state": "ks", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 38842}
{"candidates": ["Use hands-free devices so you can keep both hands on the steering wheel.", "Keep your phone within easy reach so you won't need to take your eyes off the road.", "Review the number before answering a call."], "question": "When you are stopped, you should keep the motorcycle in ____ gear.", "answer": 0, "state": "ks", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 38935}
{"candidates": ["Make eye contact and then pass him/her.", "Stop and let him/her finish crossing the street.", "Slow down as you pass him/her."], "question": "According to the manual what do drugs and alcohol do to you to make you a less cautious and non-attentive driver.", "answer": 1, "state": "ks", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 38993}
{"candidates": ["Any 3-axle vehicle regardless of the weight.", "A vehicle pulling two trailers.", "A 3-axle vehicle if the Gross Vehicle Weight is less than 6,000 pounds."], "question": "In order to help with the effects of fatigue, riders should rest at least every ____ hours.", "answer": 2, "state": "ks", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 39019}
{"candidates": ["15 to 20 seconds", "10 to 15 seconds", "5 to 10 seconds"], "question": "More than ____ of motorcycle/car crashes happen because the car enters the motorcycle's right of way.", "answer": 1, "state": "ks", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 39050}
{"candidates": ["Merge into another lane and try to go around the traffic.", "Stay out of the intersection until traffic clears.", "Enter the intersection and wait until traffic clears."], "question": "You should use ____ brake(s) on slippery surfaces.", "answer": 1, "state": "ks", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 39079}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "Debris in the roadway", "Railroad crossings"], "question": "Which of the following is a hazard to motorcycles?", "answer": 2, "state": "ky", "type": "permit", "id": 40541}
{"candidates": ["Class M", "Class C", "Class D"], "question": "Commercial driver's must hold what class of license?", "answer": 1, "state": "ky", "type": "permit", "id": 40570}
{"candidates": ["Keep at least a wheel length between your front wheel and the back wheel in front. ", "Keep at least two wheels length between your front wheel and the back wheel in front. ", "Keep at least a car length between your front wheel and the back wheel in front. "], "question": "How should you position yourself when riding in a group.", "answer": 0, "state": "ky", "type": "permit", "id": 40571}
{"candidates": ["50", "100", "75"], "question": "All intermediate drivers are required to complete and pass a safety class, how long does this class last.", "answer": 1, "state": "ky", "type": "permit", "id": 40632}
{"candidates": ["Sell or transfer your vehicle.", "Fail a smog test for your vehicle.", "Get a new prescription for lenses or contacts."], "question": "Questions regarding organ donation can be resolved by contacting who?", "answer": 0, "state": "ky", "type": "permit", "id": 40660}
{"candidates": ["Hexagon", "Circular", "Diamond"], "question": "Which of the following is not a standard sign shape?", "answer": 1, "state": "ky", "type": "permit", "id": 40686}
{"candidates": ["Fail a smog test for your vehicle.", "Get a new prescription for lenses or contacts.", "Sell or transfer your vehicle."], "question": "A motorcycle driver must ____ during the performance test.", "answer": 2, "state": "ky", "type": "permit", "id": 40747}
{"candidates": ["Letting go of your brakes.", "Letting go of the steering wheel.", "Pressing your head firmly against the head restraint."], "question": "If you are going to be hit from behind what should you do?", "answer": 2, "state": "ky", "type": "permit", "id": 40748}
{"candidates": ["White", "Orange", "Red"], "question": "What color is used on signs to convey construction or maintenance?", "answer": 1, "state": "ky", "type": "permit", "id": 40774}
{"candidates": ["below 15 mph", "below 25 mph", "below 20 mph"], "question": "A vehicle going ____ is a slow moving vehicle and is required to display a slow-moving emblem on the back of the vehicle.", "answer": 1, "state": "ky", "type": "permit", "id": 40803}
{"candidates": ["Unless you are in a limousine.", "When the vehicle is equipped with seat belts.", "Unless the vehicle was built before 1978."], "question": "If you are under 18 and the parent who signed your driving permit application withdraws his or her responsibility, you must wait until you are ____ years old before getting a drivers permit or license.", "answer": 1, "state": "ky", "type": "permit", "id": 40805}
{"candidates": ["3", "2", "4"], "question": "When merging with other traffic, you must allow a space of ____ seconds.", "answer": 2, "state": "ky", "type": "permit", "id": 40894}
{"candidates": ["Must merge into the bicycle lane before turning.", "Should only merge into the bicycle lane if you stop before turning.", "May not enter the bicycle lane."], "question": "Which of the following actions are sometimes necessary to avoid a collision?", "answer": 0, "state": "ky", "type": "permit", "id": 40978}
{"candidates": ["Operating a truck with a GVWR of 26,001 pounds or more", "Any size vehicle with advertising", "Operating a vehicle designed to transport 16 or more passengers, including the driver"], "question": "Which of the following does not need a CDL?", "answer": 1, "state": "ky", "type": "permit", "id": 41097}
{"candidates": ["His/Her local Department of Transportation Field Office", "His/Her local Circuit Court Clerk\u2019s Office", "His/Her local DMV Office"], "question": "A non U.S. citizen with a permanent resident card can apply for a drivers license where?", "answer": 1, "state": "ky", "type": "permit", "id": 41101}
{"candidates": ["Driving too slow.", "Approaching you from behind.", "You have already passed."], "question": "Just like any other vehicle, a motorcycle is not permitted to pass another vehicle ____ if driving on a two-lane road.", "answer": 1, "state": "ky", "type": "permit", "id": 41130}
{"candidates": ["Under no circumstances", "If the shoulder is wide enough to accommodate your vehicle", "If the vehicle ahead of you is turning left."], "question": "Over ____ percent of motorcycle/car crashes occur at intersections.", "answer": 0, "state": "ky", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 41218}
{"candidates": ["70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic.", "No faster than 65 mph.", "Between 65 mph and 70 mph."], "question": "It is important to keep at least a ____ second following distance from the vehicle in front of you.", "answer": 1, "state": "ky", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 41219}
{"candidates": ["Any 3-axle vehicle regardless of the weight.", "A vehicle pulling two trailers.", "A 3-axle vehicle if the Gross Vehicle Weight is less than 6,000 pounds."], "question": "If you are in traffic and a small animal runs in front of your vehicle, what is the safest way to handle the situation?", "answer": 2, "state": "ky", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 41276}
{"candidates": ["You do not have room on the other side to completely cross the tracks.", "The railroad crossing is located in a city or town that has frequent train traffic.", "You transport two or more young children in a passenger vehicle."], "question": "Which of the following are not eligible required permits to enroll in a motorcycle safety education program?", "answer": 0, "state": "ky", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 41309}
{"candidates": ["Change lanes and maintain your current speed.", "Be prepared for workers and equipment ahead.", "Slow down because the lane ends ahead."], "question": "Distance around your motorcycle gives you which of the following?", "answer": 1, "state": "ky", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 41339}
{"candidates": ["Within the distance you can see ahead.", "Within 5-10 seconds.", "Within the distance lighted by your parking lights."], "question": "To prevent fatigue, even the most experienced drivers try not to ride for more than ____ hours in a day.", "answer": 0, "state": "ky", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 41490}
{"candidates": ["No faster than 65 mph.", "70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic.", "Between 65 mph and 70 mph."], "question": "What is the maximum BAC level a person under the age of 21 may have and still drive?", "answer": 0, "state": "ky", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 41581}
{"candidates": ["Headlights.", "Parking lights", "Interior lights"], "question": "Experienced riders tend to limit themselves to ____ hours of riding.", "answer": 0, "state": "ky", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 41698}
{"candidates": ["About 100 years old", "About 20 years old", "About 50 years old"], "question": "How old is the Highway Transportation System?", "answer": 0, "state": "la", "type": "permit", "id": 43155}
{"candidates": ["Decrease your following distance.", "Slow down to watch the workers.", "Pass the construction zone carefully and not rubberneck."], "question": "Which of the following is NOT a way to prevent vehicle theft?", "answer": 2, "state": "la", "type": "permit", "id": 43186}
{"candidates": ["Up to four seconds", "Up to five seconds", "Up to three seconds"], "question": "How much distance should you give when following behind a motorcycle?", "answer": 0, "state": "la", "type": "permit", "id": 43244}
{"candidates": ["Predict which hazards could potentially come into conflict with you", "All the others.", "Sweep, Search, and Scan"], "question": "What does the SIPDE technique teach drivers?", "answer": 2, "state": "la", "type": "permit", "id": 43274}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "Walk or bike when you can.", "Take public transit when possible."], "question": "What can you do to cut down on driving?", "answer": 1, "state": "la", "type": "permit", "id": 43275}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "Allow more space between the trailer and curb. ", "Avoid lingering in blind spots."], "question": "How should you be careful when sharing the road with big trucks?", "answer": 2, "state": "la", "type": "permit", "id": 43301}
{"candidates": ["Both are true.", "Reduces the ability to judge speeds, distances and angles.", "Encourages the driver to take foolish risks and break laws."], "question": "Which of the following is true about how alcohol affects your body?", "answer": 1, "state": "la", "type": "permit", "id": 43362}
{"candidates": ["Look only at the car in front of you while driving.", "Always put one car length between you and the car ahead.", "Keep your eyes moving to look for possible hazards."], "question": "Which of the following can extend the life of your vehicle when you plan trips?", "answer": 2, "state": "la", "type": "permit", "id": 43390}
{"candidates": ["Keep your eyes moving to look for possible hazards.", "Look only at the car in front of you while driving.", "Always put one car length between you and the car ahead."], "question": "Which of the following can inhibit your ability to be a safe driver while you are ill?", "answer": 0, "state": "la", "type": "permit", "id": 43392}
{"candidates": ["You can frustrate the other drivers and make them angry.", "You help reduce traffic congestion.", "Your actions cannot result in a traffic citation."], "question": "What is a hazard of interstate driving?", "answer": 0, "state": "la", "type": "permit", "id": 43540}
{"candidates": ["A child of 5 years old", "A child of 8 years old", "A child of 14 years old"], "question": "Which of the following child can legally ride in the front passenger seat equipped with an airbag?", "answer": 2, "state": "la", "type": "permit", "id": 43595}
{"candidates": ["During rush hour traffic if there are no bicyclists in the bike lane.", "When you want to pass a driver ahead of you who is turning right.", "When you are within 200 feet of a cross street where you plan to turn right."], "question": "How can dust on gravel roads impair your driving?", "answer": 2, "state": "la", "type": "permit", "id": 43598}
{"candidates": ["Solid double white lines", "Solid single white line", "Broken white lines"], "question": "What type of white line can you never cross on a roadway?", "answer": 0, "state": "la", "type": "permit", "id": 43626}
{"candidates": ["At least 30 feet but not more than 100 feet from the nearest track", "A maximum of 50 feet and a minimum of 15 feet from the nearest railroad track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 50 feet from the nearest track"], "question": "In what position should the seat of the motorcycle be?", "answer": 1, "state": "la", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 43743}
{"candidates": ["At least 30 feet but not more than 50 feet from the nearest track", "A maximum of 50 feet and a minimum of 15 feet from the nearest railroad track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 100 feet from the nearest track"], "question": "What should you when riding with passengers?", "answer": 1, "state": "la", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 43745}
{"candidates": ["100", "50", "75"], "question": "Which of the following should your lane position not help you do?", "answer": 0, "state": "la", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 43778}
{"candidates": ["Next to the solid line may pass.", "Next to the broken line may pass.", "In both directions may pass."], "question": "Which of the following should you not do when you get a new motorcycle?", "answer": 1, "state": "la", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 43833}
{"candidates": ["The posted speed limit.", "A speed just below the posted speed limit.", "A speed which matches the flow of traffic."], "question": "What percentage is closest to the amount of motorcycle crashes that result in neck and head injuries?", "answer": 2, "state": "la", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 43896}
{"candidates": ["In an unmarked crosswalk", "Within three feet of a private driveway.", "In a bicycle lane."], "question": "When should you brake while swerving?", "answer": 0, "state": "la", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 43898}
{"candidates": ["The posted speed limit for traffic on the freeway.", "At or near the same speed as the traffic on the freeway.", "5 to 10 MPH slower than the traffic on the freeway."], "question": "Which of the following is not recommended when passing parked cars?", "answer": 1, "state": "la", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 43925}
{"candidates": ["Within three feet of a private driveway.", "In an unmarked crosswalk", "In a bicycle lane."], "question": "When braking, what is a common mistake that results in more frequent crashes?", "answer": 1, "state": "la", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 44015}
{"candidates": ["Use the shoulder of the main road to get up to the speed of the traffic", "Enter the far right traffic lane and speed up to the flow of traffic", "Speed up on the entrance only after you have found a gap in traffic"], "question": "When on a short entrance to an interstate where there is no merge area or lane:", "answer": 2, "state": "me", "type": "permit", "id": 45556}
{"candidates": ["Push the brake pedal hard.", "If the car begins to skid, quickly let up on the brake. Then quickly push it down again.", "Press the back of your head firmly against the head restraint."], "question": "Which of the following is not recommended when making quick stops?", "answer": 0, "state": "me", "type": "permit", "id": 45744}
{"candidates": ["Stop, then inch forward until you can see clearly in both directions", "Maintain speed and look both ways", "Slow down and look both ways"], "question": "If you come to an intersection and your view to the side is blocked, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "me", "type": "permit", "id": 45750}
{"candidates": ["Catalytic converter is clogged or missing.", "All the others.", "Malfunctioning oxygen sensor."], "question": "What would cause a vehicle to fail an inspection?", "answer": 2, "state": "me", "type": "permit", "id": 45770}
{"candidates": ["Two to four times", "Three to four times", "Three to six times"], "question": "Whenever you wear a lap belt and a shoulder strap the chances of surviving a car crash increase how many times?", "answer": 1, "state": "me", "type": "permit", "id": 45801}
{"candidates": ["Keep it locked until you have come to a complete stop.", "Maintain pressure on the rear brake pedal and keep your knees against the tank and your eyes up.", "All the others."], "question": "If your rear wheel locks, what should you do?", "answer": 0, "state": "me", "type": "permit", "id": 45863}
{"candidates": ["A title is a proof of obtaining our first driver\u2019s license.", "A title is a warning issued by the Secretary of State.", "A title is a legal document which identifies ownership of a motor vehicle."], "question": "What is a title?", "answer": 2, "state": "me", "type": "permit", "id": 45923}
{"candidates": ["25 mph", "30 mph", "20 mph"], "question": "What is a safe speed?", "answer": 0, "state": "me", "type": "permit", "id": 45982}
{"candidates": ["Stay in a vehicle\u2019s tire tracks\u2014the center of the lane can be the most dangerous area of the road.", "All the others.", "Avoid sudden moves."], "question": "Which of the following should you do to handle slippery surfaces on a motorcycle?", "answer": 2, "state": "me", "type": "permit", "id": 46189}
{"candidates": ["$24.00 per $1000 of MSRP", "$25.00 per $1000 of MSRP", "$28.00 per $1000 of MSRP"], "question": "What is the registration fee for a motor vehicle in Maine?", "answer": 1, "state": "me", "type": "permit", "id": 46216}
{"candidates": ["No Passing Zone", "Railroad crossing", "Pedestrian crossing"], "question": "The sign shown means:", "answer": 1, "state": "me", "type": "permit", "id": 46223}
{"candidates": ["Three feet", "Four feet", "Five feet"], "question": "When passing a bicyclist, at least how much room should you give?", "answer": 0, "state": "me", "type": "permit", "id": 46397}
{"candidates": ["The posted speed limit.", "A speed just below the posted speed limit.", "A speed which matches the flow of traffic."], "question": "You will travel a minimum of ____ in 10 to 12 seconds at highway speeds.", "answer": 2, "state": "me", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 46576}
{"candidates": ["Signal for 100 feet before turning.", "Avoid driving in the bicycle lane.", "Move toward the left side of your lane."], "question": "Which of the following is true of driving in fog?", "answer": 0, "state": "me", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 46607}
{"candidates": ["Loading zone for passengers or mail only.", "Loading zone for freight only.", "Loading zone for freight or passengers."], "question": "If your gas pedal becomes stuck or jammed, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "me", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 46907}
{"candidates": ["Parallel with the pavement.", "Turned to the left (toward the street).", "Turned to the right (away from the street)."], "question": "At highway speeds, how far away must oncoming cars be to safely pass on a two-lane road?", "answer": 2, "state": "me", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 46967}
{"candidates": ["Slowly pass vehicles that seem to be stopped for no reason.", "Look to the sides of your vehicle to see what is coming.", "Stop, listen, and proceed cautiously."], "question": "What is a good way to see if you are following a large vehicle too closely?", "answer": 1, "state": "me", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 47027}
{"candidates": ["16", "8", "13"], "question": "Any individual under the age of ____ is required by law to wear a seat belt or be restrained in a child safety seat, regardless of seating position.", "answer": 2, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48523}
{"candidates": ["Refuses to submit to a test to determine BAC", "Fails to meet the attendance requirement for school", "Refuses to use a false ID to purchase alcohol"], "question": "MVA will suspend the license of any driver who:", "answer": 0, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48527}
{"candidates": ["The vehicle is traveling 25 mph or less", "The vehicle is being drawn by an animal", "The vehicle makes sudden stops"], "question": "When displayed on the rear of a vehicle, the sign shown indicates:", "answer": 0, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48545}
{"candidates": ["They are located every mile on interstate roadways.", "All the others.", "They serve as a location point for drivers when they need assistance."], "question": "What are mile marker signs?", "answer": 2, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48574}
{"candidates": ["Your front wheels be turned toward the street.", "As vehicle speed increases and the amount of water on the roadway increases, vehicles tend to ride on a cushion of water and the tires lose contact with the road.", "The grip between the tires and the road surface that allows a vehicle to start, stop and/or change direction."], "question": "What is \"hydroplaning?\"", "answer": 1, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48635}
{"candidates": ["Anything that takes your attention away from driving", "Anything that causes you to pay more attention to driving", "Anything that causes evasive action while driving"], "question": "Distracted driving is:", "answer": 0, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48648}
{"candidates": ["Do not use your turn signal until the vehicle has moved onto the deceleration lane", "Do not slow down until your vehicle has moved onto the deceleration lane", "Do not follow the posted warning speeds unless the roadway is slippery"], "question": "When using a deceleration lane to exit a roadway:", "answer": 1, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48732}
{"candidates": ["40 feet", "20 feet", "30 feet"], "question": "How many feet must you stop from the front or back of a school bus when their alternating red lights are flashing?", "answer": 1, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48751}
{"candidates": ["May not pass that vehicle", "Should go around the vehicle if it seems safe", "May not yield to any pedestrians at the crosswalk"], "question": "If you come up behind a vehicle stopped at a crosswalk, you:", "answer": 0, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48764}
{"candidates": ["The lane to the right may pass", "Both lanes may pass", "Neither lane may pass"], "question": "Double solid yellow lane markings mean that:", "answer": 2, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48791}
{"candidates": ["Pull off the road, turn on your emergency flashers and stay in your vehicle if you can", "Get out of the vehicle and flag down the first vehicle that passes", "Blow the horn at passing cars to get their attention"], "question": "If it is necessary to make an emergency stop while driving on an interstate, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48792}
{"candidates": ["Submitting to a chemical test to determine BAC", "Submitting to a physical examination before licensure", "Submitting to a field sobriety test to determine impairment"], "question": "As it relates to your driver's license, implied consent means:", "answer": 0, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48794}
{"candidates": ["Have headlights turned on and hazard lights flashing", "Have turning signals turned on", "Sound their horns"], "question": "What must vehicles do to be granted right-of-way in a funeral procession?", "answer": 0, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48811}
{"candidates": ["Must pass a funeral procession on the right on a multiple lane highway", "Must yield the right-of-way to any vehicles in the funeral procession", "May drive between the vehicles moving in the funeral procession"], "question": "If you see a funeral procession you:", "answer": 1, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48827}
{"candidates": ["Always be prepared to yield the right of way", "Assume most drivers obey the right of way rules", "Assume all drivers automatically obey the right of way rules"], "question": "A driver should:", "answer": 0, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48829}
{"candidates": ["0.06", "0.08", "0.02"], "question": "MVA will suspend the license of any driver with a BAC test result of:", "answer": 1, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48845}
{"candidates": ["Slow down and let it pass", "Increase your speed to get around the incident quickly", "Move to the far lane and slow down to a safe speed"], "question": "If you approach a stopped emergency vehicle using its visual signals:", "answer": 2, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48856}
{"candidates": ["Stop and proceed only when clear", "Come to a complete stop as quickly as possible", "Slow down and proceed with caution"], "question": "The flashing yellow light at an intersection means you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48876}
{"candidates": ["Slowly pass vehicles that seem to be stopped for no reason.", "Look to the sides of your vehicle to see what is coming.", "Stop, listen, and proceed cautiously."], "question": "On a 2-way-2-lane roadway, where travel is going in the same direction, what does a separation of lines that indicates it is acceptable to pass or change lanes look like?", "answer": 1, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48894}
{"candidates": ["New noncommercial driver\u2019s license applicants under 21.", "All new noncommercial driver\u2019s license applicants, regardless of age.", "New noncommercial driver\u2019s license applicants under 18."], "question": "Who does the Rookie Driver/Graduated Driver Licensing System (GLS) apply to?", "answer": 1, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48897}
{"candidates": ["Above your vehicle windows", "Above the normal warning signs", "Above the roadway"], "question": "Where are overhead lane use signs posted?", "answer": 2, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48926}
{"candidates": ["Legal if the driver is 21 years of age or older", "Permitted when driving at a slow speed", "Not legal"], "question": "Texting while driving a motor vehicle is:", "answer": 2, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48936}
{"candidates": ["You must know what is happening around your vehicle.", "Adjust your speed, position, and direction to respond to roadway conditions, enhance vehicle control, and increase response time.", "All the others."], "question": "Which of the following is not a good practice to follow for defensive driving?", "answer": 0, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 48958}
{"candidates": ["They will face possible imprisonment.", "Their driver's license will be taken away.", "They need to pay a double fine."], "question": "What can happen to someone under age 21 who is driving after drinking?", "answer": 1, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 49042}
{"candidates": ["Requirement", "Right", "Privilege"], "question": "Having a driver's license is a:", "answer": 2, "state": "md", "type": "permit", "id": 49076}
{"candidates": ["Motor homes or pickup trucks towing a boat trailer.", "Any vehicle with 3 or more axles or weighing more than 4,000 pounds.", "Tank trucks marked with hazardous materials placards."], "question": "How long does it take for alcohol to start affecting the drinker?", "answer": 2, "state": "md", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 49251}
{"candidates": ["Turned to the left (toward the street).", "Turned to the right (away from the street).", "Parallel with the pavement."], "question": "When crossing a rain groove, you should cross how?", "answer": 1, "state": "md", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 49282}
{"candidates": ["One lane of traffic is traveling faster than the other lanes.", "All vehicles are traveling about the same speed.", "One vehicle is traveling faster or slower than the flow of traffic."], "question": "You should park at a roadside at what angle?", "answer": 2, "state": "md", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 49312}
{"candidates": ["Loading zone for freight or passengers.", "Loading zone for freight only.", "Loading zone for passengers or mail only."], "question": "An engine seizure is normally caused by what?", "answer": 2, "state": "md", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 49433}
{"candidates": ["As long as someone is under the legal alcohol limit, it is safe to drive.", "It takes at least 2 drinks before driving is impaired.", "If under 21, it is illegal to drive with any measurable amount of alcohol in one\u2019s blood system."], "question": "Which of the following is true about alcohol and driving?", "answer": 0, "state": "ma", "type": "permit", "id": 51008}
{"candidates": ["20 mph, 25 mph", "25 mph, 30 mph", "15 mph, 25 mph"], "question": "What is the minimum speed and maximum speed of a low speed vehicle?", "answer": 0, "state": "ma", "type": "permit", "id": 51067}
{"candidates": ["Yell or use obscene gestures at other drivers.", "All the others.", "Drive over the speed limit or try to beat red lights."], "question": "What are some signs of an aggressive driver?", "answer": 2, "state": "ma", "type": "permit", "id": 51155}
{"candidates": ["Change lanes and maintain your current speed.", "Be prepared for workers and equipment ahead.", "Slow down because the lane ends ahead."], "question": "All the insurance rates must be approved by whom before the insurance company is able to sell the insurance?", "answer": 1, "state": "ma", "type": "permit", "id": 51187}
{"candidates": ["50 feet", "200 feet", "100 feet"], "question": "A person can be eligible for disability plates and placards if they are unable to walk what distance without stopping and resting?", "answer": 1, "state": "ma", "type": "permit", "id": 51214}
{"candidates": ["$1000", "$1800", "$1500"], "question": "A driver is classified as 50% or more at fault by their insurance if the damage caused was more than what amount?", "answer": 0, "state": "ma", "type": "permit", "id": 51269}
{"candidates": ["White Cane Law", "Seat Belt Law", "Move Over Law"], "question": "What is the name of the law that requires you to be cautious\nand reduce your speed when you approach a stationary emergency vehicle with flashing lights?", "answer": 2, "state": "ma", "type": "permit", "id": 51323}
{"candidates": ["When pulling over.", "All the others.", "When making a turn."], "question": "When does a driver need to signal?", "answer": 2, "state": "ma", "type": "permit", "id": 51324}
{"candidates": ["1 year", "3 years", "2 years"], "question": "Newly registered vehicles are issued how many license plates?", "answer": 2, "state": "ma", "type": "permit", "id": 51326}
{"candidates": ["2,500", "3,500", "4,900"], "question": "Trailers that are used in commerce and have a gross vehicle weight of ____ pounds are not required for an inspection.", "answer": 0, "state": "ma", "type": "permit", "id": 51381}
{"candidates": ["Within 14 days", "Within 7 days", "Within 8 days"], "question": "Within how many days of registration after the purchase of a motor vehicle or motorcycle must you have it inspected?", "answer": 1, "state": "ma", "type": "permit", "id": 51382}
{"candidates": ["Avoid crashes.", "All the others.", "Warn pedestrians or other drivers of possible trouble."], "question": "What should you use your horn for?", "answer": 2, "state": "ma", "type": "permit", "id": 51440}
{"candidates": ["That vehicles may pass in all directions.", "That only vehicles next to the broken line may pass.", "That vehicles next to the solid yellow line may pass."], "question": "Slow-moving vehicles usually have a ____ color sign on the back of it.", "answer": 1, "state": "ma", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 51559}
{"candidates": ["Stop before entering the right lane and let all other traffic go first.", "Slow down or stop, if necessary, and then make the turn.", "Signal and turn immediately."], "question": "A rider must gain gear selection experience when:", "answer": 1, "state": "ma", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 51589}
{"candidates": ["Transporting an unrestrained animal inside the vehicle.", "Listening to music through headphones that cover both ears", "Adjusting your outside mirrors."], "question": "When riding over rain grooves or metal bridge gratings, the motorcyclist should ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "ma", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 51646}
{"candidates": ["You help reduce traffic congestion.", "You can frustrate the other drivers and make them angry.", "Your actions cannot result in a traffic citation."], "question": "An applicant must be ____ years old in order to obtain a learner's permit.", "answer": 1, "state": "ma", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 51679}
{"candidates": ["Parallel with the pavement.", "Turned to the left (toward the street).", "Turned to the right (away from the street)."], "question": "You may park in a permit only zone if:", "answer": 2, "state": "ma", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 51707}
{"candidates": ["Assume the other driver will maintain a constant speed.", "Not assume the other driver will make space for you to return to your lane.", "Assume the other driver will let you pass if you use your turn signal."], "question": "When carrying a passenger you need to take into account:", "answer": 1, "state": "ma", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 51737}
{"candidates": ["The truck driver to stop the vehicle.", "Other drivers when they want to slow down.", "Other drivers when merging onto a freeway."], "question": "When riding near parked vehicles, you should ride on the ____ side of your lane.", "answer": 0, "state": "ma", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 51769}
{"candidates": ["Stop, then proceed when you think all of the children have exited the bus.", "Slow to 25 MPH and pass cautiously.", "Stop as long as the red lights are flashing."], "question": "Which of the following is the correct method for a motorcycle operator when encountering a funeral procession?", "answer": 2, "state": "ma", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 51825}
{"candidates": ["Both of the above.", "Leave a note on the vehicle.", "Report the accident without delay to the city police or, in unincorporated areas, to the CHP."], "question": "One advantage of a motorcycle rider is:", "answer": 0, "state": "ma", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 51856}
{"candidates": ["If there is property damage in excess of $750 or if there are any injuries.", "Only if you or the other driver is injured.", "Only if you are at fault."], "question": "A limited use vehicle is restricted from going faster than ____ mph.", "answer": 0, "state": "ma", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 51921}
{"candidates": ["Sell or transfer your vehicle.", "Fail a smog test for your vehicle.", "Get a new prescription for lenses or contacts."], "question": "The speed limit in a school zone is ____ mph.", "answer": 0, "state": "ma", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 51922}
{"candidates": ["The other side of the road is a broken line.", "The other side of the road is a solid line.", "Your side of the road is a broken line."], "question": "The first offense for operating under the influence gives you a ____ year(s) license suspension.", "answer": 2, "state": "ma", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 51952}
{"candidates": ["Stop before entering the intersection and let all other traffic go first.", "Slow down or stop, only if necessary.", "Stop, then proceed when safe."], "question": "If your engine seizes, it's most likely due to:", "answer": 2, "state": "ma", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 51979}
{"candidates": ["Germany", "Mexico", "Canada"], "question": "A licensed driver from which of the following countries would be required to take the driving skills test?", "answer": 2, "state": "mi", "type": "permit", "id": 53409}
{"candidates": ["Anti-Lock Braking System.", "Abdominal muscles.", "Asset-backed security."], "question": "What is the braking method that is used by releasing pressure and applying the brakes again when the wheels lock in a vehicle without antilock brakes called?", "answer": 0, "state": "mi", "type": "permit", "id": 53458}
{"candidates": ["Stop, and cannot move until the signal changes.", "Come to a full stop, then proceed when the road is clear.", "Proceed with caution."], "question": "What should drivers do at a signal showing a flashing red light?", "answer": 1, "state": "mi", "type": "permit", "id": 53512}
{"candidates": ["8", "6", "4"], "question": "How many points is assessed to your driving record for operating while visibly impaired on your first offense?", "answer": 2, "state": "mi", "type": "permit", "id": 53516}
{"candidates": ["The day it released", "On your 21st birthday", "The day after your 21st birthday"], "question": "If you are under 21, when does your driver's license expire?", "answer": 1, "state": "mi", "type": "permit", "id": 53567}
{"candidates": ["5", "4", "6"], "question": "Under Michigan law, it is illegal to leave children less than ____ unattended in a motor vehicle if the amount of time or circumstances in which they are left poses an unreasonable risk of harm or injury.", "answer": 2, "state": "mi", "type": "permit", "id": 53597}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "A 25% increase on the maximum sentence for a second felony conviction", "A 50% increase on the maximum sentence for a third felony conviction"], "question": "Sanctions under the Repeat Offender laws can include which of the following?", "answer": 1, "state": "mi", "type": "permit", "id": 53598}
{"candidates": ["You can have an additional ten years to complete your license renewal.", "You can have an additional two years to complete your license renewal.", "You need to pay a renewal fee of $12."], "question": "If your license expires while on active duty in the military:", "answer": 1, "state": "mi", "type": "permit", "id": 53629}
{"candidates": ["You need a parent or guardian's endorsement.", "You must pass the written chauffeur\u2019s test.", "You must be at least age 16."], "question": "Which of the following is not required to obtain a chauffeur's license?", "answer": 0, "state": "mi", "type": "permit", "id": 53656}
{"candidates": ["2", "5", "10"], "question": "At what age can a child ride in the car without a child restraint system?", "answer": 2, "state": "mi", "type": "permit", "id": 53816}
{"candidates": ["Stop", "Proceed with caution", "Pass the bus"], "question": "Yellow hazard lights on a school bus mean that you should ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "mi", "type": "permit", "id": 53846}
{"candidates": ["Between 65 mph and 70 mph.", "No faster than 65 mph.", "70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic."], "question": "When should you perform head checks?", "answer": 1, "state": "mi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 53900}
{"candidates": ["20 mph", "15 mph", "25 mph"], "question": "A cushion of space around your motorcycle gives you ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "mi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 53901}
{"candidates": ["70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic.", "Between 65 mph and 70 mph.", "No faster than 65 mph."], "question": "When making turns as a group at an intersection you should ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "mi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 53904}
{"candidates": ["Cannot see the vehicle directly to your right.", "Have passed the other vehicle\u2019s front bumper.", "See the vehicle\u2019s headlights in your rear view mirror."], "question": "Alcohol hits your brain within ____ after consumption.", "answer": 2, "state": "mi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 53906}
{"candidates": ["All vehicles are traveling about the same speed.", "One lane of traffic is traveling faster than the other lanes.", "One vehicle is traveling faster or slower than the flow of traffic."], "question": "If a rider falls behind, you should ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "mi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 54019}
{"candidates": ["Next to the broken line may pass.", "In both directions may pass.", "Next to the solid line may pass."], "question": "Before starting your group ride, you should decide on a lead rider and a ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "mi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 54115}
{"candidates": ["Wait four seconds before proceeding.", "Yield to any vehicle, bicycle, or pedestrian in the intersection.", "Yield to pedestrians only in the intersection."], "question": "Riders should always be extra careful of ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "mi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 54116}
{"candidates": ["When you want to pass a driver ahead of you who is turning right.", "During rush hour traffic if there are no bicyclists in the bike lane.", "When you are within 200 feet of a cross street where you plan to turn right."], "question": "Drivers involved in crashes with motorcycles, most often say ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "mi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 54173}
{"candidates": ["Stop as long as the red lights are flashing.", "Stop, then proceed when you think all of the children have exited the bus.", "Slow to 25 MPH and pass cautiously."], "question": "What does the \"Traffic Signal Ahead\" sign mean?", "answer": 0, "state": "mn", "type": "permit", "id": 55627}
{"candidates": ["6 months", "3 months", "4 months"], "question": "Under the GDL system, before taking the road test, drivers 18 years or under must hold an instructional permit for a period of:", "answer": 0, "state": "mn", "type": "permit", "id": 55656}
{"candidates": ["at 8 and 4", "at 10 and 2", "at 9 and 3"], "question": "Which of the following are proper hand positions on the wheel when equipped with an airbag?", "answer": 2, "state": "mn", "type": "permit", "id": 55665}
{"candidates": ["Slow down or stop, if necessary, and then make the turn.", "Stop before entering the right lane and let all other traffic go first.", "Signal and turn immediately."], "question": "A yellow warning sign with a large T-shaped symbol indicates:", "answer": 0, "state": "mn", "type": "permit", "id": 55695}
{"candidates": ["Mufflers can keep the vehicle from making sudden or prolonged loud noises.", "All the others.", "Check the muffler regularly for carbon monoxide leaks."], "question": "Which is true about mufflers?", "answer": 0, "state": "mn", "type": "permit", "id": 55719}
{"candidates": ["50 mph", "35 mph", "25 mph"], "question": "When driving on a freeway, at what speed should you drive relative to other vehicles?", "answer": 0, "state": "mn", "type": "permit", "id": 55833}
{"candidates": ["18 years old", "21 years old", "16 years old"], "question": "How old must you be to drive a recreational vehicle combination?", "answer": 0, "state": "mn", "type": "permit", "id": 55858}
{"candidates": ["Allows the driver to operate commercial driver's license enables you to drive vehicles with a gross combination weight rating (GVWR) of 26,001 or more.", "Allows the driver to operate operate any vehicle with a semi-trailer or trailer with two or more axles.", "Allows the driver to operate all the vehicles in the particular class for which the license was issued."], "question": "A CDL allows you to ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "mn", "type": "permit", "id": 55859}
{"candidates": ["Slow down, and pull to a safe area off the roadway.", "Turn on your emergency flashers.", "All the others."], "question": "If your wipers fail during rain or snow what should you do?", "answer": 0, "state": "mn", "type": "permit", "id": 55860}
{"candidates": ["100 to 150 feet", "400 to 500 feet", "350 to 400 feet"], "question": "When set on high beam, headlights should make objects visible to what distance?", "answer": 2, "state": "mn", "type": "permit", "id": 55891}
{"candidates": ["Indicate which lane should be merging into the other.", "Indicate next to the solid line may pass.", "Indicate next to the broken line may pass."], "question": "What does a \"Merging Traffic\" sign indicate in Minnesota?", "answer": 0, "state": "mn", "type": "permit", "id": 55922}
{"candidates": ["Both of the above.", "Report the accident without delay to the city police or, in unincorporated areas, to the CHP.", "Leave a note on the vehicle."], "question": "At a green light, you ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "mn", "type": "permit", "id": 56010}
{"candidates": ["A yellow, diamond-shaped warning sign featuring the words \u201cDRAW BRIDGE AHEAD\u201d", "A yellow, diamond-shaped warning sign featuring the words \u201cSCHOOL ZONE AHEAD\u201d", "A orange, diamond-shaped warning sign featuring the words \u201cDRAW BRIDGE AHEAD\u201d"], "question": "What signage should you look for while on a bridge?", "answer": 0, "state": "mn", "type": "permit", "id": 56064}
{"candidates": ["Orange", "Red", "Green"], "question": "Guidance and information signs are denoted by the color ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "mn", "type": "permit", "id": 56089}
{"candidates": ["Traffic merging left.", "Traffic merging right.", "New traffic will not have to merge."], "question": "The \"Added Lane\" sign signifies what?", "answer": 2, "state": "mn", "type": "permit", "id": 56093}
{"candidates": ["Poor balance", "Failing eyesight", "All the others."], "question": "Which is true about medical conditions that may affect your driving?", "answer": 1, "state": "mn", "type": "permit", "id": 56150}
{"candidates": ["Increase your chances of an accident.", "Help prevent traffic congestion.", "Get you to your destination much faster and safer."], "question": "Which of the following can affect your ability to operate a motorcycle?", "answer": 0, "state": "mn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 56206}
{"candidates": ["That vehicles may pass in all directions.", "That vehicles next to the solid yellow line may pass.", "That only vehicles next to the broken line may pass."], "question": "Approximately ____ percent of riders killed since 2002 have had alcohol in their system.", "answer": 2, "state": "mn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 56208}
{"candidates": ["In a bicycle lane.", "In an unmarked crosswalk", "Within three feet of a private driveway."], "question": "A motorcycle endorsement renewal fee is ____ dollars.", "answer": 1, "state": "mn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 56236}
{"candidates": ["On the side of the freeway in an emergency.", "Within 100 feet of an elementary school.", "Next to a red painted curb."], "question": "Which of the following must you bring to a moped skills test?", "answer": 2, "state": "mn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 56238}
{"candidates": ["Should wait for the first two vehicles to pass, then drive into the lane.", "Need a large enough gap to get up to the speed of traffic.", "Should drive slower than other traffic for 200 feet."], "question": "Which of the following are ways you can avoid driving drunk?", "answer": 1, "state": "mn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 56297}
{"candidates": ["Unless the vehicle was built before 1978.", "When the vehicle is equipped with seat belts.", "Unless you are in a limousine."], "question": "Any moped rider under the age of ____ must wear a DOT approved helmet.", "answer": 1, "state": "mn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 56298}
{"candidates": ["They are eliminated if you have one outside mirror on each side of the vehicle.", "Blind spots can be checked by looking in your rear view mirrors.", "Large trucks have bigger blind spots than most passenger vehicles."], "question": "An adult with a BAC of ____ % or above is considered intoxicated.", "answer": 2, "state": "mn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 56355}
{"candidates": ["At all times.", "Unless they conflict with existing signs, signals, or laws.", "Only if you see orange cones on the road ahead."], "question": "Which of the following is affected first by drinking alcohol?", "answer": 0, "state": "mn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 56388}
{"candidates": ["May complete its turn in either of the two lanes.", "May have to swing wide to complete the right turn.", "Must stay in the right lane at all times while turning."], "question": "Your chance of falling or being involved in a crash increases whenever you ride across ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "mn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 56480}
{"candidates": ["Within the distance lighted by your parking lights.", "Within the distance you can see ahead.", "Within 5-10 seconds."], "question": "New residents of Minnesota have ____ days to register their motorcycle in the state after changing residence.", "answer": 1, "state": "mn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 56481}
{"candidates": ["Have passed the other vehicle\u2019s front bumper.", "See the vehicle\u2019s headlights in your rear view mirror.", "Cannot see the vehicle directly to your right."], "question": "The SEE strategy consists of Search, Evaluate, and ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "mn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 56570}
{"candidates": ["Decrease your following distance.", "Pass the construction zone carefully and not rubberneck.", "Slow down to watch the workers."], "question": "It is important to keep a following distance of at least ____ seconds behind another vehicle.", "answer": 1, "state": "mn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 56598}
{"candidates": ["25 mph", "15 mph", "20 mph"], "question": "If your faceplate is damaged by a flying object, which of the following should you do?", "answer": 1, "state": "mn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 56630}
{"candidates": ["Next to the solid line may pass.", "Next to the broken line may pass.", "In both directions may pass."], "question": "In addition to alcohol and illegal drugs, ____ can also have adverse effects on the body to impair driving.", "answer": 1, "state": "mn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 56684}
{"candidates": ["Within the distance you can see ahead.", "Within 5-10 seconds.", "Within the distance lighted by your parking lights."], "question": "Which of the following must you bring to a motorcycle skills test?", "answer": 0, "state": "mn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 56685}
{"candidates": ["Traffic on the street moves to the right.", "A sign permits the turn.", "Traffic on the street moves to the left."], "question": "Which of the following components of your motorcycle should be checked before riding with a passenger?", "answer": 2, "state": "mn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 56688}
{"candidates": ["Use hands-free devices so you can keep both hands on the steering wheel.", "Review the number before answering a call.", "Keep your phone within easy reach so you won't need to take your eyes off the road."], "question": "Where is the greatest potential for conflict between a motorcycle and other vehicles?", "answer": 0, "state": "mn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 56690}
{"candidates": ["When the vehicle is equipped with seat belts.", "Unless you are in a limousine.", "Unless the vehicle was built before 1978."], "question": "For a first DUI conviction, you may serve jail time for up to ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "ms", "type": "permit", "id": 58205}
{"candidates": ["Stop, then proceed when you think all of the children have exited the bus.", "Stop as long as the red lights are flashing.", "Slow to 25 MPH and pass cautiously."], "question": "You must wear a helmet approved by the ____ if you drive a motorcycle on Mississippi roads.", "answer": 1, "state": "ms", "type": "permit", "id": 58239}
{"candidates": ["Stop and let him/her finish crossing the street.", "Slow down as you pass him/her.", "Make eye contact and then pass him/her."], "question": "What is the name of the form you will be given if your Mississippi eye test indicates that you need glasses or contact lenses?", "answer": 0, "state": "ms", "type": "permit", "id": 58267}
{"candidates": ["Stay out of the intersection until traffic clears.", "Enter the intersection and wait until traffic clears.", "Merge into another lane and try to go around the traffic."], "question": "Your tires must be free of ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "ms", "type": "permit", "id": 58328}
{"candidates": ["The lane closest to the left curb", "Any lane (as long as it is safe)", "The lane in the center of the road."], "question": "When sharing the road with a large vehicle, how should you position your vehicle?", "answer": 0, "state": "ms", "type": "permit", "id": 58388}
{"candidates": ["Next to a red painted curb.", "Within 100 feet of an elementary school.", "On the side of the freeway in an emergency."], "question": "Those of what age need to show proof of domicile in order to receive a license?", "answer": 0, "state": "ms", "type": "permit", "id": 58390}
{"candidates": ["It is OK for small children to ride in the front passenger seat of your car.", "Use the rear-facing child restraint system in the front passenger seat.", "Small children should ride in the back seat."], "question": "When passing someone on a bicycle, you should stay at least ____ feet away.", "answer": 2, "state": "ms", "type": "permit", "id": 58418}
{"candidates": ["Your side of the road is a broken line.", "The other side of the road is a solid line.", "The other side of the road is a broken line."], "question": "If you are applying for a license in Mississippi and are under 18 years old, the school certification form accompanying said application must not be over:", "answer": 0, "state": "ms", "type": "permit", "id": 58451}
{"candidates": ["Traffic on the street moves to the left.", "A sign permits the turn.", "Traffic on the street moves to the right."], "question": "In which of the following places are you not allowed to park?", "answer": 0, "state": "ms", "type": "permit", "id": 58659}
{"candidates": ["See the vehicle\u2019s headlights in your rear view mirror.", "Have passed the other vehicle\u2019s front bumper.", "Cannot see the vehicle directly to your right."], "question": "What is the typical maximum speed limit for standard passenger vehicles on U.S. roads?", "answer": 0, "state": "ms", "type": "permit", "id": 58661}
{"candidates": ["Make sure the pedestrian sees you, but continue driving.", "Stop and let the pedestrian cross the street.", "Carefully drive around the pedestrian."], "question": "In Mississippi, unless otherwise mandated, if you are parallel parking, your vehicle must be near the curb within:", "answer": 1, "state": "ms", "type": "permit", "id": 58780}
{"candidates": ["Assume the other driver will let you pass if you use your turn signal.", "Assume the other driver will maintain a constant speed.", "Not assume the other driver will make space for you to return to your lane."], "question": "As a pedestrian, which of the following lets you know that you have the right of way?", "answer": 2, "state": "mo", "type": "permit", "id": 60659}
{"candidates": ["Any 3-axle vehicle regardless of the weight.", "A 3-axle vehicle if the Gross Vehicle Weight is less than 6,000 pounds.", "A vehicle pulling two trailers."], "question": "If you are a new resident in Missouri how long do you have to register your vehicle?", "answer": 1, "state": "mo", "type": "permit", "id": 60687}
{"candidates": ["Make sure the pedestrian sees you, but continue driving.", "Carefully drive around the pedestrian.", "Stop and let the pedestrian cross the street."], "question": "Which of the following HEIGHT limitations (without special permit) on Missouri state roadways is FALSE/NOT TRUE?", "answer": 2, "state": "mo", "type": "permit", "id": 60716}
{"candidates": ["Your actions cannot result in a traffic citation.", "You can frustrate the other drivers and make them angry.", "You help reduce traffic congestion."], "question": "What is one reason that you can possibly have your drivers license revoked for?", "answer": 1, "state": "mo", "type": "permit", "id": 60719}
{"candidates": ["A speed just below the posted speed limit.", "A speed which matches the flow of traffic.", "The posted speed limit."], "question": "What number do you call in the state of Missouri when you have an emergency on the road?", "answer": 1, "state": "mo", "type": "permit", "id": 60720}
{"candidates": ["Avoid making fast turns and fast stops.", "Test your tires\u2019 traction while going uphill.", "Decrease the distance you look ahead of your vehicle."], "question": "To find information on salvaging a vehicle, you should contact ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "mo", "type": "permit", "id": 60776}
{"candidates": ["Stop, then proceed when you think all of the children have exited the bus.", "Slow to 25 MPH and pass cautiously.", "Stop as long as the red lights are flashing."], "question": "What numbers are used to identify a North-South route sign?", "answer": 2, "state": "mo", "type": "permit", "id": 60839}
{"candidates": ["The other side of the road is a solid line.", "The other side of the road is a broken line.", "Your side of the road is a broken line."], "question": "If you hurt or kill someone because you were drinking or using drugs while driving, you may ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "mo", "type": "permit", "id": 60867}
{"candidates": ["Traffic on the street moves to the left.", "A sign permits the turn.", "Traffic on the street moves to the right."], "question": "Which of the following is an example of a soft surface?", "answer": 0, "state": "mo", "type": "permit", "id": 60868}
{"candidates": ["Look to the sides of your vehicle to see what is coming.", "Stop, listen, and proceed cautiously.", "Slowly pass vehicles that seem to be stopped for no reason."], "question": "What does a flashing yellow traffic light mean?", "answer": 0, "state": "mo", "type": "permit", "id": 60869}
{"candidates": ["25 mph", "20 mph", "15 mph"], "question": "Which of the following do not have to obtain a Missouri driver's license?", "answer": 2, "state": "mo", "type": "permit", "id": 60870}
{"candidates": ["Loading zone for passengers or mail only.", "Loading zone for freight or passengers.", "Loading zone for freight only."], "question": "What must vehicle operators do, above all else, when driving in Missouri?", "answer": 0, "state": "mo", "type": "permit", "id": 60898}
{"candidates": ["When there are no vehicles approaching nearby.", "On a one-way street on a green arrow.", "Across two sets of solid double, yellow lines."], "question": "What does a broken line on the pavement mean?", "answer": 0, "state": "mo", "type": "permit", "id": 60958}
{"candidates": ["After it has been raining for awhile.", "The first rain after a dry spell.", "During a heavy downpour."], "question": "Left-turn lanes are marked with ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "mo", "type": "permit", "id": 61140}
{"candidates": ["Between 65 mph and 70 mph.", "70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic.", "No faster than 65 mph."], "question": "Which of the following can be taken away if you fail to keep your insurance?", "answer": 2, "state": "mo", "type": "permit", "id": 61163}
{"candidates": ["Get a new prescription for lenses or contacts.", "Fail a smog test for your vehicle.", "Sell or transfer your vehicle."], "question": "Which of the following is true of crosswalks and stop lines?", "answer": 2, "state": "mo", "type": "permit", "id": 61164}
{"candidates": ["Unless you do not see any children present.", "Only during school hours.", "At all times."], "question": "What is the maximum weight limit of a single axle vehicle on an interstate?", "answer": 2, "state": "mo", "type": "permit", "id": 61170}
{"candidates": ["Stop. Yield to all cross traffic before crossing the intersection.", "Stop before entering the intersection as long as you can do so safely.", "Slow down and cross the intersection carefully."], "question": "When traveling across pavement seems, you should cross at least a ____ degree angle.", "answer": 2, "state": "mo", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 61258}
{"candidates": ["Should only merge into the bicycle lane if you stop before turning.", "May not enter the bicycle lane.", "Must merge into the bicycle lane before turning."], "question": "Which of the following should you not do if you are riding an unfamiliar motorcycle?", "answer": 2, "state": "mo", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 61259}
{"candidates": ["Within 5-10 seconds.", "Within the distance lighted by your parking lights.", "Within the distance you can see ahead."], "question": "Which of the following should you instruct your passenger not do?", "answer": 2, "state": "mo", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 61288}
{"candidates": ["Stop and let the pedestrian cross the street.", "Carefully drive around the pedestrian.", "Make sure the pedestrian sees you, but continue driving."], "question": "How many skills are critical to avoiding a crash?", "answer": 0, "state": "mo", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 61320}
{"candidates": ["When you entered the intersection on the green light.", "During rush hour traffic.", "Under no circumstances."], "question": "What equipment do you need to have to ensure you are carrying a passenger safely?", "answer": 2, "state": "mo", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 61321}
{"candidates": ["Only if you are at fault.", "Only if you or the other driver is injured.", "If there is property damage in excess of $750 or if there are any injuries."], "question": "Which of the following are times you should check your mirrors?", "answer": 2, "state": "mo", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 61374}
{"candidates": ["Listening to music through headphones that cover both ears", "Adjusting your outside mirrors.", "Transporting an unrestrained animal inside the vehicle."], "question": "Keeping distance provides which of the following?", "answer": 0, "state": "mo", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 61376}
{"candidates": ["Stop before entering the intersection and let all other traffic go first.", "Slow down or stop, only if necessary.", "Stop, then proceed when safe."], "question": "The front brake can provide ____ % of the stopping power.", "answer": 2, "state": "mo", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 61410}
{"candidates": ["Slowly pass vehicles that seem to be stopped for no reason.", "Look to the sides of your vehicle to see what is coming.", "Stop, listen, and proceed cautiously."], "question": "Which of the following should you not wear while riding?", "answer": 1, "state": "mo", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 61436}
{"candidates": ["You can frustrate the other drivers and make them angry.", "You help reduce traffic congestion.", "Your actions cannot result in a traffic citation."], "question": "Where should your seat be while you are operating a motorcycle?", "answer": 0, "state": "mo", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 61439}
{"candidates": ["Only if you see orange cones on the road ahead.", "At all times.", "Unless they conflict with existing signs, signals, or laws."], "question": "There are ____ steps for better control while turning.", "answer": 1, "state": "mo", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 61471}
{"candidates": ["No, you can block traffic when you drive too slowly.", "Yes, it is a good defensive driving technique.", "Yes, it is always safer than driving faster than other traffic."], "question": "In an emergency situation, how should you use your horn?", "answer": 0, "state": "mo", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 61590}
{"candidates": ["Signal for 100 feet before turning.", "Move toward the left side of your lane.", "Avoid driving in the bicycle lane."], "question": "Alcohol begins to affect the drinker when?", "answer": 0, "state": "mo", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 61618}
{"candidates": ["Under no circumstances.", "When you entered the intersection on the green light.", "During rush hour traffic."], "question": "What is the best way to lengthen the life of your vehicle?", "answer": 0, "state": "mt", "type": "permit", "id": 63048}
{"candidates": ["A maximum of 50 feet and a minimum of 15 feet from the nearest railroad track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 50 feet from the nearest track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 100 feet from the nearest track"], "question": "Men between the ages of ____ and ____ must register with the Selective Service.", "answer": 0, "state": "mt", "type": "permit", "id": 63141}
{"candidates": ["Pass the construction zone carefully and not rubberneck.", "Slow down to watch the workers.", "Decrease your following distance."], "question": "Which of the following are NOT included in the definition of a school zone?", "answer": 0, "state": "mt", "type": "permit", "id": 63164}
{"candidates": ["Cannot see the vehicle directly to your right.", "Have passed the other vehicle\u2019s front bumper.", "See the vehicle\u2019s headlights in your rear view mirror."], "question": "New residents have ____ days to transfer their out of state license.", "answer": 2, "state": "mt", "type": "permit", "id": 63196}
{"candidates": ["Unless you do not see any children present.", "At all times.", "Only during school hours."], "question": "If you are required to speed up in order to avoid a collision:", "answer": 1, "state": "mt", "type": "permit", "id": 63290}
{"candidates": ["Merge into another lane and try to go around the traffic.", "Enter the intersection and wait until traffic clears.", "Stay out of the intersection until traffic clears."], "question": "In Montana it's required that you have at least ____ vision in one eye.", "answer": 2, "state": "mt", "type": "permit", "id": 63317}
{"candidates": ["Loading zone for passengers or mail only.", "Loading zone for freight only.", "Loading zone for freight or passengers."], "question": "What should the driver assume when passing by a cyclist?", "answer": 0, "state": "mt", "type": "permit", "id": 63438}
{"candidates": ["15", "5", "10"], "question": "If there aren't any lane markings you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "mt", "type": "permit", "id": 63439}
{"candidates": ["You are approaching from behind.", "Approaching you from behind.", "You have already passed."], "question": "If an emergency vehicle is approaching, you must:", "answer": 0, "state": "mt", "type": "permit", "id": 63651}
{"candidates": ["May have to swing wide to complete the right turn.", "Must stay in the right lane at all times while turning.", "May complete its turn in either of the two lanes."], "question": "When accelerating, you should do so:", "answer": 0, "state": "mt", "type": "permit", "id": 63678}
{"candidates": ["A speed which matches the flow of traffic.", "A speed just below the posted speed limit.", "The posted speed limit."], "question": "What should you do if your headlights stop working?", "answer": 0, "state": "mt", "type": "permit", "id": 63679}
{"candidates": ["They are eliminated if you have one outside mirror on each side of the vehicle.", "Blind spots can be checked by looking in your rear view mirrors.", "Large trucks have bigger blind spots than most passenger vehicles."], "question": "Which of the following scenarios is a proper way to use your horn?", "answer": 2, "state": "mt", "type": "permit", "id": 63681}
{"candidates": ["Your front wheels must be turned toward the street.", "Your wheels must be within 18 inches of the curb.", "One of your rear wheels must touch the curb."], "question": "How should you protect yourself from fatigue when riding a motorcycle?", "answer": 1, "state": "mt", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 63861}
{"candidates": ["0.02", "0.1", "0.08"], "question": "The Nebraska blood alcohol concentration (BAC) limit for minor drivers under age 21 is:", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65503}
{"candidates": ["20 miles per hour", "30 miles per hour", "25 miles per hour"], "question": "Unless otherwise posted, the speed limit in a residential district is:", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65505}
{"candidates": ["the same for all vehicles", "less than other vehicles because a motorcycle can stop faster than other vehicles", "more than other vehicles because a motorcycle is smaller than other vehicles"], "question": "The following distance behind a motorcycle should be:", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65507}
{"candidates": ["in the front seat of the vehicle", "secured in a safety belt or child safety seat", "in the back seat of the vehicle"], "question": "All children ages six up to 18 are required to ride:", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65541}
{"candidates": ["Stop and let him/her finish crossing the street.", "Make eye contact and then pass him/her.", "Slow down as you pass him/her."], "question": "What saying should you remember when it comes to deer in the road?", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65559}
{"candidates": ["No faster than 65 mph.", "Between 65 mph and 70 mph.", "70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic."], "question": "In what year did most vehicles become equipped with a spring loaded steering wheel lock device?", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65561}
{"candidates": ["press brake pedal firmly, do not pump brakes", "pump brakes until the vehicle has come to a stop", "wait for the car to stop without pressing on the brakes"], "question": "When stopping on snow or ice, drivers who are operating vehicles equipped with antilock (ABS) brakes should:", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65567}
{"candidates": ["slow", "stop", "yield"], "question": "When you see an octagon shaped sign, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65571}
{"candidates": ["activate your four way flashers at least 100 feet before entering the work zone", "stay alert, obey signs that are posted, don't slow speed abruptly, but be prepared to stop", "increase speed so as not to impede traffic"], "question": "When driving in work zones, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65572}
{"candidates": ["guide drivers into certain traffic lanes and to inform them that part of the road ahead is closed.", "indicate where you must pull onto the shoulder of the road and stop.", "are only used on the Interstate Highway System."], "question": "Flashing arrow panels used in work zones:", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65574}
{"candidates": ["continue moving and clear the intersection safely", "increase your speed so as not to cause an accident", "stop"], "question": "A steady yellow signal light is a warning that the light is about to change to red. If you are already in the intersection, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65579}
{"candidates": ["indicate that a stop is ahead.", "alert drowsy or inattentive drivers through vibrations and sound that their vehicles has left the road.", "help slow the vehicle in case of brake failure."], "question": "Shoulder rumble strips are a series of indented or raised elements installed on a paved roadway near the travel lane. Rumble strips are intended to:", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65594}
{"candidates": ["two points and court costs assessed against the driver", "two points assessed against the driver", "a $25 fine with one point assessed against the driver"], "question": "Failure to secure children ages six up to 18 in a safety belt or child safety seat is punishable by:", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65595}
{"candidates": ["keep to the right.", "drive with the 4-way flashers on.", "keep to the left."], "question": "When driving on the interstate, slower traffic should:", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65596}
{"candidates": ["That vehicles may pass in all directions.", "That vehicles next to the solid yellow line may pass.", "That only vehicles next to the broken line may pass."], "question": "As a defensive driving technique, you should signal your intentions how many feet before you change direction?", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65617}
{"candidates": ["six", "nine", "three"], "question": "Accumulating 12 violation points in a two year period results in an automatic revocation of your driver's license for ____ months.", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65626}
{"candidates": ["the lack of work zone barricades alerting the driver to the work zone.", "driving slower or faster than the surrounding traffic.", "construction equipment obstructing the driver's view."], "question": "The major cause of rear-end crashes in work zones is:", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65660}
{"candidates": ["stop at the stop line", "stop in the crosswalk", "stop after the stop line, but before the stop sign or traffic signal"], "question": "Stop lines are white lines painted across the pavement at intersections. When you approach a stop line, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65685}
{"candidates": ["the driver who stops first should be allowed to go first", "drivers may insist on the right-of-way even at the risk of an accident", "drivers must slow down and proceed if the roads are clear"], "question": "At intersections with four-way stops:", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65698}
{"candidates": ["Avoid driving in the bicycle lane.", "Move toward the left side of your lane.", "Signal for 100 feet before turning."], "question": "Where and when is the use of nitrous oxide prohibited?", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65706}
{"candidates": ["only when there is an adequate and safe gap in traffic.", "immediately, as you always have the right-of-way.", "after coming to a complete stop and looking both ways."], "question": "Enter a roundabout:", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65715}
{"candidates": ["90", "10", "60"], "question": "Nebraska law requires that individuals who change their name or address shall apply to the County Treasurer for a replacement operator's license within ____ days.", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65717}
{"candidates": ["following too close and inadequate road conditions", "excessive speed and inattention by the motorcycle driver", "failure to yield the right-of-way and making a left turn in front of an oncoming motorcycle"], "question": "The two most frequent causes of motorcycle accidents are:", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65748}
{"candidates": ["seven", "five", "three"], "question": "Always keep a cushion of space between you and other vehicles to have time to react to emergencies and avoid collisions. Use the ____ second rule to determine safe following distance", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65753}
{"candidates": ["The driver could have his/her operator's license revoked", "The driver can be charged with a misdemeanor or felony offense", "All the others."], "question": "What is the penalty for fleeing to avoid arrest?", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65755}
{"candidates": ["they are not considered emergency vehicles.", "they are considered emergency vehicles only when escorted by a police vehicle.", "they are classified as emergency vehicles."], "question": "The following is true regarding funeral procession escort vehicles:", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65776}
{"candidates": ["before you cross the median of the interstate highway", "to exit", "while overtaking or passing another vehicle"], "question": "When driving on the interstate, you should use the left lane:", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65778}
{"candidates": ["signal and slow down 50-100 feet prior to the exit ramp", "signal and move into the proper lane a mile or more before the exit", "slow to 45 miles per hour"], "question": "When you plan on leaving the interstate, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65780}
{"candidates": ["25 miles per hour", "20 miles per hour", "30 miles per hour"], "question": "Unless otherwise posted, the speed limit in a business district is:", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65804}
{"candidates": ["twelve", "eighteen", "eight"], "question": "Children up to age ____ are prohibited from riding in cargo areas.", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65810}
{"candidates": ["100", "50", "150"], "question": "To let others know you intend to turn, give signals at least ____ feet from the place you plan to turn.", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65833}
{"candidates": ["doubled", "reduced", "tripled"], "question": "Fines for speeding are ____ in work zones.", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65838}
{"candidates": ["15/$750", "10/$1000", "5/$250"], "question": "Nebraska law requires individuals involved in a crash to report it to the Department of Roads within ____ days if any person is injured or killed, or damages appear to exceed ____ for any vehicle or piece of property.", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65844}
{"candidates": ["a safety belt should not be worn by the driver of a vehicle equipped with air bags", "when combined with safety belts, air bags provide improved crash protection", "children age 12 and under should always sit in the front seat of a car that is equipped with air bags"], "question": "The following is true about air bags:", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65845}
{"candidates": ["pass within 300 feet of a railroad crossing.", "pass in any marked no-passing zone.", "All the others."], "question": "It is unlawful to:", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65866}
{"candidates": ["aggressive driving by the driver.", "driver being under the influence of alcohol or other drugs.", "drive distractions (cell phone usage, etc.)."], "question": "The major contributing factor in Nebraska crashes resulting in death and/or serious injury is:", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65893}
{"candidates": ["indicate there is two-way traffic", "separate lanes of traffic going in the same direction", "indicate you are in a no passing zone"], "question": "Road markings are used to guide and warn drivers as well as regulate traffic. Broken white lines:", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65896}
{"candidates": ["leave the vehicle running when you exit the vehicle.", "activate your four way flashers before pulling over to the side of the road.", "shift transmission to proper gear and set parking brake."], "question": "When making an emergency roadside stop, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65901}
{"candidates": ["Small children should ride in the back seat.", "It is OK for small children to ride in the front passenger seat of your car.", "Use the rear-facing child restraint system in the front passenger seat."], "question": "If you own a vehicle that has a safety defect who should you contact?", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65920}
{"candidates": ["stay in your lane", "increase your speed to beat the vehicles that are on the entrance ramp", "move left to allow them a smooth, safe entry, if it is safe"], "question": "While driving on the interstate, you see vehicles on the entrance ramp to your right. You should:", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65935}
{"candidates": ["Must merge into the bicycle lane before turning.", "Should only merge into the bicycle lane if you stop before turning.", "May not enter the bicycle lane."], "question": "If there isn't a stop line at a railroad crossing, you should stop within ____ feet from the closest rail.", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65948}
{"candidates": ["at a speed that is reasonable and safe under existing conditions", "5 miles per hour below the posted speed", "at the posted speed"], "question": "Nebraska's speed law requires you drive:", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65953}
{"candidates": ["passing is not permitted", "passing is permitted on the right when the way ahead is clear", "passing is permitted on the left when the way ahead is clear"], "question": "A broken yellow center line indicates:", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65955}
{"candidates": ["six", "four", "eight"], "question": "The Child Passenger Restraint Law requires that all children up to age ____ ride correctly secured in a federally approved child safety seat.", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65960}
{"candidates": ["you must stop at the stop sign, regardless of where it is located.", "it is permissible for you to stop your vehicle inside the crosswalk.", "you must stop before entering the crosswalk."], "question": "When approaching an intersection with a stop sign and a sidewalk, but the crosswalk is not painted:", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65964}
{"candidates": ["Help prevent traffic congestion.", "Get you to your destination much faster and safer.", "Increase your chances of an accident."], "question": "What term is used to define any controlled access, multi-lane highway?", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65981}
{"candidates": ["come to a complete stop, look both ways and yield the right of way to pedestrians and other traffic.", "maintain normal speed because you have the right of way.", "slow down and proceed without stopping if the way is clear."], "question": "At many intersections, under certain conditions, a right turn may be made while the traffic light is red. Before turning right:", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65986}
{"candidates": ["school and school crossing sign", "stop sign", "regulatory or guide sign"], "question": "A pentagon-shaped sign tells you that the sign is a:", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65991}
{"candidates": ["motorist services", "construction and maintenance", "guide information, such as distance or direction"], "question": "Blue color traffic signs offer information on:", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 65995}
{"candidates": ["large trucks and buses have air brakes which do not operate as quickly as the hydraulic brakes on smaller vehicles", "large trucks and buses travel at a higher rate of speed than small vehicles", "small vehicle drivers cannot adequately see large trucks and buses in their rearview mirror"], "question": "You should not make sudden stops in front of large trucks and buses because:", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 66023}
{"candidates": ["put on your cruise control to maintain a constant speed", "slow down", "move to the shoulder of the road immediately"], "question": "Hydroplaning occurs when tires ride on a thin film of water instead of the road. To prevent hydroplaning, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 66076}
{"candidates": ["40 miles per hour", "45 miles per hour", "50 miles per hour"], "question": "Unless otherwise posted, the speed limit on a non-hard surface county road is:", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 66084}
{"candidates": ["That vehicles may pass in all directions.", "That vehicles next to the solid yellow line may pass.", "That only vehicles next to the broken line may pass."], "question": "On a Nebraska state highway, the maximum speed is:", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 66097}
{"candidates": ["90 days", "1 year", "30 days"], "question": "Drivers who refuse to submit to a chemical test for alcohol or drugs lose their driver's license for:", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 66104}
{"candidates": ["5", "15", "10"], "question": "You should never park within ____ feet of a fire hydrant.", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 66108}
{"candidates": ["200 feet", "100 feet", "500 feet"], "question": "No vehicle may follow any fire apparatus traveling in an emergency status closer than:", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "permit", "id": 66138}
{"candidates": ["Avoid surface hazards", "Increase your ability to see", "Encourage the sharing of your lane"], "question": "A lane position should do all of the following, except:", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66197}
{"candidates": ["Knees should be against the gas tank", "Feet should be firmly on the footrests", "Handlebars should be adjusted so the hands are above your elbows"], "question": "To control a motorcycle well, your posture is important. Which of the following is not a proper position on a motorcycle?", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66203}
{"candidates": ["Must be operated on the shoulder", "Cannot carry a passenger", "Cannot be driven on a public roadway"], "question": "A motorized bike with 45 or fewer cc's:", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66207}
{"candidates": ["When you are within 200 feet of a cross street where you plan to turn right.", "When you want to pass a driver ahead of you who is turning right.", "During rush hour traffic if there are no bicyclists in the bike lane."], "question": "It is important to use your signal not only to let the other drivers know what you doing but also for what other reason?", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66211}
{"candidates": ["Loading zone for passengers or mail only.", "Loading zone for freight only.", "Loading zone for freight or passengers."], "question": "What is the best protection you can have as a motorcyclist?", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66213}
{"candidates": ["That vehicles may pass in all directions.", "That only vehicles next to the broken line may pass.", "That vehicles next to the solid yellow line may pass."], "question": "How does the brake light of a motorcycle compare to the brake light of a car?", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66215}
{"candidates": ["No, you can block traffic when you drive too slowly.", "Yes, it is always safer than driving faster than other traffic.", "Yes, it is a good defensive driving technique."], "question": "If you lend your motorcycle to a friend or someone else, you should ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66219}
{"candidates": ["Slowly pass vehicles that seem to be stopped for no reason.", "Look to the sides of your vehicle to see what is coming.", "Stop, listen, and proceed cautiously."], "question": "When is it advisable to ride next to cars or trucks in other lanes?", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66220}
{"candidates": ["Stop where the cross-traffic lane meets your lane", "Stop at the stop sign and then continue through the intersection", "Stop at the stop sign and proceed slowly to just before where the cross-traffic lane meets your lane"], "question": "If you are approaching a blind intersection with a stop sign, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66223}
{"candidates": ["A sign permits the turn.", "Traffic on the street moves to the left.", "Traffic on the street moves to the right."], "question": "During what situation might you need to swerve or turn quickly?", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66244}
{"candidates": ["The lane in the center of the road.", "Any lane (as long as it is safe)", "The lane closest to the left curb"], "question": "Which of the following is the best method to stop quickly?", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66251}
{"candidates": ["Should be done every time you stop", "Should not be done, except for an emergency situation", "Should not be done unless the roadway is slippery"], "question": "Using both brakes:", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66262}
{"candidates": ["You should only use the right portion of the lane", "You should only use the left portion of the lane", "You should vary your lane position depending on the situation"], "question": "When riding a motorcycle,", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66269}
{"candidates": ["If the vehicle ahead of you is turning left.", "If the shoulder is wide enough to accommodate your vehicle", "Under no circumstances"], "question": "What is the best type of face protection to wear on a motorcycle?", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66273}
{"candidates": ["Provides protection from heat and cold", "Allows you to get a suntan", "Makes you more visible to others"], "question": "Which of the following is not a possible benefit of wearing the right clothing?", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66288}
{"candidates": ["Help lean the motorcycle", "Decrease your speed, to provide more control", "Maintain or increase speed, helping to stabilize the motorcycle"], "question": "In a turn, you should roll the throttle to:", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66293}
{"candidates": ["Open highway", "Intersections", "Rural road"], "question": "Where is the location for the greatest potential of conflict between you and other drivers?", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66338}
{"candidates": ["Lock up the wheels, but allow control", "Discourage braking on slippery surfaces", "Prevent wheel lock-up and avoid skids"], "question": "Anti-lock braking systems (ABS) are designed to:", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66353}
{"candidates": ["Move toward the left side of your lane.", "Avoid driving in the bicycle lane.", "Signal for 100 feet before turning."], "question": "When riding at night, what is the safest way to drive?", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66368}
{"candidates": ["Stop, End and Evaluate", "Search, Evaluate and Execute", "Scan, Error and Energy"], "question": "Good drivers use a SEE strategy to see what\u2019s around them. What does SEE stand for?", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66378}
{"candidates": ["Left portion, so the other driver sees you", "Right portion, to allow the other driver to cut over as quickly as possible", "Center portion, to discourage the other vehicle from sharing your lane"], "question": "When being passed, what portion of the lane should you ride in?", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66385}
{"candidates": ["Maintain an adequate search cushion ahead of you", "Wear dark-colored clothes", "Communicate your intentions, such as changing lanes"], "question": "To lessen your chances of a crash happening, you should do all of the following except:", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66386}
{"candidates": ["Low beams.", "Fog lights only.", "High beams."], "question": "What is affected first when you are inebriated?", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66397}
{"candidates": ["Be prepared for workers and equipment ahead.", "Slow down because the lane ends ahead.", "Change lanes and maintain your current speed."], "question": "After deciding it is possible to drive over an uneven surface, approach the obstacle at as close to a ____ degree angle as possible.", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66427}
{"candidates": ["No, you can block traffic when you drive too slowly.", "Yes, it is always safer than driving faster than other traffic.", "Yes, it is a good defensive driving technique."], "question": "How does the extra weight of passengers or cargo affect the way your motorcycle rides?", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66428}
{"candidates": ["On the right handle grip", "On the left handle grip", "On both handle grips"], "question": "The control for the front brake lever is located:", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66452}
{"candidates": ["Need a large enough gap to get up to the speed of traffic.", "Should drive slower than other traffic for 200 feet.", "Should wait for the first two vehicles to pass, then drive into the lane."], "question": "Which of the following is NOT a helpful way to handle corners?", "answer": 0, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66457}
{"candidates": ["Stop. Yield to all cross traffic before crossing the intersection.", "Stop before entering the intersection as long as you can do so safely.", "Slow down and cross the intersection carefully."], "question": "What portion of motorcycle/car crashes are caused by drivers entering a rider's right of way?", "answer": 2, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66461}
{"candidates": ["Any lane (as long as it is safe)", "The lane closest to the left curb", "The lane in the center of the road."], "question": "Most riders are moving slower than what speed when crashes occur?", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66486}
{"candidates": ["Assume the other driver will maintain a constant speed.", "Not assume the other driver will make space for you to return to your lane.", "Assume the other driver will let you pass if you use your turn signal."], "question": "Which of the following is a surface that can increase your chance of falling?", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66515}
{"candidates": ["The posted speed limit for traffic on the freeway.", "At or near the same speed as the traffic on the freeway.", "5 to 10 MPH slower than the traffic on the freeway."], "question": "When entering a turn, it's best to ____ gears.", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66542}
{"candidates": ["Get you to your destination much faster and safer.", "Increase your chances of an accident.", "Help prevent traffic congestion."], "question": "When operating a motorcycle, you should seat yourself how?", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66544}
{"candidates": ["Will prevent you from turning your head", "Will allow you to see adequately from side to side", "Will severely restrict your ability to see"], "question": "A DOT-compliant helmet:", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66554}
{"candidates": ["Turn within the lane to make a 90-degree crossing", "Use the shoulder so you can reduce your speed", "Ride straight in your lane to cross the tracks"], "question": "How should you cross railroad tracks in your lane?", "answer": 1, "state": "ne", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 66577}
{"candidates": ["Yield to any vehicle, bicycle, or pedestrian in the intersection.", "Yield to pedestrians only in the intersection.", "Wait four seconds before proceeding."], "question": "What must you provide to obtain a veteran designation on your license?", "answer": 0, "state": "nv", "type": "permit", "id": 68069}
{"candidates": ["Closely behind the truck in bad weather because the driver can see farther ahead.", "Farther behind the truck than you would for a passenger vehicle.", "No more than one car length behind the truck so the driver can see you."], "question": "What is the most important thing to do when driving in bad weather?", "answer": 1, "state": "nv", "type": "permit", "id": 68131}
{"candidates": ["Enter the intersection and wait until traffic clears.", "Stay out of the intersection until traffic clears.", "Merge into another lane and try to go around the traffic."], "question": "What can overloading your vehicle negatively affect?", "answer": 1, "state": "nv", "type": "permit", "id": 68158}
{"candidates": ["It is OK for small children to ride in the front passenger seat of your car.", "Small children should ride in the back seat.", "Use the rear-facing child restraint system in the front passenger seat."], "question": "A great defensive driving tip suggests you look ahead how many seconds at minimum?", "answer": 1, "state": "nv", "type": "permit", "id": 68188}
{"candidates": ["Fog lights only.", "Low beams.", "High beams."], "question": "An orange sign on the road means ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "nv", "type": "permit", "id": 68213}
{"candidates": ["Slow down because the lane ends ahead.", "Change lanes and maintain your current speed.", "Be prepared for workers and equipment ahead."], "question": "Though the fees are subject to change, what is the current cost of an original license for drivers under age 65?", "answer": 2, "state": "nv", "type": "permit", "id": 68218}
{"candidates": ["30 mph", "25 mph", "20 mph"], "question": "If you have to park during an emergency situation on the freeway, you should remember to do which of the following?", "answer": 1, "state": "nv", "type": "permit", "id": 68219}
{"candidates": ["A speed which matches the flow of traffic.", "A speed just below the posted speed limit.", "The posted speed limit."], "question": "Which of the following signals means that you must always come to a full stop?", "answer": 0, "state": "nv", "type": "permit", "id": 68247}
{"candidates": ["A 3-axle vehicle if the Gross Vehicle Weight is less than 6,000 pounds.", "Any 3-axle vehicle regardless of the weight.", "A vehicle pulling two trailers."], "question": "Most vehicles can float in ____ of water or less.", "answer": 0, "state": "nv", "type": "permit", "id": 68250}
{"candidates": ["Parking lights", "Interior lights", "Headlights."], "question": "When backing up trying to parallel park, you should allow about ____ feet of distance between your vehicle and the vehicle parked on the sidewalk.", "answer": 2, "state": "nv", "type": "permit", "id": 68311}
{"candidates": ["The lane in the center of the road.", "The lane closest to the left curb", "Any lane (as long as it is safe)"], "question": "Which of the following signals that a parked vehicle may pull out in front of you?", "answer": 1, "state": "nv", "type": "permit", "id": 68430}
{"candidates": ["Under no circumstances.", "When you entered the intersection on the green light.", "During rush hour traffic."], "question": "How many types of Anti-lock braking systems are there?", "answer": 0, "state": "nv", "type": "permit", "id": 68459}
{"candidates": ["Stop before entering the intersection as long as you can do so safely.", "Stop. Yield to all cross traffic before crossing the intersection.", "Slow down and cross the intersection carefully."], "question": "Which of the following is not true about the yellow light?", "answer": 2, "state": "nh", "type": "permit", "id": 70458}
{"candidates": ["The lane in the center of the road.", "Any lane (as long as it is safe)", "The lane closest to the left curb"], "question": "You should signal your intention to turn at least ____ before the turn.", "answer": 2, "state": "nh", "type": "permit", "id": 70461}
{"candidates": ["That vehicles next to the solid yellow line may pass.", "That only vehicles next to the broken line may pass.", "That vehicles may pass in all directions."], "question": "What should you do in the event the vehicle stalls on railroad tracks?", "answer": 1, "state": "nh", "type": "permit", "id": 70486}
{"candidates": ["Slowly pass vehicles that seem to be stopped for no reason.", "Stop, listen, and proceed cautiously.", "Look to the sides of your vehicle to see what is coming."], "question": "If the hood suddenly flies up and your vision is totally blocked, you should ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "nh", "type": "permit", "id": 70488}
{"candidates": ["Pass the construction zone carefully and not rubberneck.", "Decrease your following distance.", "Slow down to watch the workers."], "question": "Which of the following people need a New Hampshire license?", "answer": 0, "state": "nh", "type": "permit", "id": 70490}
{"candidates": ["The railroad crossing is located in a city or town that has frequent train traffic.", "You transport two or more young children in a passenger vehicle.", "You do not have room on the other side to completely cross the tracks."], "question": "Trailers above what weight require their own separate annual inspection?", "answer": 2, "state": "nh", "type": "permit", "id": 70581}
{"candidates": ["If there is property damage in excess of $750 or if there are any injuries.", "Only if you or the other driver is injured.", "Only if you are at fault."], "question": "Whenever you approach a school bus from any direction, which has stopped to pick up or let off its passengers while operating its flashing red lights, you must stop your vehicle at least ____ from the school bus.", "answer": 0, "state": "nh", "type": "permit", "id": 70610}
{"candidates": ["25 mph", "30 mph", "20 mph"], "question": "Which of the following demonstrates a proper turn between two multi-lane roads?", "answer": 0, "state": "nh", "type": "permit", "id": 70637}
{"candidates": ["Must merge into the bicycle lane before turning.", "May not enter the bicycle lane.", "Should only merge into the bicycle lane if you stop before turning."], "question": "A two-wheeled vehicle qualifies as a motor-driven cycle if it has a maximum of:", "answer": 0, "state": "nh", "type": "permit", "id": 70639}
{"candidates": ["Directly before and after school hours.", "There are children present.", "You must always obey school crossing-guards."], "question": "How long are new residents given from the date they move to New Hampshire to register their vehicles?", "answer": 2, "state": "nh", "type": "permit", "id": 70664}
{"candidates": ["Signal and turn immediately.", "Stop before entering the right lane and let all other traffic go first.", "Slow down or stop, if necessary, and then make the turn."], "question": "How many of the 40 questions must be answered correctly to pass the knowledge test before getting a license?", "answer": 2, "state": "nh", "type": "permit", "id": 70667}
{"candidates": ["Only if you or the other driver is injured.", "If there is property damage in excess of $750 or if there are any injuries.", "Only if you are at fault."], "question": "Who handles the registration of mopeds in New Hampshire?", "answer": 1, "state": "nh", "type": "permit", "id": 70671}
{"candidates": ["Move toward the left side of your lane.", "Avoid driving in the bicycle lane.", "Signal for 100 feet before turning."], "question": "One should signal at least how many seconds before turning or changing lanes?", "answer": 2, "state": "nh", "type": "permit", "id": 70785}
{"candidates": ["The railroad crossing is located in a city or town that has frequent train traffic.", "You transport two or more young children in a passenger vehicle.", "You do not have room on the other side to completely cross the tracks."], "question": "No more than ____ duplicate driver licenses will be issued for the term of your driver license.", "answer": 2, "state": "nh", "type": "permit", "id": 70789}
{"candidates": ["Approaching you from behind.", "You have already passed.", "You are approaching from behind."], "question": "Which of the following is true of a red arrow?", "answer": 2, "state": "nh", "type": "permit", "id": 70970}
{"candidates": ["10 to 15 seconds", "5 to 10 seconds", "15 to 20 seconds"], "question": "At what speed do air bags inflate?", "answer": 0, "state": "nj", "type": "permit", "id": 72878}
{"candidates": ["Only during school hours.", "At all times.", "Unless you do not see any children present."], "question": "The BAC is determined by all of the following except:", "answer": 1, "state": "nj", "type": "permit", "id": 73000}
{"candidates": ["Merge into another lane and try to go around the traffic.", "Enter the intersection and wait until traffic clears.", "Stay out of the intersection until traffic clears."], "question": "On packed snow, a car traveling 30 mph should remain how many car lengths back from the car in front of them?", "answer": 2, "state": "nj", "type": "permit", "id": 73031}
{"candidates": ["At or near the same speed as the traffic on the freeway.", "The posted speed limit for traffic on the freeway.", "5 to 10 MPH slower than the traffic on the freeway."], "question": "If blinded by sun glare, drivers should:", "answer": 0, "state": "nj", "type": "permit", "id": 73084}
{"candidates": ["Have passed the other vehicle\u2019s front bumper.", "Cannot see the vehicle directly to your right.", "See the vehicle\u2019s headlights in your rear view mirror."], "question": "What is not used for divided roadways to have an ease of traffic flow?", "answer": 2, "state": "nj", "type": "permit", "id": 73085}
{"candidates": ["After it has been raining for awhile.", "The first rain after a dry spell.", "During a heavy downpour."], "question": "Which of the following is not a requirement for a basic driver's license in New Jersey?", "answer": 1, "state": "nj", "type": "permit", "id": 73121}
{"candidates": ["Look only at the car in front of you while driving.", "Keep your eyes moving to look for possible hazards.", "Always put one car length between you and the car ahead."], "question": "In the \"decide\" portion of the SIPDE system, riders should determine how to reduce a hazard by:", "answer": 1, "state": "nj", "type": "permit", "id": 73211}
{"candidates": ["When you entered the intersection on the green light.", "During rush hour traffic.", "Under no circumstances."], "question": "What do stopping distances depend on?", "answer": 2, "state": "nj", "type": "permit", "id": 73267}
{"candidates": ["Only during school hours.", "At all times.", "Unless you do not see any children present."], "question": "Which of the following uses of a cell phone while driving is legal?", "answer": 1, "state": "nj", "type": "permit", "id": 73330}
{"candidates": ["Stop. Yield to all cross traffic before crossing the intersection.", "Stop before entering the intersection as long as you can do so safely.", "Slow down and cross the intersection carefully."], "question": "By law, New Jersey motorists must keep to the right:", "answer": 2, "state": "nj", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 73600}
{"candidates": ["Pass the construction zone carefully and not rubberneck.", "Slow down to watch the workers.", "Decrease your following distance."], "question": "An out-of-state driver must purchase an examination permit within how long after becoming a New Jersey resident?", "answer": 0, "state": "nj", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 73749}
{"candidates": ["There are children present.", "You must always obey school crossing-guards.", "Directly before and after school hours."], "question": "Your body typically processes how many drinks in one hour?", "answer": 1, "state": "nm", "type": "permit", "id": 75329}
{"candidates": ["May be crossed to enter or exit a private driveway.", "Should be treated as a separate traffic lane.", "May not be crossed for any reason."], "question": "When starting a vehicle with an automatic transmission, the shift selector should be in what position?", "answer": 2, "state": "nm", "type": "permit", "id": 75390}
{"candidates": ["Increase your chances of an accident.", "Help prevent traffic congestion.", "Get you to your destination much faster and safer."], "question": "When passing parked vehicles on your motorcycle, what should you do?", "answer": 0, "state": "nm", "type": "permit", "id": 75450}
{"candidates": ["Leave a note on the vehicle.", "Both of the above.", "Report the accident without delay to the city police or, in unincorporated areas, to the CHP."], "question": "Drinking and driving is extremely dangerous and illegal. After consumption, how long does it take for alcohol to reach your brain?", "answer": 1, "state": "nm", "type": "permit", "id": 75451}
{"candidates": ["Stop. Yield to all cross traffic before crossing the intersection.", "Slow down and cross the intersection carefully.", "Stop before entering the intersection as long as you can do so safely."], "question": "How many seconds should you keep, at least, between your vehicle and the vehicle in front of you?", "answer": 1, "state": "nm", "type": "permit", "id": 75478}
{"candidates": ["Large trucks have bigger blind spots than most passenger vehicles.", "Blind spots can be checked by looking in your rear view mirrors.", "They are eliminated if you have one outside mirror on each side of the vehicle."], "question": "When must New Mexico motorcycle operators under 18 years of age wear a helmet?", "answer": 0, "state": "nm", "type": "permit", "id": 75510}
{"candidates": ["A maximum of 50 feet and a minimum of 15 feet from the nearest railroad track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 100 feet from the nearest track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 50 feet from the nearest track"], "question": "When merging into traffic, at what speed should you try to maintain your vehicle?", "answer": 0, "state": "nm", "type": "permit", "id": 75536}
{"candidates": ["When you entered the intersection on the green light.", "Under no circumstances.", "During rush hour traffic."], "question": "What does a green traffic light indicate?", "answer": 1, "state": "nm", "type": "permit", "id": 75659}
{"candidates": ["If there is property damage in excess of $750 or if there are any injuries.", "Only if you or the other driver is injured.", "Only if you are at fault."], "question": "Which of the following is true of stopping?", "answer": 0, "state": "nm", "type": "permit", "id": 75691}
{"candidates": ["5 to 10 MPH slower than the traffic on the freeway.", "At or near the same speed as the traffic on the freeway.", "The posted speed limit for traffic on the freeway."], "question": "Which of the following can happen when you are driving while tired?", "answer": 1, "state": "nm", "type": "permit", "id": 75748}
{"candidates": ["Avoid driving in the bicycle lane.", "Move toward the left side of your lane.", "Signal for 100 feet before turning."], "question": "What should you do in the event of brake failure?", "answer": 2, "state": "nm", "type": "permit", "id": 75781}
{"candidates": ["Turn on your high beam headlights to better see the vehicles ahead of you.", "Keep the instrument panel lights bright to be more visible to other\tdrivers.", "Drive slowly enough so you can stop within the area lighted by your headlights."], "question": "What are the majority of vehicle skids attributable to?", "answer": 2, "state": "nm", "type": "permit", "id": 75838}
{"candidates": ["Should be treated as a separate traffic lane.", "May be crossed to enter or exit a private driveway.", "May not be crossed for any reason."], "question": "How should a rider compensate for riding during the night?", "answer": 2, "state": "nm", "type": "permit", "id": 75956}
{"candidates": ["Yes, it is a good defensive driving technique.", "Yes, it is always safer than driving faster than other traffic.", "No, you can block traffic when you drive too slowly."], "question": "In city traffic, how far ahead of your vehicle should you look?", "answer": 2, "state": "nm", "type": "permit", "id": 75988}
{"candidates": ["Merge into another lane and try to go around the traffic.", "Enter the intersection and wait until traffic clears.", "Stay out of the intersection until traffic clears."], "question": "Which of the following is true concerning space to the side?", "answer": 2, "state": "nm", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 76111}
{"candidates": ["At or near the same speed as the traffic on the freeway.", "5 to 10 MPH slower than the traffic on the freeway.", "The posted speed limit for traffic on the freeway."], "question": "When driving past the scene of an accident that you are not involved in, what should you never do?", "answer": 0, "state": "nm", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 76200}
{"candidates": ["At least 30 feet but not more than 100 feet from the nearest track", "A maximum of 50 feet and a minimum of 15 feet from the nearest railroad track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 50 feet from the nearest track"], "question": "What vision do you need, in one eye, to be able to drive in New Mexico?", "answer": 1, "state": "nm", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 76201}
{"candidates": ["Get a new prescription for lenses or contacts.", "Sell or transfer your vehicle.", "Fail a smog test for your vehicle."], "question": "When parking your vehicle, what is the minimum distance you should park away from a fire hydrant?", "answer": 1, "state": "nm", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 76321}
{"candidates": ["Next to the broken line may pass.", "Next to the solid line may pass.", "In both directions may pass."], "question": "What does an orange sign in the shape of a diamond indicate on the road?", "answer": 0, "state": "ny", "type": "permit", "id": 77833}
{"candidates": ["Between 65 mph and 70 mph.", "No faster than 65 mph.", "70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic."], "question": "After you become a resident of the state, in order to remain legally licensed, you must apply for a New York State driver license within ____ after you establish you are a New York State resident.", "answer": 1, "state": "ny", "type": "permit", "id": 77835}
{"candidates": ["Slow down or stop, if necessary, and then make the turn.", "Stop before entering the right lane and let all other traffic go first.", "Signal and turn immediately."], "question": "Which of the following does the DMV not regulate?", "answer": 0, "state": "ny", "type": "permit", "id": 77922}
{"candidates": ["When there are no vehicles approaching nearby.", "Across two sets of solid double, yellow lines.", "On a one-way street on a green arrow."], "question": "Which of the following is an example of a chemical test to determine if you are intoxicated?", "answer": 0, "state": "ny", "type": "permit", "id": 77923}
{"candidates": ["30 mph", "20 mph", "25 mph"], "question": "What will happen if you leave the scene of a crash you are involved in and someone is injured?", "answer": 2, "state": "ny", "type": "permit", "id": 77926}
{"candidates": ["One lane of traffic is traveling faster than the other lanes.", "All vehicles are traveling about the same speed.", "One vehicle is traveling faster or slower than the flow of traffic."], "question": "What is the only effective method for reducing your BAC?", "answer": 2, "state": "ny", "type": "permit", "id": 77931}
{"candidates": ["A sign permits the turn.", "Traffic on the street moves to the right.", "Traffic on the street moves to the left."], "question": "In which situation would parking not be allowed?", "answer": 2, "state": "ny", "type": "permit", "id": 77961}
{"candidates": ["Your actions cannot result in a traffic citation.", "You can frustrate the other drivers and make them angry.", "You help reduce traffic congestion."], "question": "Which of the following is the class of license or a junior driver's license?", "answer": 1, "state": "ny", "type": "permit", "id": 77982}
{"candidates": ["Test your tires\u2019 traction while going uphill.", "Decrease the distance you look ahead of your vehicle.", "Avoid making fast turns and fast stops."], "question": "If you are over 21 and are convicted of alcohol or drug related violations in another state how long will your license be revoked for?", "answer": 2, "state": "ny", "type": "permit", "id": 77983}
{"candidates": ["Farther behind the truck than you would for a passenger vehicle.", "No more than one car length behind the truck so the driver can see you.", "Closely behind the truck in bad weather because the driver can see farther ahead."], "question": "Which of the following documents may be used to prove your age at the DMV?", "answer": 0, "state": "ny", "type": "permit", "id": 77985}
{"candidates": ["Across two sets of solid double, yellow lines.", "On a one-way street on a green arrow.", "When there are no vehicles approaching nearby."], "question": "How many auto accidents are there in New York yearly?", "answer": 2, "state": "ny", "type": "permit", "id": 78011}
{"candidates": ["Should be treated as a separate traffic lane.", "May be crossed to enter or exit a private driveway.", "May not be crossed for any reason."], "question": "What term is used to define a turn you make so you can proceed in the opposite direction?", "answer": 2, "state": "ny", "type": "permit", "id": 78016}
{"candidates": ["Carefully drive around the pedestrian.", "Stop and let the pedestrian cross the street.", "Make sure the pedestrian sees you, but continue driving."], "question": "If you are 18 or older when you pass your road test for a driver license, or obtain a license following revocation, you will be on probation for ____ months.", "answer": 1, "state": "ny", "type": "permit", "id": 78050}
{"candidates": ["They are eliminated if you have one outside mirror on each side of the vehicle.", "Large trucks have bigger blind spots than most passenger vehicles.", "Blind spots can be checked by looking in your rear view mirrors."], "question": "A BAC of more than ____ percent is legal evidence that you are impaired.", "answer": 1, "state": "ny", "type": "permit", "id": 78051}
{"candidates": ["Any lane (as long as it is safe)", "The lane in the center of the road.", "The lane closest to the left curb"], "question": "When driving at night, your vehicle's headlights will typically help you see ____ ahead.", "answer": 2, "state": "ny", "type": "permit", "id": 78074}
{"candidates": ["Signal and turn immediately.", "Stop before entering the right lane and let all other traffic go first.", "Slow down or stop, if necessary, and then make the turn."], "question": "You should use signals when ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "ny", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 78255}
{"candidates": ["During a heavy downpour.", "After it has been raining for awhile.", "The first rain after a dry spell."], "question": "When driving a motorcycle, you should rest at least every ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "ny", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 78260}
{"candidates": ["You can frustrate the other drivers and make them angry.", "Your actions cannot result in a traffic citation.", "You help reduce traffic congestion."], "question": "If you are caught driving under the influence, you may____.", "answer": 0, "state": "ny", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 78287}
{"candidates": ["At least 30 feet but not more than 50 feet from the nearest track", "A maximum of 50 feet and a minimum of 15 feet from the nearest railroad track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 100 feet from the nearest track"], "question": "In order to properly control your motorcycle you should ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "ny", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 78315}
{"candidates": ["Parallel with the pavement.", "Turned to the left (toward the street).", "Turned to the right (away from the street)."], "question": "On a road with several lanes, you should check ____ first to make sure it is clear.", "answer": 2, "state": "ny", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 78347}
{"candidates": ["Yes, it is always safer than driving faster than other traffic.", "Yes, it is a good defensive driving technique.", "No, you can block traffic when you drive too slowly."], "question": "When riding at night, you should have a ____ second following distance.", "answer": 2, "state": "ny", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 78350}
{"candidates": ["At all times.", "Only during school hours.", "Unless you do not see any children present."], "question": "If there is no vehicles present on the road where should you start when cornering a turn?", "answer": 0, "state": "ny", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 78376}
{"candidates": ["Drive slowly enough so you can stop within the area lighted by your headlights.", "Keep the instrument panel lights bright to be more visible to other\tdrivers.", "Turn on your high beam headlights to better see the vehicles ahead of you."], "question": "What required documents are needed when applying for a driver's license for the first time?", "answer": 0, "state": "nc", "type": "permit", "id": 79898}
{"candidates": ["Must merge into the bicycle lane before turning.", "May not enter the bicycle lane.", "Should only merge into the bicycle lane if you stop before turning."], "question": "What of the following is a requirement for transferring license plates?", "answer": 0, "state": "nc", "type": "permit", "id": 79899}
{"candidates": ["Traffic on the street moves to the left.", "Traffic on the street moves to the right.", "A sign permits the turn."], "question": "What is the cost for receiving a special identification card?", "answer": 0, "state": "nc", "type": "permit", "id": 79931}
{"candidates": ["Your wheels must be within 18 inches of the curb.", "Your front wheels must be turned toward the street.", "One of your rear wheels must touch the curb."], "question": "If you are under 18, a provisional licensee, and are convicted of a third moving violation in a 12-month period, how long may your license be suspended for in North Carolina?", "answer": 0, "state": "nc", "type": "permit", "id": 79957}
{"candidates": ["It is OK for small children to ride in the front passenger seat of your car.", "Use the rear-facing child restraint system in the front passenger seat.", "Small children should ride in the back seat."], "question": "What should you NOT do in the event of a tire blowout while operating your motor vehicle?", "answer": 2, "state": "nc", "type": "permit", "id": 80021}
{"candidates": ["Stop and let him/her finish crossing the street.", "Slow down as you pass him/her.", "Make eye contact and then pass him/her."], "question": "How many inches of fast moving water can sweep a car off the highway during flood conditions?", "answer": 0, "state": "nc", "type": "permit", "id": 80108}
{"candidates": ["Unless you are in a limousine.", "Unless the vehicle was built before 1978.", "When the vehicle is equipped with seat belts."], "question": "When your license is up for renewal, the DMV will mail you a reminder card to renew it this many days in advance?", "answer": 2, "state": "nc", "type": "permit", "id": 80109}
{"candidates": ["Cannot see the vehicle directly to your right.", "See the vehicle\u2019s headlights in your rear view mirror.", "Have passed the other vehicle\u2019s front bumper."], "question": "What is the minimum fine if convicted of littering from a motor vehicle if it is your first offense?", "answer": 1, "state": "nc", "type": "permit", "id": 80166}
{"candidates": ["Next to the broken line may pass.", "Next to the solid line may pass.", "In both directions may pass."], "question": "What is the minimum fine fee for a driver who fails to yield to a pedestrian in areas where the driver turns right in any intersection?", "answer": 0, "state": "nc", "type": "permit", "id": 80171}
{"candidates": ["When the vehicle is equipped with seat belts.", "Unless you are in a limousine.", "Unless the vehicle was built before 1978."], "question": "It is important for bicyclists to go ____ of traffic.", "answer": 0, "state": "nc", "type": "permit", "id": 80198}
{"candidates": ["Yes, it is always safer than driving faster than other traffic.", "Yes, it is a good defensive driving technique.", "No, you can block traffic when you drive too slowly."], "question": "A motorcycle learner permit is valid for how long?", "answer": 2, "state": "nc", "type": "permit", "id": 80319}
{"candidates": ["That only vehicles next to the broken line may pass.", "That vehicles may pass in all directions.", "That vehicles next to the solid yellow line may pass."], "question": "When backing up your vehicle, what is the maximum speed your vehicle should achieve?", "answer": 0, "state": "nc", "type": "permit", "id": 80320}
{"candidates": ["The posted speed limit for traffic on the freeway.", "5 to 10 MPH slower than the traffic on the freeway.", "At or near the same speed as the traffic on the freeway."], "question": "What level full provisional license must a person have to operate a motorcycle?", "answer": 2, "state": "nc", "type": "permit", "id": 80379}
{"candidates": ["The other side of the road is a solid line.", "The other side of the road is a broken line.", "Your side of the road is a broken line."], "question": "When driving over an uneven surface, it is important to approach it at a ____ degree angle if possible.", "answer": 2, "state": "nc", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 80441}
{"candidates": ["Next to the solid line may pass.", "Next to the broken line may pass.", "In both directions may pass."], "question": "Where will speed limit signs typically be found?", "answer": 1, "state": "nd", "type": "permit", "id": 82109}
{"candidates": ["Use hands-free devices so you can keep both hands on the steering wheel.", "Review the number before answering a call.", "Keep your phone within easy reach so you won't need to take your eyes off the road."], "question": "Where in your vehicle can you have an open container of alcohol?", "answer": 0, "state": "nd", "type": "permit", "id": 82168}
{"candidates": ["5 to 10 MPH slower than the traffic on the freeway.", "The posted speed limit for traffic on the freeway.", "At or near the same speed as the traffic on the freeway."], "question": "What does a yellow traffic light mean?", "answer": 2, "state": "nd", "type": "permit", "id": 82171}
{"candidates": ["Only if you or the other driver is injured.", "If there is property damage in excess of $750 or if there are any injuries.", "Only if you are at fault."], "question": "What level of light transmittance is required on a tinted windshield?", "answer": 1, "state": "nd", "type": "permit", "id": 82316}
{"candidates": ["Sell or transfer your vehicle.", "Get a new prescription for lenses or contacts.", "Fail a smog test for your vehicle."], "question": "All turn signals should be given what distance before a turn?", "answer": 0, "state": "nd", "type": "permit", "id": 82351}
{"candidates": ["Turned to the left (toward the street).", "Turned to the right (away from the street).", "Parallel with the pavement."], "question": "Even if it is not dark, you should use your headlights when visibility is less than ____ due to rain, sleet, snow, or anything else that compromises visibility.", "answer": 1, "state": "nd", "type": "permit", "id": 82379}
{"candidates": ["The first rain after a dry spell.", "After it has been raining for awhile.", "During a heavy downpour."], "question": "What is the penalty for littering on a public highway?", "answer": 0, "state": "nd", "type": "permit", "id": 82380}
{"candidates": ["Slow to 25 MPH and pass cautiously.", "Stop as long as the red lights are flashing.", "Stop, then proceed when you think all of the children have exited the bus."], "question": "Your chances of being killed during a crash are ____ if you are throw from a vehicle.", "answer": 1, "state": "nd", "type": "permit", "id": 82381}
{"candidates": ["Your wheels must be within 18 inches of the curb.", "Your front wheels must be turned toward the street.", "One of your rear wheels must touch the curb."], "question": "When turning, the rear wheels follow a ____ path than the front.", "answer": 0, "state": "nd", "type": "permit", "id": 82440}
{"candidates": ["When you are within 200 feet of a cross street where you plan to turn right.", "When you want to pass a driver ahead of you who is turning right.", "During rush hour traffic if there are no bicyclists in the bike lane."], "question": "What should you do when it is raining on the roadway?", "answer": 0, "state": "nd", "type": "permit", "id": 82441}
{"candidates": ["Stop, listen, and proceed cautiously.", "Slowly pass vehicles that seem to be stopped for no reason.", "Look to the sides of your vehicle to see what is coming."], "question": "How should you handle driving on a road with a snow plow?", "answer": 2, "state": "nd", "type": "permit", "id": 82499}
{"candidates": ["Be prepared for workers and equipment ahead.", "Slow down because the lane ends ahead.", "Change lanes and maintain your current speed."], "question": "If you are under the age of ____, you must have a parent or legal guardian with you when appearing before the testing examiner.", "answer": 0, "state": "nd", "type": "permit", "id": 82590}
{"candidates": ["A speed just below the posted speed limit.", "A speed which matches the flow of traffic.", "The posted speed limit."], "question": "What day of the year does your driver's license expire?", "answer": 1, "state": "nd", "type": "permit", "id": 82709}
{"candidates": ["Assume the other driver will let you pass if you use your turn signal.", "Not assume the other driver will make space for you to return to your lane.", "Assume the other driver will maintain a constant speed."], "question": "What are standard colors for pedestrian signs?", "answer": 1, "state": "nd", "type": "permit", "id": 82767}
{"candidates": ["On the side of the freeway in an emergency.", "Next to a red painted curb.", "Within 100 feet of an elementary school."], "question": "____, in addition to alcohol and illegal drugs, can have very negative effects on the body that impair your ability to drive.", "answer": 1, "state": "nd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 82831}
{"candidates": ["Blind spots can be checked by looking in your rear view mirrors.", "Large trucks have bigger blind spots than most passenger vehicles.", "They are eliminated if you have one outside mirror on each side of the vehicle."], "question": "Vehicles moving slower than the flow of traffic:", "answer": 1, "state": "oh", "type": "permit", "id": 84619}
{"candidates": ["Stop, then proceed when you think all of the children have exited the bus.", "Slow to 25 MPH and pass cautiously.", "Stop as long as the red lights are flashing."], "question": "Which of the following is not a valid way to deal with fatigue while driving?", "answer": 2, "state": "oh", "type": "permit", "id": 84621}
{"candidates": ["25 mph", "20 mph", "15 mph"], "question": "When two cars arrive simultaneously at an intersection with no traffic signal or stop sign, who has the right of way?", "answer": 2, "state": "oh", "type": "permit", "id": 84671}
{"candidates": ["Need a large enough gap to get up to the speed of traffic.", "Should wait for the first two vehicles to pass, then drive into the lane.", "Should drive slower than other traffic for 200 feet."], "question": "What is the standard representation of \"no\" on a prohibitory sign?", "answer": 0, "state": "oh", "type": "permit", "id": 84677}
{"candidates": ["That only vehicles next to the broken line may pass.", "That vehicles next to the solid yellow line may pass.", "That vehicles may pass in all directions."], "question": "When following a Mail carrier vehicle all traffic laws regarding ____ and ____ apply.", "answer": 0, "state": "oh", "type": "permit", "id": 84768}
{"candidates": ["Parking lights", "Interior lights", "Headlights."], "question": "Which of the following is not an item checked during inspection?", "answer": 2, "state": "oh", "type": "permit", "id": 84770}
{"candidates": ["15 to 20 seconds", "10 to 15 seconds", "5 to 10 seconds"], "question": "A yellow pennant-shaped sign is used to indicate:", "answer": 1, "state": "oh", "type": "permit", "id": 84799}
{"candidates": ["Look to the sides of your vehicle to see what is coming.", "Slowly pass vehicles that seem to be stopped for no reason.", "Stop, listen, and proceed cautiously."], "question": "A safety zone of what distance should be kept between a car and a bicyclist?", "answer": 0, "state": "oh", "type": "permit", "id": 84855}
{"candidates": ["In a bicycle lane.", "In an unmarked crosswalk", "Within three feet of a private driveway."], "question": "In which of the following cases are headlights required to be used?", "answer": 1, "state": "oh", "type": "permit", "id": 84856}
{"candidates": ["Slow down or stop, if necessary, and then make the turn.", "Stop before entering the right lane and let all other traffic go first.", "Signal and turn immediately."], "question": "When scoring the maneuverability test, which of the following is considered an automatic failure?", "answer": 0, "state": "oh", "type": "permit", "id": 84918}
{"candidates": ["Increase your chances of an accident.", "Help prevent traffic congestion.", "Get you to your destination much faster and safer."], "question": "The term \"E-check\" refers to:", "answer": 0, "state": "oh", "type": "permit", "id": 84921}
{"candidates": ["25 mph", "30 mph", "20 mph"], "question": "Which of the following vehicles do NOT require the driver to possess a commercial driver's license?", "answer": 0, "state": "oh", "type": "permit", "id": 85035}
{"candidates": ["During rush hour traffic.", "When you entered the intersection on the green light.", "Under no circumstances."], "question": "What should a pedestrian do before stepping foot on a public road or highway?", "answer": 2, "state": "oh", "type": "permit", "id": 85039}
{"candidates": ["Only if you or the other driver is injured.", "If there is property damage in excess of $750 or if there are any injuries.", "Only if you are at fault."], "question": "When is the greatest potential for problems between a motorcyclist and other vehicles?", "answer": 1, "state": "oh", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 85188}
{"candidates": ["25 mph", "15 mph", "20 mph"], "question": "When you are being passed by another vehicle, you should do what?", "answer": 1, "state": "oh", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 85189}
{"candidates": ["15", "5", "10"], "question": "Riding a motorcycle involves all of your ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "oh", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 85218}
{"candidates": ["Stop before entering the intersection and let all other traffic go first.", "Slow down or stop, only if necessary.", "Stop, then proceed when safe."], "question": "When driving a three-wheeled motorcycle, to prevent tipping, you should ____ before entering a curve.", "answer": 2, "state": "oh", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 85220}
{"candidates": ["Interior lights", "Headlights.", "Parking lights"], "question": "To protect your face, your eye or face shield protection should ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "oh", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 85309}
{"candidates": ["Other drivers when merging onto a freeway.", "Other drivers when they want to slow down.", "The truck driver to stop the vehicle."], "question": "When are crashes among beginning riders fairly common?", "answer": 2, "state": "oh", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 85400}
{"candidates": ["May not be crossed for any reason.", "May be crossed to enter or exit a private driveway.", "Should be treated as a separate traffic lane."], "question": "You have to sit in jail for at least ____ days upon conviction of your 1st offense OVI or complete an intervention program of the same amount of days.", "answer": 0, "state": "oh", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 85427}
{"candidates": ["Loading zone for freight or passengers.", "Loading zone for freight only.", "Loading zone for passengers or mail only."], "question": "In which lane positions should you not ride in if the pavement is wet?", "answer": 2, "state": "oh", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 85429}
{"candidates": ["20 mph", "15 mph", "25 mph"], "question": "To ensure that your motorcycle isn't a source of trouble for you, you should do which of the following to familiarize yourself with it?", "answer": 1, "state": "oh", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 85457}
{"candidates": ["Keep your eyes moving to look for possible hazards.", "Look only at the car in front of you while driving.", "Always put one car length between you and the car ahead."], "question": "A ____ can happen if you brake too hard.", "answer": 0, "state": "oh", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 85521}
{"candidates": ["Low beams.", "Fog lights only.", "High beams."], "question": "If you are involved in a collision out of state and are not properly insured, what will happen to your license?", "answer": 0, "state": "ok", "type": "permit", "id": 86979}
{"candidates": ["Between 65 mph and 70 mph.", "No faster than 65 mph.", "70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic."], "question": "What color might a guide sign be?", "answer": 1, "state": "ok", "type": "permit", "id": 87010}
{"candidates": ["Need a large enough gap to get up to the speed of traffic.", "Should wait for the first two vehicles to pass, then drive into the lane.", "Should drive slower than other traffic for 200 feet."], "question": "It is a felony to use a fake id, what is the maximum amount of jail time for using a fake id?", "answer": 0, "state": "ok", "type": "permit", "id": 87129}
{"candidates": ["Cannot see the vehicle directly to your right.", "Have passed the other vehicle\u2019s front bumper.", "See the vehicle\u2019s headlights in your rear view mirror."], "question": "What colors are used on warning signs?", "answer": 2, "state": "ok", "type": "permit", "id": 87187}
{"candidates": ["Next to a red painted curb.", "On the side of the freeway in an emergency.", "Within 100 feet of an elementary school."], "question": "Your driver's license is the property of who?", "answer": 0, "state": "ok", "type": "permit", "id": 87191}
{"candidates": ["Farther behind the truck than you would for a passenger vehicle.", "Closely behind the truck in bad weather because the driver can see farther ahead.", "No more than one car length behind the truck so the driver can see you."], "question": "Where do you get your license from in Oklahoma?", "answer": 0, "state": "ok", "type": "permit", "id": 87249}
{"candidates": ["The truck driver to stop the vehicle.", "Other drivers when they want to slow down.", "Other drivers when merging onto a freeway."], "question": "What do flashing lights on a crossbuck mean?", "answer": 0, "state": "ok", "type": "permit", "id": 87310}
{"candidates": ["When you are within 200 feet of a cross street where you plan to turn right.", "When you want to pass a driver ahead of you who is turning right.", "During rush hour traffic if there are no bicyclists in the bike lane."], "question": "How many classroom hours must a student log while enrolled in a parent-taught driver education program?", "answer": 0, "state": "ok", "type": "permit", "id": 87399}
{"candidates": ["Stop as long as the red lights are flashing.", "Slow to 25 MPH and pass cautiously.", "Stop, then proceed when you think all of the children have exited the bus."], "question": "What is the minimum liability insurance for the injury or death of one person you must carry as a driver of the state of Oklahoma?", "answer": 0, "state": "ok", "type": "permit", "id": 87489}
{"candidates": ["A maximum of 50 feet and a minimum of 15 feet from the nearest railroad track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 100 feet from the nearest track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 50 feet from the nearest track"], "question": "In Oregon, traffic fines for all traffic offenses in construction, maintenance, and utility work zones are increased by a factor of:", "answer": 0, "state": "or", "type": "permit", "id": 89371}
{"candidates": ["Stop and let him/her finish crossing the street.", "Make eye contact and then pass him/her.", "Slow down as you pass him/her."], "question": "According to Oregon law, a driver needs to have his car's headlights turned on from sunset to sunrise. His car's headlights must also be turned on at any time conditions make it difficult for the driver to see pedestrians or vehicles ____ ahead.", "answer": 0, "state": "or", "type": "permit", "id": 89399}
{"candidates": ["Pass the construction zone carefully and not rubberneck.", "Decrease your following distance.", "Slow down to watch the workers."], "question": "What do historic, cultural, and recreational signs indicate in Oregon?", "answer": 0, "state": "or", "type": "permit", "id": 89429}
{"candidates": ["Between 65 mph and 70 mph.", "70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic.", "No faster than 65 mph."], "question": "Which of the following is true concerning overtaking and passing another vehicle?", "answer": 2, "state": "or", "type": "permit", "id": 89548}
{"candidates": ["Must merge into the bicycle lane before turning.", "May not enter the bicycle lane.", "Should only merge into the bicycle lane if you stop before turning."], "question": "A driver cannot stop, stand or park his vehicle within how many feet of a railroad track?", "answer": 0, "state": "or", "type": "permit", "id": 89578}
{"candidates": ["Assume the other driver will maintain a constant speed.", "Not assume the other driver will make space for you to return to your lane.", "Assume the other driver will let you pass if you use your turn signal."], "question": "You should communicate with other drivers by:", "answer": 1, "state": "or", "type": "permit", "id": 89638}
{"candidates": ["When the vehicle is equipped with seat belts.", "Unless the vehicle was built before 1978.", "Unless you are in a limousine."], "question": "What is the maximum street speed limit that officially designated slow moving vehicles can travel on?", "answer": 0, "state": "or", "type": "permit", "id": 89670}
{"candidates": ["Test your tires\u2019 traction while going uphill.", "Avoid making fast turns and fast stops.", "Decrease the distance you look ahead of your vehicle."], "question": "What portion of all traffic fatalities in Oregon are caused by driving under the influence?", "answer": 1, "state": "or", "type": "permit", "id": 89699}
{"candidates": ["Look to the sides of your vehicle to see what is coming.", "Slowly pass vehicles that seem to be stopped for no reason.", "Stop, listen, and proceed cautiously."], "question": "When are you required to use your turn signals?", "answer": 0, "state": "or", "type": "permit", "id": 89728}
{"candidates": ["25 mph", "20 mph", "15 mph"], "question": "When sharing the road with motorcycles, it is best to maintain a following distance of:", "answer": 2, "state": "or", "type": "permit", "id": 89759}
{"candidates": ["Stop. Yield to all cross traffic before crossing the intersection.", "Stop before entering the intersection as long as you can do so safely.", "Slow down and cross the intersection carefully."], "question": "Which of the following is true concerning the driver's role in regards to defensive driving?", "answer": 2, "state": "or", "type": "permit", "id": 89847}
{"candidates": ["Fail a smog test for your vehicle.", "Get a new prescription for lenses or contacts.", "Sell or transfer your vehicle."], "question": "Which of the following is a DMV test that you must pass to obtain your original license?", "answer": 2, "state": "or", "type": "permit", "id": 89910}
{"candidates": ["After it has been raining for awhile.", "The first rain after a dry spell.", "During a heavy downpour."], "question": "When should you flash your brake light?", "answer": 1, "state": "or", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 90001}
{"candidates": ["A maximum of 50 feet and a minimum of 15 feet from the nearest railroad track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 100 feet from the nearest track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 50 feet from the nearest track"], "question": "Which of the following are dangers when passing parked cars?", "answer": 0, "state": "or", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 90091}
{"candidates": ["Slow down or stop, only if necessary.", "Stop, then proceed when safe.", "Stop before entering the intersection and let all other traffic go first."], "question": "The word accident implies the event was ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "or", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 90149}
{"candidates": ["Parallel with the pavement.", "Turned to the left (toward the street).", "Turned to the right (away from the street)."], "question": "Traffic sensors are also called a ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "or", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 90181}
{"candidates": ["Small children should ride in the back seat.", "It is OK for small children to ride in the front passenger seat of your car.", "Use the rear-facing child restraint system in the front passenger seat."], "question": "SIPDE stands for Scan, Identify, Predict, Decide and ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "or", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 90301}
{"candidates": ["At or near the same speed as the traffic on the freeway.", "5 to 10 MPH slower than the traffic on the freeway.", "The posted speed limit for traffic on the freeway."], "question": "Being awake for 24 hours straight has the same effect on your driving as approximately what BAC level?", "answer": 0, "state": "pa", "type": "permit", "id": 91848}
{"candidates": ["Must stay in the right lane at all times while turning.", "May complete its turn in either of the two lanes.", "May have to swing wide to complete the right turn."], "question": "What is the maximum speed allowed if a person is riding in an open bed truck?", "answer": 2, "state": "pa", "type": "permit", "id": 91940}
{"candidates": ["Unless you do not see any children present.", "At all times.", "Only during school hours."], "question": "When there is a \"weaving lane\" for both entering and exiting cars on a highway, who has the right of way?", "answer": 1, "state": "pa", "type": "permit", "id": 91966}
{"candidates": ["Keep your eyes moving to look for possible hazards.", "Look only at the car in front of you while driving.", "Always put one car length between you and the car ahead."], "question": "What blood alcohol level results in being considered as driving under the influence for an adult?", "answer": 0, "state": "pa", "type": "permit", "id": 91970}
{"candidates": ["Any vehicle with 3 or more axles or weighing more than 4,000 pounds.", "Tank trucks marked with hazardous materials placards.", "Motor homes or pickup trucks towing a boat trailer."], "question": "What will you be fined if you do not use your windshield wipers when necessary?", "answer": 1, "state": "pa", "type": "permit", "id": 91998}
{"candidates": ["Should be treated as a separate traffic lane.", "May be crossed to enter or exit a private driveway.", "May not be crossed for any reason."], "question": "Which statement about parking is false?", "answer": 2, "state": "pa", "type": "permit", "id": 92091}
{"candidates": ["Assume the other driver will maintain a constant speed.", "Not assume the other driver will make space for you to return to your lane.", "Assume the other driver will let you pass if you use your turn signal."], "question": "Driver's who are turning left must yield to drivers doing what?", "answer": 1, "state": "pa", "type": "permit", "id": 92117}
{"candidates": ["After it has been raining for awhile.", "During a heavy downpour.", "The first rain after a dry spell."], "question": "What is the possible fine if you are the driver of a car convicted of littering from your car?", "answer": 2, "state": "pa", "type": "permit", "id": 92120}
{"candidates": ["Leave a note on the vehicle.", "Report the accident without delay to the city police or, in unincorporated areas, to the CHP.", "Both of the above."], "question": "What is the minimum fine amount for someone not disabled who parks in a disabled parking spot?", "answer": 2, "state": "pa", "type": "permit", "id": 92148}
{"candidates": ["15 to 20 seconds", "5 to 10 seconds", "10 to 15 seconds"], "question": "What should you always tell your passenger before starting to ride?", "answer": 2, "state": "pa", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 92299}
{"candidates": ["Not assume the other driver will make space for you to return to your lane.", "Assume the other driver will let you pass if you use your turn signal.", "Assume the other driver will maintain a constant speed."], "question": "If someone is following you too closely (sometimes called \"tailgating\"), what should you do?", "answer": 0, "state": "pa", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 92300}
{"candidates": ["5 to 10 MPH slower than the traffic on the freeway.", "At or near the same speed as the traffic on the freeway.", "The posted speed limit for traffic on the freeway."], "question": "Why should you keep a center position in your lane when driving a motorcycle?", "answer": 1, "state": "pa", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 92356}
{"candidates": ["10 to 15 seconds", "15 to 20 seconds", "5 to 10 seconds"], "question": "Most \"wobbles\" can be traced to what?", "answer": 0, "state": "pa", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 92388}
{"candidates": ["May complete its turn in either of the two lanes.", "May have to swing wide to complete the right turn.", "Must stay in the right lane at all times while turning."], "question": "How long after being consumed does alcohol reach the brain and start affecting the body?", "answer": 1, "state": "pa", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 92478}
{"candidates": ["Signal for 100 feet before turning.", "Move toward the left side of your lane.", "Avoid driving in the bicycle lane."], "question": "When you pull to a blind intersection, which lane position should you be in?", "answer": 0, "state": "pa", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 92540}
{"candidates": ["Within 100 feet of an elementary school.", "On the side of the freeway in an emergency.", "Next to a red painted curb."], "question": "Over ____ percent of car/motorcycle crashes are caused by driver's entering the rider's right of way.", "answer": 2, "state": "pa", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 92598}
{"candidates": ["Directly before and after school hours.", "You must always obey school crossing-guards.", "There are children present."], "question": "Which of the following should you do if you are pulled over?", "answer": 1, "state": "ri", "type": "permit", "id": 94240}
{"candidates": ["Stop before entering the intersection as long as you can do so safely.", "Slow down and cross the intersection carefully.", "Stop. Yield to all cross traffic before crossing the intersection."], "question": "How long does the driver education class run for?", "answer": 1, "state": "ri", "type": "permit", "id": 94361}
{"candidates": ["Slow down because the lane ends ahead.", "Change lanes and maintain your current speed.", "Be prepared for workers and equipment ahead."], "question": "Which of the following is a recommended way to control a vehicle in a skid?", "answer": 2, "state": "ri", "type": "permit", "id": 94419}
{"candidates": ["It is OK for small children to ride in the front passenger seat of your car.", "Small children should ride in the back seat.", "Use the rear-facing child restraint system in the front passenger seat."], "question": "If your out-of-state license is currently valid or has not been expired for more than ____, you will not be required to take a computerized test or a road test.", "answer": 1, "state": "ri", "type": "permit", "id": 94569}
{"candidates": ["Slow down or stop, only if necessary.", "Stop, then proceed when safe.", "Stop before entering the intersection and let all other traffic go first."], "question": "If you fail you road test, you must wait at least ____ days before re-taking the road test.", "answer": 1, "state": "ri", "type": "permit", "id": 94571}
{"candidates": ["Make eye contact and then pass him/her.", "Slow down as you pass him/her.", "Stop and let him/her finish crossing the street."], "question": "If you are backing greater than ____ feet, you should activate your hazard lights.", "answer": 2, "state": "ri", "type": "permit", "id": 94690}
{"candidates": ["At all times.", "Only during school hours.", "Unless you do not see any children present."], "question": "The law requires motorists to turn their headlights on any time you cannot see ____ feet ahead of you.", "answer": 0, "state": "ri", "type": "permit", "id": 94691}
{"candidates": ["Other drivers when merging onto a freeway.", "Other drivers when they want to slow down.", "The truck driver to stop the vehicle."], "question": "Any person of any age with a BAC of ____ is intoxicated and will be charged with drunk driving. Driving while intoxicated (DWI).", "answer": 2, "state": "ri", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 94840}
{"candidates": ["Only if you are at fault.", "If there is property damage in excess of $750 or if there are any injuries.", "Only if you or the other driver is injured."], "question": "You should perform a turnabout at least ____ feet from an intersection.", "answer": 1, "state": "ri", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 94990}
{"candidates": ["Drive in any lane.", "Drive in the right lane except to pass.", "Drive in the left lane except to pass."], "question": "You are driving on a road with two or more lanes traveling in the same direction. You should:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96551}
{"candidates": ["Come to a complete stop, yield to oncoming traffic or pedestrians, then proceed.", "Come to a complete stop and remain stopped as long as the light is red.", "Reduce your speed, and proceed with caution."], "question": "When approaching an intersection with a flashing red light you must:", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96560}
{"candidates": ["Over the left or right shoulder.", "Only the inside rearview mirror.", "Only the left outside mirror."], "question": "To see objects in your blind spot when changing lanes, drivers should check:", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96575}
{"candidates": ["Increase your speed so as not to cause an accident.", "Slow down and use your low beam headlights, and if fog is heavy, pull clear of the roadway and stop.", "Turn on your high beam headlights."], "question": "When faced with low visibility conditions due to fog while driving, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96576}
{"candidates": ["A construction zone is ahead.", "Passing is not permitted in either direction.", "Passing is permitted in either direction."], "question": "A broken yellow line in the center of the road indicates that:", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96579}
{"candidates": ["You should swing wide into the right lane when making a left turn.", "You cannot make a left turn at a red traffic light.", "When making a left turn onto a four lane roadway, finish the turn in the far right lane."], "question": "What statement about making a left turn is true?", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96606}
{"candidates": ["Toward the edge of the road.", "Away from the edge of the road.", "Leave them straight."], "question": "If you park facing up hill where there is NO curb, set the parking brake and turn the wheels:", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96607}
{"candidates": ["Use a firm but gentle grip on the steering wheel using your fingers and not your palms.", "All the others.", "Both hands placed on the outside of the steering wheel on opposite sides."], "question": "The proper method of steering is:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96636}
{"candidates": ["Steering with one hand.", "Speeding.", "Driving barefooted."], "question": "Which of the following is against the law and is punishable by imprisonment and / or fines?", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96637}
{"candidates": ["It is always permissible to drive the posted speed limit.", "The speed at which you are traveling affects almost everything else that can happen to you in a car.", "Heavy traffic situations do not affect speed."], "question": "Which statement about speed is true:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96640}
{"candidates": ["See the vehicle\u2019s headlights in your rear view mirror.", "Have passed the other vehicle\u2019s front bumper.", "Cannot see the vehicle directly to your right."], "question": "Which of the following will allow you to drive any single vehicle with a GVWR of 26,001 or more pounds, or any such vehicle towing a vehicle not in excess of 10,000 pounds GVWR?", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96659}
{"candidates": ["When you are within 200 feet of a cross street where you plan to turn right.", "When you want to pass a driver ahead of you who is turning right.", "During rush hour traffic if there are no bicyclists in the bike lane."], "question": "Where are guide signs used in South Carolina?", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96660}
{"candidates": ["Report the accident to the police within one week.", "Go to the nearest telephone and call for help.", "Stop / remain at the scene of the accident and move your vehicle to the shoulder of the road."], "question": "If you are involved in an accident, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96665}
{"candidates": ["Look toward the right edge of your lane.", "Look below the lights.", "Allow other driver to pass."], "question": "When a car with bright headlights comes toward you at night, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96694}
{"candidates": ["Only passengers and not the driver.", "All passengers, including the driver.", "Passengers on the driver's side of the car."], "question": "Who must wear seat belts in your vehicle:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96695}
{"candidates": ["Yield to any vehicle, bicycle, or pedestrian in the intersection.", "Wait four seconds before proceeding.", "Yield to pedestrians only in the intersection."], "question": "In South Carolina, if you are over 17 and under 65 years of age and obtain an original or renewal license at a SCDMV field office, how long is your license valid for?", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96716}
{"candidates": ["Away from the curb.", "Leave them straight.", "Toward the curb."], "question": "If you park facing up hill where there IS a curb, set the parking brake and turn the wheels:", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96724}
{"candidates": ["The speed at which you drive a vehicle does not affect safety.", "Driving too slowly on certain highways can be dangerous.", "Driving too slowly is not an unsafe practice."], "question": "Which statement is true about driving too slowly:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96726}
{"candidates": ["Walk around and check your vehicle, when inside adjust the seat and mirrors and fasten the safety belt before starting.", "Check fuel gauge, volume on the radio and gear shift.", "Start the engine, adjust the side mirror and check that the heater / defroster work."], "question": "Before you enter and start a parked vehicle, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96727}
{"candidates": ["A speed which matches the flow of traffic.", "A speed just below the posted speed limit.", "The posted speed limit."], "question": "You should never ride your bike when you are what?", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96747}
{"candidates": ["Parallel with the pavement.", "Turned to the left (toward the street).", "Turned to the right (away from the street)."], "question": "You have almost no chance of surviving a crash if you are traveling above:", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96749}
{"candidates": ["Drive only in the center of the roadway.", "Do not drive through the flooded area; turn around and find another route.", "Slam on the brakes."], "question": "If you find that the roadway ahead of you is flooded, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96757}
{"candidates": ["They are eliminated if you have one outside mirror.", "Large trucks have bigger blind spots than most passenger vehicles.", "Blind spots can be checked by looking in your rearview mirror."], "question": "Which of the following statements about blind spots is true:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96758}
{"candidates": ["Signal and move into the correct exit lane as soon as it is reached.", "All the others.", "Reduce speed to the posted exit speed."], "question": "When you see a sign indicating that your chosen exit point is nearing, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96759}
{"candidates": ["55mph", "60mph", "40mph"], "question": "The maximum un-posted speed limit when driving in a rural area is ____, except when a higher limit is allowed by federal law.", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96761}
{"candidates": ["The driver should give a hand signal to warn approaching traffic from the rear, that they intend to stop.", "Traffic checks are not necessary when backing up.", "Look straight ahead while backing."], "question": "Which statement about stopping on a roadway to perform a straight line backing maneuver is true?", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96762}
{"candidates": ["A vehicle pulling two trailers.", "A 3-axle vehicle if the Gross Vehicle Weight is less than 6,000 pounds.", "Any 3-axle vehicle regardless of the weight."], "question": "During the initial vehicle check, pressure loss should not exceed which psi amount for single vehicle?", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96778}
{"candidates": ["Red background / Green lettering", "Orange background / Black lettering", "Yellow background / Blue lettering"], "question": "The basic color for temporary signs in work zones used in construction and maintenance work areas have a(n) ____ background with ____ lettering:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96786}
{"candidates": ["You only have to stop if you see children crossing the street.", "You must stop for a school bus on any two-lane highway.", "You must stop for a school bus when the bus is in a passenger loading zone completely off the roadway."], "question": "Which statement about stopping for a school bus is true:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96788}
{"candidates": ["Signal, check mirror, and perform turnabout.", "Give your signal and perform three point turnabout.", "Signal, check mirrors, look over left shoulder(blind spot), perform turnabout when clear."], "question": "The correct way to execute a three point turnabout is:", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96792}
{"candidates": ["Always avoid driving beside a large vehicle for long periods of time.", "All the others.", "Trucks have a larger blind spot on the right side starting behind the cab and extending the length of the truck."], "question": "Which statement about side zones and commercial vehicles is true:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96796}
{"candidates": ["Report the accident the following week.", "Go to the nearest convenience store and call your insurance company.", "Protect the area, notify authorities, and care for the injured."], "question": "Which of the following is a basic step to take after an accident:", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96813}
{"candidates": ["Use your right foot for both braking and accelerating your vehicle.", "Using your left foot.", "You should brake hard always to ensure stopping."], "question": "Which statement of the proper braking method is true?", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96815}
{"candidates": ["Stop. Yield to all cross traffic before crossing the intersection.", "Stop before entering the intersection as long as you can do so safely.", "Slow down and cross the intersection carefully."], "question": "When should you use your seat belts?", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96840}
{"candidates": ["As your speed increases, so should your following distance.", "As speed increases, the chance of a fatality increases.", "All the others."], "question": "Which of these statements about speeding is true:", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96877}
{"candidates": ["Not permitted.", "Permitted on the left when the way ahead is clear.", "Permitted on the right when the way ahead is clear."], "question": "A broken yellow center line indicates that passing is:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96882}
{"candidates": ["When the shoulder is wide enough.", "If the vehicle ahead of you is turning left.", "Under no circumstance."], "question": "You should drive on the shoulder to pass a car only:", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96883}
{"candidates": ["Yield the right-of-way to cross traffic close enough to cause conflict.", "Slow down and proceed.", "Yield to those vehicles only on your right."], "question": "At intersections with a Yield sign, you must:", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96885}
{"candidates": ["Yield to oncoming traffic from both directions before performing the maneuver.", "Begin the exercise anyway.", "Flash your head lights and begin the exercise."], "question": "When planning to make a three point turnabout across a roadway, and you have oncoming traffic approaching, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96904}
{"candidates": ["5 to 10 MPH slower than the traffic on the freeway.", "At or near the same speed as the traffic on the freeway.", "The posted speed limit for traffic on the freeway."], "question": "What do the rules of the road include?", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96927}
{"candidates": ["When there are no vehicles approaching nearby.", "Across two sets of solid double, yellow lines.", "On a one-way street on a green arrow."], "question": "Which is the only eight sided octagonal sign you will see?", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96930}
{"candidates": ["Shift into a lower gear.", "Pull over to the side of the road.", "Turn on your headlights."], "question": "When it starts raining or snowing enough to turn on your windshield wipers, it is also time to:", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96932}
{"candidates": ["Slow down, and if you don't hear anything, drive around the gates.", "Drive through / around the crossing gates, if you don't see a train.", "Come to a complete stop well behind the gates, wait for the tracks to clear, and the gates to raise before proceeding."], "question": "If you come to a railroad crossing where the crossing gates are down and the lights are flashing, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96935}
{"candidates": ["Stop until the light turns yellow.", "Go through the intersection without stopping.", "Stop until the light turns green."], "question": "If you approach a traffic light with a red signal and a police officer directs you to go through the intersection without stopping, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96944}
{"candidates": ["Drinking caffeine", "Eating foods high in fat", "Time"], "question": "Only ____ can reduce the alcohol level and its effects on the body.", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96964}
{"candidates": ["Between 65 mph and 70 mph.", "70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic.", "No faster than 65 mph."], "question": "Which of the following is true concerning flooded roads?", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96991}
{"candidates": ["Are in the proper lane and the roadway is clear.", "Wait until the light changes.", "Make a complete stop first."], "question": "At a red traffic light with a green arrow, you may proceed in the direction of the arrow if you:", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96994}
{"candidates": ["Slow down and cross the intersection carefully.", "Yield to all traffic before crossing the intersection.", "Stop, then enter the intersection when it is safe to do so."], "question": "When you see a flashing yellow light at an intersection you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96996}
{"candidates": ["On a sidewalk.", "Within 100 feet of a driveway.", "Within 45 feet of a fire hydrant."], "question": "If you must park your vehicle, which location should you not park:", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 96997}
{"candidates": ["Over-inflated tires do not skid in wet weather.", "Tires must have good tread and be free of damage.", "Tires with low air pressure provide a smoother ride."], "question": "Which statement about vehicle tires is true:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97000}
{"candidates": ["Hit the breaks hard.", "Grip the steering wheel firmly, begin to slow down, then move slowly back onto the road surface.", "Hit the brakes firmly and jerk the steering wheel hard to pull the vehicle onto the road surface as quickly as possible."], "question": "When your wheels run off the pavement, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97029}
{"candidates": ["3-4 second minimum following distance.", "As speed increases following distance should decrease.", "Following distance is only important on snow and ice."], "question": "When establishing a proper following distance, you should practice the following:", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97034}
{"candidates": ["5 to 10 MPH slower than the traffic on the freeway.", "At or near the same speed as the traffic on the freeway.", "The posted speed limit for traffic on the freeway."], "question": "Which conditions may require a change of speed?", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97047}
{"candidates": ["It will make you more alert.", "It can make you unfit to drive.", "No effect one way or the other."], "question": "What is the likely effect of taking a prescription drug while drinking alcohol:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97059}
{"candidates": ["Turn your lights on and off to warn other drivers.", "Switch your lights to the high beam.", "Slow down and use your low beam headlights."], "question": "When driving and encountering fog, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97060}
{"candidates": ["Often a hazard since other drivers may become frustrated and try to pass you.", "Appropriate if you don\u2019t know the speed limit.", "A good idea if the weather is bad."], "question": "Driving more slowly than the surrounding traffic is:", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97062}
{"candidates": ["Make eye contact and then pass him/her.", "Slow down as you pass him/her.", "Stop and let him/her finish crossing the street."], "question": "Which of the following is an example of a traffic control device?", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97080}
{"candidates": ["May complete its turn in either of the two lanes.", "Must stay in the right lane at all times while turning.", "May have to swing wide to complete the right turn."], "question": "Which of the following is considered a moped under South Carolina law?", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97081}
{"candidates": ["You should put on your cruise control to maintain a constant speed.", "You must stop at a railroad crossing when directed by a flagman or stop sign.", "You have the right-of-way and do not need to stop."], "question": "Which statement about stopping at railroad grade crossings is true:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97084}
{"candidates": ["Never steer with just one hand except when backing or operating a vehicle control (wiper ,flashers, lights) that only requires a temporary reach from the steering wheel.", "All the others.", "Both hands should be placed on the outside of the steering wheel."], "question": "Which of these statements about steering a vehicle is true?", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97088}
{"candidates": ["A stimulant.", "A antihistamine.", "A depressant."], "question": "Alcohol is:", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97090}
{"candidates": ["Turn on your high beam headlights and continue.", "Turn on your four way flashers and continue.", "Reduce your speed, move as far to the right as possible, and stop off the roadway."], "question": "If you see the roadway up ahead is covered by heavy smoke, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97094}
{"candidates": ["Do not pass other cars often.", "Block other vehicles moving at normal, safe speeds.", "Drive at speeds less than 40 mph on any highway."], "question": "You are driving too slowly if you:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97095}
{"candidates": ["You can make a right turn at a red traffic light, unless a sign prohibits the turn.", "You should swing wide to the left when making a right turn so you won't run over the curb.", "When making a right turn onto a four lane roadway, finish the turn in the far left lane."], "question": "What statement about making a right turn is true?", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97113}
{"candidates": ["Permitted on the right.", "Not allowed in either direction.", "Permitted on the left."], "question": "When double solid yellow lines mark the center of the road and separates oncoming traffic, passing is:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97119}
{"candidates": ["Always put one car length between you and the car ahead.", "Keep your eyes moving to look for possible hazards.", "Look only at the car in front of you while driving."], "question": "In case of mechanical signal failure on your vehicle, what is the proper hand signal to display for indicating intent to make a left turn?", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97141}
{"candidates": ["Right lane", "Center lane", "Left lane"], "question": "On a four lane highway slower traffic should drive in the ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97144}
{"candidates": ["On or near any curve or hill.", "In a parking lot.", "On a straight-a-way with a clear view of 500 feet in both directions."], "question": "A U-Turn is not permitted:", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97147}
{"candidates": ["All the others.", "Where there is a red light.", "At an intersection where a police officer orders you to stop."], "question": "You are required to stop your vehicle:", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97150}
{"candidates": ["Only if pedestrians are in the crosswalk.", "At a point that it is clear to see in all directions.", "At the line."], "question": "When a stop line is present at a stop sign, drivers must stop:", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97174}
{"candidates": ["The lane in the center of the road.", "Any lane (as long as it is safe)", "The lane closest to the left curb"], "question": "What in a vehicle will remind you to buckle up?", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97200}
{"candidates": ["Move toward the left side of your lane.", "Avoid driving in the bicycle lane.", "Signal for 100 feet before turning."], "question": "What must you provide to apply for a South Carolina credential if you are an international customer?", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97201}
{"candidates": ["Permitted on the side of the broken yellow line.", "Permitted on the side of the solid yellow line.", "Not permitted in either direction."], "question": "A broken yellow line beside a solid yellow line indicates that passing is:", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97204}
{"candidates": ["Drive on the right side of large vehicles when going up and down hills.", "Always avoid driving beside a large vehicle for long periods at a time.", "Follow the large vehicle closely to reduce wind drag on your vehicle."], "question": "If you are approaching a large commercial vehicle from the rear on an interstate, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97209}
{"candidates": ["Have sufficient space when traveling behind trucks and when consistent speed has been maintained by the car when passing trucks.", "Try to squeeze around the truck when the truck makes a wide turn and when several car lengths have been left between the large truck and car.", "Disappear into blind spots or are so close they restrict the truck driver's ability to stop or maneuver safely."], "question": "No Zones' are areas around trucks where cars:", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "permit", "id": 97212}
{"candidates": ["All the time", "Between sunset and sunrise", "Only when it is dark outside"], "question": "When should headlights be turned on?", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 97268}
{"candidates": ["Must contain hearing protection", "Must be reflectorized", "Must be colored yellow"], "question": "A helmet for a person 21 and under:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 97269}
{"candidates": ["In a staggered position", "In single-file formation", "Side-by-side"], "question": "When riding in a group, how should motorcycle drivers ride?", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 97311}
{"candidates": ["50", "100", "75"], "question": "What should you do if there are traffic officers around?", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 97410}
{"candidates": ["Need a large enough gap to get up to the speed of traffic.", "Should drive slower than other traffic for 200 feet.", "Should wait for the first two vehicles to pass, then drive into the lane."], "question": "Most accidents occur on:", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 97439}
{"candidates": ["Always take them at a 90 degree angle", "Speed up", "Take them as they come in the roadway"], "question": "To safely cross railroad tracks, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 97444}
{"candidates": ["Parallel with the pavement.", "Turned to the right (away from the street).", "Turned to the left (toward the street)."], "question": "Drivers should inspect their vehicles:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 97469}
{"candidates": ["May not enter the bicycle lane.", "Must merge into the bicycle lane before turning.", "Should only merge into the bicycle lane if you stop before turning."], "question": "What does a broken yellow line indicate?", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 97471}
{"candidates": ["Between 65 mph and 70 mph.", "70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic.", "No faster than 65 mph."], "question": "To obtain an identification card in South Carolina, you must be a resident of the state and at least how many years old?", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 97527}
{"candidates": ["Share a lane with a small truck", "Use a lane of traffic without sharing it", "Share a lane with a car"], "question": "Motorcyclea are allowed to:", "answer": 1, "state": "sc", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 97535}
{"candidates": ["Yes, it is a good defensive driving technique.", "Yes, it is always safer than driving faster than other traffic.", "No, you can block traffic when you drive too slowly."], "question": "If you have a medical condition which department may require you provide medical reports before your license is issued?", "answer": 2, "state": "sc", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 97555}
{"candidates": ["To the left portion of the lane", "To the center of the lane", "To the far right of the lane"], "question": "When riding in a group, where should the leader go after passing a vehicle?", "answer": 0, "state": "sc", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 97600}
{"candidates": ["May be crossed to enter or exit a private driveway.", "Should be treated as a separate traffic lane.", "May not be crossed for any reason."], "question": "If your license is revoked or suspended because of a first time Driving While Intoxicated, you will have to pay a reinstatement fee of ____ dollars.", "answer": 2, "state": "sd", "type": "permit", "id": 99201}
{"candidates": ["Under no circumstances.", "When you entered the intersection on the green light.", "During rush hour traffic."], "question": "You must contact the police if there is property damage of $____ or more to one person's property.", "answer": 0, "state": "sd", "type": "permit", "id": 99260}
{"candidates": ["You can frustrate the other drivers and make them angry.", "Your actions cannot result in a traffic citation.", "You help reduce traffic congestion."], "question": "After the age of 21, South Dakota licenses are valid for how many years at a time?", "answer": 0, "state": "sd", "type": "permit", "id": 99288}
{"candidates": ["When there are no vehicles approaching nearby.", "Across two sets of solid double, yellow lines.", "On a one-way street on a green arrow."], "question": "If your gas pedal sticks, which of the following should you do?", "answer": 0, "state": "sd", "type": "permit", "id": 99380}
{"candidates": ["Between 65 mph and 70 mph.", "No faster than 65 mph.", "70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic."], "question": "If you are a male between the ages of 18 and ____ you must register for the Selective Service.", "answer": 1, "state": "sd", "type": "permit", "id": 99439}
{"candidates": ["Change lanes and maintain your current speed.", "Be prepared for workers and equipment ahead.", "Slow down because the lane ends ahead."], "question": "If you have antilock brakes, which of the following should you do to stop quickly?", "answer": 1, "state": "sd", "type": "permit", "id": 99441}
{"candidates": ["Transporting an unrestrained animal inside the vehicle.", "Listening to music through headphones that cover both ears", "Adjusting your outside mirrors."], "question": "Warning signs typically use what color scheme?", "answer": 1, "state": "sd", "type": "permit", "id": 99492}
{"candidates": ["The railroad crossing is located in a city or town that has frequent train traffic.", "You do not have room on the other side to completely cross the tracks.", "You transport two or more young children in a passenger vehicle."], "question": "What is required of a vehicle operator in order to give authorities consent to an alcohol chemical test in South Dakota?", "answer": 1, "state": "sd", "type": "permit", "id": 99555}
{"candidates": ["100", "50", "75"], "question": "All the following need to be checked regularly for safety purposes, except:", "answer": 0, "state": "sd", "type": "permit", "id": 99557}
{"candidates": ["Any 3-axle vehicle regardless of the weight.", "A vehicle pulling two trailers.", "A 3-axle vehicle if the Gross Vehicle Weight is less than 6,000 pounds."], "question": "What is the safest lane position on a multi-lane road?", "answer": 2, "state": "sd", "type": "permit", "id": 99561}
{"candidates": ["Listening to music through headphones that cover both ears", "Transporting an unrestrained animal inside the vehicle.", "Adjusting your outside mirrors."], "question": "What is the safest way to handle curves in the road?", "answer": 0, "state": "sd", "type": "permit", "id": 99617}
{"candidates": ["Tank trucks marked with hazardous materials placards.", "Motor homes or pickup trucks towing a boat trailer.", "Any vehicle with 3 or more axles or weighing more than 4,000 pounds."], "question": "To check if you are driving too fast, you should use the ____ second sight distance rule.", "answer": 0, "state": "sd", "type": "permit", "id": 99621}
{"candidates": ["Turn on your high beam headlights to better see the vehicles ahead of you.", "Drive slowly enough so you can stop within the area lighted by your headlights.", "Keep the instrument panel lights bright to be more visible to other\tdrivers."], "question": "To get a driver's license without restrictions, you must have vision better than 20 over ____ with both eyes.", "answer": 1, "state": "sd", "type": "permit", "id": 99647}
{"candidates": ["The grips cannot be higher than shoulder height of the person riding", "The grips should not be lower than the shoulder height of the person riding", "The grips cannot be higher than the waist of the person riding"], "question": "How high can handlebars be positioned?", "answer": 0, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99690}
{"candidates": ["The outside of the curve", "The inside of the curve", "The center of the curve"], "question": "Where should you position your motorcycle when entering a curve?", "answer": 2, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99703}
{"candidates": ["You help reduce traffic congestion.", "You can frustrate the other drivers and make them angry.", "Your actions cannot result in a traffic citation."], "question": "One alcoholic drink can be eliminated from the body in ____ hours.", "answer": 1, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99741}
{"candidates": ["Use the front brake only", "Use both brakes", "Use the rear brake first"], "question": "The best way to stop quickly is to", "answer": 1, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99750}
{"candidates": [".08 percent", ".12 percent", ".04 percent"], "question": "Drivers with a Blood Alcohol Concentration of ____ or more of alcohol is considered legally intoxicated", "answer": 0, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99756}
{"candidates": ["It will have a label attached to the helmet stating the certification", "It will have a green dot inside the helmet", "DOT-certified helmets are the only type of helmet sold in North America"], "question": "How can you tell if a helmet is DOT certified?", "answer": 0, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99806}
{"candidates": ["16", "18", "14"], "question": "What is the minimum age to get a driver's license?", "answer": 2, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99812}
{"candidates": ["20 mph", "25 mph", "15 mph"], "question": "Keeping distance around your motorcycle provides which of the following?", "answer": 2, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99831}
{"candidates": ["The number of drinks", "How fast you drink", "How frequently you drink"], "question": "Which of the following is not a factor in how quickly a person\u2019s Blood Alcohol Concentration increases when consuming alcohol?", "answer": 2, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99835}
{"candidates": ["Dry surfaces", "Shiny surfaces", "Dirt and gravel"], "question": "Slippery surfaces can include all of the following except:", "answer": 0, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99849}
{"candidates": ["Motorcycles need less distance than cars", "Motorcycles need more distance than cars", "Motorcycles need about the same amount of distance as cars"], "question": "When stopping:", "answer": 2, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99851}
{"candidates": ["Use only the rear brake", "Increase speed", "Avoid sudden moves"], "question": "When driving on a slippery surface, you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99854}
{"candidates": ["Riders under age 18", "All riders", "Riders who have had their license for less than two years"], "question": "Helmets are required for:", "answer": 0, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99857}
{"candidates": ["0.08", "0.04", "0.02"], "question": "People under 21, can be arrested for and alcohol Blood Alcohol Concentration of ____ percent or omore", "answer": 2, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99867}
{"candidates": ["Riders under the age 18", "Riders on a motorcycle with a person who has had their license less than two years", "All riders"], "question": "Eye protection is required for:", "answer": 2, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99895}
{"candidates": ["Time to react", "Space to maneuver", "A chance to show off your riding skills"], "question": "Using an adequate cushion of space, allows all of the following, except:", "answer": 2, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99905}
{"candidates": ["Illegal", "Allowed when stopped at traffic control devices", "Allowed when there is minimal traffic"], "question": "Texting and driving is:", "answer": 0, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99916}
{"candidates": ["Wear bright colored clothing", "Follow other vehicles closely", "Wear dark colored clothing"], "question": "To increase your chances of being seen, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99918}
{"candidates": ["Maximum of 50", "Maximum of 10", "Maximum of 20"], "question": "How many cc's can a moped have?", "answer": 0, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99927}
{"candidates": ["2", "3", "4"], "question": "How many seconds should you follow behind another vehicle?", "answer": 2, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99960}
{"candidates": ["At least one rear view mirror", "A horn", "A yellow stoplight"], "question": "All of the following are required equipment for a motorcycle, except:", "answer": 2, "state": "sd", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 99970}
{"candidates": ["continue to the next intersection to make the desired turn", "signal the direction you want to go and wait for a gap", "stop and wait until the way is clear before turning"], "question": "At an intersection with traffic signals, if you are not in the proper lane to make a right or left turn you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101383}
{"candidates": ["50 feet", "75 feet", "25 feet"], "question": "Before making a turn, the driver should use the turn signal at what distance before the turn?", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101385}
{"candidates": ["within one foot", "within 18 inches", "within two feet"], "question": "In parallel parking, the wheels should be how far from the curb?", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101387}
{"candidates": ["48 Hours", "10 Days", "20 Days"], "question": "If involved in a reportable accident, the operator of the vehicle must file an accident report to the Department of Safety within:", "answer": 2, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101392}
{"candidates": ["6-11", "8-10", "12 or more"], "question": "An advisory letter is mailed to a licensee having how many points on a driving record within any twelve months:", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101397}
{"candidates": ["Slow down to calm your nerves.", "Stop and look for your own curiosity.", "Drive on and do not interfere with procedures."], "question": "If you are not the first at the scene of accident and your help is not needed, what should you do:", "answer": 2, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101416}
{"candidates": ["Speeds up to 55 m.p.h.", "Speeds up to 30 m.p.h.", "Any speed."], "question": "The two-second rule for following at a safe distance will hold true at:", "answer": 2, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101417}
{"candidates": ["45 days", "10 days", "6 months"], "question": "If you change your address, Tennessee law requires you to notify the Department of Safety within:", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101420}
{"candidates": ["rectangles", "squares", "diamonds"], "question": "Special laws, regulations or important information is provided on signs in the shape of:", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101424}
{"candidates": ["Stop, then proceed when safe.", "Stop before entering the intersection and let all other traffic go first.", "Slow down or stop, only if necessary."], "question": "What symbol is used to indicate \"don't walk\" for pedestrians?", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101438}
{"candidates": ["They are eliminated if you have one outside mirror on each side of the vehicle.", "Blind spots can be checked by looking in your rear view mirrors.", "Large trucks have bigger blind spots than most passenger vehicles."], "question": "In which of the following situations is it okay to NOT drive on the right side of the road?", "answer": 2, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101441}
{"candidates": ["at least 50 feet", "as soon as you decide to turn", "at least 100 feet"], "question": "How far ahead should you signal your intentions to turn?", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101443}
{"candidates": ["If asked, you will take a test to determine alcohol or drug content in the blood.", "If asked, you will take a test to determine alcohol or drug content in the blood.", "The laws apply even without any signs, markings or signals present at an intersection."], "question": "Implied Consent Law means:", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101450}
{"candidates": ["both a and b", "within 15 feet of a fire hydrant", "within 50 feet of a railroad crossing"], "question": "It is illegal to park:", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101451}
{"candidates": ["see at least 500 feet in each direction", "make the turn within 30 seconds", "drive on the shoulder of the road"], "question": "It is illegal to turn around near a curve or hill when the driver cannot:", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101452}
{"candidates": ["If people weigh the same amount, the one with more body fat will show signs of intoxication first", "Drinking three drinks in one hour affects you just the same as drinking three drinks in three hours", "The more a person weighs, the more alcohol it takes to raise their BAC"], "question": "Select the statement below that is false:", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101453}
{"candidates": ["tap your brakes lightly and shift into neutral", "steer to the left", "steer to the right"], "question": "If you are driving and the rear end of your car starts skidding to the left, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101455}
{"candidates": ["When there are no vehicles approaching nearby.", "On a one-way street on a green arrow.", "Across two sets of solid double, yellow lines."], "question": "What color are all service signs?", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101496}
{"candidates": ["slow down and yield the right-of-way", "slow down and drive carefully", "come to a complete stop, check the traffic and go on when it is safe"], "question": "You are coming to an intersection with a flashing red light. You should:", "answer": 2, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101507}
{"candidates": ["Two hours", "Three hours", "One hour"], "question": "If you have had three beers in the past hour, about how long will it take for all the alcohol to leave your blood stream?", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101533}
{"candidates": ["7", "3", "5"], "question": "If you have a BAC of .10%, you are ____ times more likely to cause an accident than if you were sober.", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101540}
{"candidates": ["turning into the wrong lane", "speeding", "following too closely"], "question": "A major cause of fatal traffic accidents in Tennessee is:", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101547}
{"candidates": ["slower traffic must keep to the right", "if you miss your exit you must go to the next exit", "change lanes without signaling"], "question": "Which of the following is not considered safe driving on an interstate system?", "answer": 2, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101548}
{"candidates": ["If there is property damage in excess of $750 or if there are any injuries.", "Only if you are at fault.", "Only if you or the other driver is injured."], "question": "Lane control signals may appear over each lane on a road. If a lane is closed or driving is not permitted in that lane, which signal will be shown?", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101560}
{"candidates": ["stop", "one way", "do not enter"], "question": "What message will be found on a red octagon shaped sign?", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101568}
{"candidates": ["Any 3-axle vehicle regardless of the weight.", "A vehicle pulling two trailers.", "A 3-axle vehicle if the Gross Vehicle Weight is less than 6,000 pounds."], "question": "Judgment is affected by which type of people who drink alcohol?", "answer": 2, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101588}
{"candidates": ["Not assume the other driver will make space for you to return to your lane.", "Assume the other driver will let you pass if you use your turn signal.", "Assume the other driver will maintain a constant speed."], "question": "If you lose your privilege to drive, you must turn in your license within____ days.", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101617}
{"candidates": ["taxis", "farm trucks hauling produce", "school or church buses"], "question": "Which of the following vehicles are not required to stop before crossing any railroad grade crossing?", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101627}
{"candidates": ["55 mph", "65 mph", "45 mph"], "question": "Unless otherwise posted, the speed limit on primary and secondary state and federal highways is:", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101628}
{"candidates": ["5 days in jail", "45 days in jail", "20 days in jail"], "question": "The DUI law states that upon a second conviction the violator will serve not less than:", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101629}
{"candidates": ["6 to 8 inches", "18 to 24 inches", "10 to 12 inches"], "question": "When adjusting the driver\u2019s seat for best driving posture, set the seat in an upright position where your body is about how far from the steering wheel?", "answer": 2, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101630}
{"candidates": ["Have a complete awareness of higher speed driving", "Constant alertness by the driver", "All the others."], "question": "Interstate driving demands require the driver to:", "answer": 2, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101631}
{"candidates": ["Only if you are at fault.", "If there is property damage in excess of $750 or if there are any injuries.", "Only if you or the other driver is injured."], "question": "Out of all motor vehicles, ____ are the most vulnerable.", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101644}
{"candidates": ["Stop before entering the intersection as long as you can do so safely.", "Slow down and cross the intersection carefully.", "Stop. Yield to all cross traffic before crossing the intersection."], "question": "The only substance that is acceptable to drive while under the influence of is:", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101649}
{"candidates": ["The other side of the road is a solid line.", "The other side of the road is a broken line.", "Your side of the road is a broken line."], "question": "How long must an Intermediate Restricted License be held?", "answer": 2, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101651}
{"candidates": ["stop until the light changes to green", "complete the turn when traffic clears", "back out of the intersection, if possible"], "question": "If the light turns red when you are in the middle of an intersection about to turn left, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101655}
{"candidates": ["five or more", "at least four", "eight or more"], "question": "Slow moving vehicles shall turn or pull off the roadway when there are how many vehicles in line behind them?", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101657}
{"candidates": ["If the shoulder is wide enough to accommodate your vehicle", "Under no circumstances", "If the vehicle ahead of you is turning left."], "question": "Every ____ days a teen is killed and seven are injured in a work zone crash in this country according to NETS.", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101673}
{"candidates": ["Drive slowly enough so you can stop within the area lighted by your headlights.", "Keep the instrument panel lights bright to be more visible to other\tdrivers.", "Turn on your high beam headlights to better see the vehicles ahead of you."], "question": "Establishing proof of residency in Tennessee requires applicants to provide ____ proof documents.", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101676}
{"candidates": ["Prepare to yield to oncoming traffic.", "All the others.", "Protected left turn is about to end."], "question": "What does a traffic signal with a yellow left arrow indicate to the driver?", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101682}
{"candidates": ["a depressant", "neither of the above", "a stimulant"], "question": "Alcohol in any concentration is:", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101721}
{"candidates": ["be charged with vehicular homicide", "All the others.", "if convicted, be fined and sentenced to a term in prison"], "question": "If you are operating a motor vehicle while under the influence of a drug or alcohol and you are involved in a crash that results in a death of another person(s), you may:", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101752}
{"candidates": ["Increase your chances of an accident.", "Help prevent traffic congestion.", "Get you to your destination much faster and safer."], "question": "What is one action you should not take to avoid road rage?", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101769}
{"candidates": ["2 years", "4 years", "3 years"], "question": "Tennessee was the first state to pass a child restraint law. This law requires that children under the age of ____ must be placed in an approved child restraint device.", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101774}
{"candidates": ["a $100.00 fine, 24 hours in jail and 6 months revocation", "a $350.00 fine, 48 hours in jail and 1 year revocation", "a $500.00 fine, 12 hours in jail and 3 months revocation"], "question": "The DUI law states that upon first conviction the penalty will be:", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101781}
{"candidates": ["A lesser penalty than for alcohol.", "Absolutely no penalty at all.", "The same penalty as for alcohol"], "question": "Driving while under the influence of drugs carries:", "answer": 2, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101784}
{"candidates": ["Frequent convictions of traffic law violations resulting in 12 or more \u201cpoints\u201d", "All the others.", "Fraudulently altering a driver license"], "question": "A driver license may be revoked or suspended for:", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101808}
{"candidates": ["7 o\u2019clock and 5 o\u2019clock positions", "11 o\u2019clock and 6 o\u2019clock positions", "9 o\u2019clock and 3 o\u2019clock positions"], "question": "The driver should drive with both hands on the steering wheel approximately in the:", "answer": 2, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101810}
{"candidates": ["50%", "0.05%", "0.08%"], "question": "Driving under the influence (DUI) for a first conviction is determined by which blood alcohol concentration?", "answer": 2, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101834}
{"candidates": ["always make a lane change", "look for a destination sign to follow", "go the direction of the arrow"], "question": "When seeing a sign over your lane with an arrow and the word \"only\" below it you should:", "answer": 2, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101839}
{"candidates": ["have decreased", "have increased", "have remained steady"], "question": "Special studies show that all fatal crashes involving alcohol in Tennessee:", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101868}
{"candidates": ["Your wheels must be within 18 inches of the curb.", "Your front wheels must be turned toward the street.", "One of your rear wheels must touch the curb."], "question": "What are the main colors of traffic signals?", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101889}
{"candidates": ["consist of a good foot brake and an \"emergency\" or \"parking\" brake", "not lock under any condition", "consist of a good \"parking\" brake that is capable of stopping the vehicle within legal limits"], "question": "By law, the brakes on every vehicle (other than a motorcycle) must:", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101893}
{"candidates": ["turn into any lane", "turn into first lane", "turn into second lane"], "question": "When turning left from a two-way street onto a one-way street, you should:", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101899}
{"candidates": ["Making a U-Turn when you missed your exit.", "Turning around when no others are present.", "Emergency vehicles and highway maintenance crews only."], "question": "Emergency crossovers on the interstate are legal in Tennessee for:", "answer": 2, "state": "tn", "type": "permit", "id": 101923}
{"candidates": ["0.1", "0.08", "0.04"], "question": "Having a Blood Alcohol Content of ____ or more is considered to be legally intoxicated.", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 101952}
{"candidates": ["Are optional without a windshield", "Must be worn if your motorcycle does not have a windshield", "Must be worn if you are under 21 years of age"], "question": "Goggles, glasses with impact resistant lenses or a helmet with a windshield:", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 102004}
{"candidates": ["A rearview mirror mounted on the left handlebar", "A rear view mirror only if the driver is younger than 21 years old", "A rearview mirror mounted on the right handlebar"], "question": "All motorcycles must have:", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 102005}
{"candidates": ["Your license will be suspended for 12 months", "Your license will be suspended for 3 months", "Your license will be suspended for 6 months"], "question": "If a law enforcement officer pulls you over and suspects you have been drinking, what happens if you refuse a breath test?", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 102099}
{"candidates": ["2", "3", "1"], "question": "You should use a following distance of ____ seconds.", "answer": 0, "state": "tn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 102214}
{"candidates": ["Should not be used", "Cannot be driven on a public roadway", "Should be driven on the shoulder of roadways"], "question": "A motorized vehicle with 45 or less cc's:", "answer": 1, "state": "tn", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 102223}
{"candidates": ["Parallel with the pavement.", "Turned to the right (away from the street).", "Turned to the left (toward the street)."], "question": "The Texas Driver's Handbook indicates \"6 Keys to Safe Driving.\" Which of the following is NOT a \"key\" to safe driving according to the Texas Driver's Handbook specific list?", "answer": 1, "state": "tx", "type": "permit", "id": 103709}
{"candidates": ["Only if you see orange cones on the road ahead.", "At all times.", "Unless they conflict with existing signs, signals, or laws."], "question": "What is the required minimum liability insurance coverage?", "answer": 1, "state": "tx", "type": "permit", "id": 103740}
{"candidates": ["Stop, then proceed when safe.", "Stop before entering the intersection and let all other traffic go first.", "Slow down or stop, only if necessary."], "question": "What is the maximum fine for a first offense of driving intoxicated while being a minor?", "answer": 0, "state": "tx", "type": "permit", "id": 103797}
{"candidates": ["Between 65 mph and 70 mph.", "70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic.", "No faster than 65 mph."], "question": "A \"4-WAY\" sign added to a stop sign at an intersection indicates ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "tx", "type": "permit", "id": 103828}
{"candidates": ["Yield to pedestrians only in the intersection.", "Wait four seconds before proceeding.", "Yield to any vehicle, bicycle, or pedestrian in the intersection."], "question": "What is the maximum length of a connector between a vehicle and the one it is towing?", "answer": 2, "state": "tx", "type": "permit", "id": 103859}
{"candidates": ["All vehicles are traveling about the same speed.", "One lane of traffic is traveling faster than the other lanes.", "One vehicle is traveling faster or slower than the flow of traffic."], "question": "One may not operate an open bed truck with a person under ____ years of age in the bed.", "answer": 2, "state": "tx", "type": "permit", "id": 103886}
{"candidates": ["Slow down to watch the workers.", "Pass the construction zone carefully and not rubberneck.", "Decrease your following distance."], "question": "In which case would it be a violation to either park or let a vehicle stand idling?", "answer": 1, "state": "tx", "type": "permit", "id": 103890}
{"candidates": ["At least 30 feet but not more than 50 feet from the nearest track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 100 feet from the nearest track", "A maximum of 50 feet and a minimum of 15 feet from the nearest railroad track"], "question": "You must file a written report to the Department of Transportation no longer than ____ days after the crash if the crash has resulted in more than $1000 worth of damage.", "answer": 2, "state": "tx", "type": "permit", "id": 104040}
{"candidates": ["When there are no vehicles approaching nearby.", "On a one-way street on a green arrow.", "Across two sets of solid double, yellow lines."], "question": "What is the duration of the validity of a Commercial Driver's License (CDL)?", "answer": 0, "state": "tx", "type": "permit", "id": 104070}
{"candidates": ["Need a large enough gap to get up to the speed of traffic.", "Should wait for the first two vehicles to pass, then drive into the lane.", "Should drive slower than other traffic for 200 feet."], "question": "An emissions test must be performed on any vehicle from 2 to ____ years old to be registered or operated in a designated county.", "answer": 0, "state": "tx", "type": "permit", "id": 104099}
{"candidates": ["Slow down and cross the intersection carefully.", "Stop before entering the intersection as long as you can do so safely.", "Stop. Yield to all cross traffic before crossing the intersection."], "question": "Mandatory suspensions, revocations and convictions of certain offenses involving fraudulent government records require an additional fee of how much?", "answer": 0, "state": "tx", "type": "permit", "id": 104101}
{"candidates": ["Get a new prescription for lenses or contacts.", "Sell or transfer your vehicle.", "Fail a smog test for your vehicle."], "question": "Good, experienced drivers use the three-step strategy SEE: Search, Evaluate, Execute. Using the SEE strategy will help you search for which of the following factors?", "answer": 1, "state": "tx", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 104280}
{"candidates": ["The other side of the road is a broken line.", "The other side of the road is a solid line.", "Your side of the road is a broken line."], "question": "Beginning riders should position themselves ____ the group while the group rides.", "answer": 2, "state": "tx", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 104281}
{"candidates": ["The lane closest to the left curb", "Any lane (as long as it is safe)", "The lane in the center of the road."], "question": "If you find yourself with a stuck throttle, you should do what?", "answer": 0, "state": "tx", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 104338}
{"candidates": ["A speed just below the posted speed limit.", "A speed which matches the flow of traffic.", "The posted speed limit."], "question": "To obtain your license you must pass which test?", "answer": 1, "state": "tx", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 104427}
{"candidates": ["Slow down as you pass him/her.", "Make eye contact and then pass him/her.", "Stop and let him/her finish crossing the street."], "question": "The greatest risk for a group is ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "tx", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 104430}
{"candidates": ["Turned to the right (away from the street).", "Turned to the left (toward the street).", "Parallel with the pavement."], "question": "A minimum of how many seconds in distance should be kept behind the vehicle ahead?", "answer": 0, "state": "tx", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 104431}
{"candidates": ["May complete its turn in either of the two lanes.", "May have to swing wide to complete the right turn.", "Must stay in the right lane at all times while turning."], "question": "If arriving at a four-way intersection at the same time as another vehicle, who has the right-of-way?", "answer": 1, "state": "ut", "type": "permit", "id": 105946}
{"candidates": ["Carefully drive around the pedestrian.", "Stop and let the pedestrian cross the street.", "Make sure the pedestrian sees you, but continue driving."], "question": "How long will the driving test take?", "answer": 1, "state": "ut", "type": "permit", "id": 105950}
{"candidates": ["You can frustrate the other drivers and make them angry.", "Your actions cannot result in a traffic citation.", "You help reduce traffic congestion."], "question": "When must you make a complete stop?", "answer": 0, "state": "ut", "type": "permit", "id": 105977}
{"candidates": ["When the vehicle is equipped with seat belts.", "Unless you are in a limousine.", "Unless the vehicle was built before 1978."], "question": "What should you do when turning right in a continuous flow intersection?", "answer": 0, "state": "ut", "type": "permit", "id": 105979}
{"candidates": ["One lane of traffic is traveling faster than the other lanes.", "One vehicle is traveling faster or slower than the flow of traffic.", "All vehicles are traveling about the same speed."], "question": "Which is a place where you would be allowed to park?", "answer": 1, "state": "ut", "type": "permit", "id": 106011}
{"candidates": ["Low beams.", "High beams.", "Fog lights only."], "question": "Physicians are responsible for:", "answer": 0, "state": "ut", "type": "permit", "id": 106071}
{"candidates": ["Interior lights", "Parking lights", "Headlights."], "question": "Of the following, who may not have a Utah driver's license?", "answer": 2, "state": "ut", "type": "permit", "id": 106099}
{"candidates": ["Only if you are at fault.", "If there is property damage in excess of $750 or if there are any injuries.", "Only if you or the other driver is injured."], "question": "If you drive on a suspended license, you can be jailed up to ____ days.", "answer": 1, "state": "ut", "type": "permit", "id": 106191}
{"candidates": ["Loading zone for passengers or mail only.", "Loading zone for freight only.", "Loading zone for freight or passengers."], "question": "Being convicted of a felony DUI will result in a ____ ignition interlock device restriction.", "answer": 0, "state": "ut", "type": "permit", "id": 106310}
{"candidates": ["Unless you do not see any children present.", "At all times.", "Only during school hours."], "question": "If you are involved in a crash and do not stop, you may lose your license for up to ____ year(s).", "answer": 1, "state": "ut", "type": "permit", "id": 106338}
{"candidates": ["Get you to your destination much faster and safer.", "Help prevent traffic congestion.", "Increase your chances of an accident."], "question": "SEE helps increase awareness on the road and stands for:", "answer": 2, "state": "ut", "type": "permit", "id": 106399}
{"candidates": ["25 mph", "30 mph", "20 mph"], "question": "When you wish to change lanes, you must:", "answer": 0, "state": "ut", "type": "permit", "id": 106400}
{"candidates": ["At or near the same speed as the traffic on the freeway.", "The posted speed limit for traffic on the freeway.", "5 to 10 MPH slower than the traffic on the freeway."], "question": "You must register your vehicle if it is a:", "answer": 0, "state": "ut", "type": "permit", "id": 106488}
{"candidates": ["Any 3-axle vehicle regardless of the weight.", "A vehicle pulling two trailers.", "A 3-axle vehicle if the Gross Vehicle Weight is less than 6,000 pounds."], "question": "Which of the following are possible restrictions that may be placed on your driver's license?", "answer": 2, "state": "ut", "type": "permit", "id": 106490}
{"candidates": ["It is OK for small children to ride in the front passenger seat of your car.", "Use the rear-facing child restraint system in the front passenger seat.", "Small children should ride in the back seat."], "question": "Alcohol reaches your brain within ____ minutes of consumption.", "answer": 2, "state": "ut", "type": "permit", "id": 106491}
{"candidates": ["Should wait for the first two vehicles to pass, then drive into the lane.", "Need a large enough gap to get up to the speed of traffic.", "Should drive slower than other traffic for 200 feet."], "question": "Where should your seat be while operating a motorcycle?", "answer": 1, "state": "ut", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 106820}
{"candidates": ["Report the accident without delay to the city police or, in unincorporated areas, to the CHP.", "Leave a note on the vehicle.", "Both of the above."], "question": "Skills tests are not available between the months of November and ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "vt", "type": "permit", "id": 108334}
{"candidates": ["Small children should ride in the back seat.", "Use the rear-facing child restraint system in the front passenger seat.", "It is OK for small children to ride in the front passenger seat of your car."], "question": "If someone uses a counterfeit license, their license will be suspended for ____ days.", "answer": 0, "state": "vt", "type": "permit", "id": 108335}
{"candidates": ["Need a large enough gap to get up to the speed of traffic.", "Should drive slower than other traffic for 200 feet.", "Should wait for the first two vehicles to pass, then drive into the lane."], "question": "The Real Id Act set verification standards for which of the following?", "answer": 0, "state": "vt", "type": "permit", "id": 108369}
{"candidates": ["Stop and let him/her finish crossing the street.", "Slow down as you pass him/her.", "Make eye contact and then pass him/her."], "question": "A series of white triangles painted on the roadway, pointing towards oncoming traffic, is used to indicate which of the following?", "answer": 0, "state": "vt", "type": "permit", "id": 108370}
{"candidates": ["Unless the vehicle was built before 1978.", "Unless you are in a limousine.", "When the vehicle is equipped with seat belts."], "question": "Which of the following choices is a bad example of being a responsible pedestrian?", "answer": 2, "state": "vt", "type": "permit", "id": 108371}
{"candidates": ["Not assume the other driver will make space for you to return to your lane.", "Assume the other driver will let you pass if you use your turn signal.", "Assume the other driver will maintain a constant speed."], "question": "Vehicles older than how many years require an odometer statement signed by both the seller and the buyer?", "answer": 0, "state": "vt", "type": "permit", "id": 108431}
{"candidates": ["Keep your eyes moving to look for possible hazards.", "Look only at the car in front of you while driving.", "Always put one car length between you and the car ahead."], "question": "How far in advance should you signal before making a left hand turn?", "answer": 0, "state": "vt", "type": "permit", "id": 108488}
{"candidates": ["Your wheels must be within 18 inches of the curb.", "One of your rear wheels must touch the curb.", "Your front wheels must be turned toward the street."], "question": "What are the times you may drive with a learner's permit?", "answer": 0, "state": "vt", "type": "permit", "id": 108489}
{"candidates": ["In a bicycle lane.", "Within three feet of a private driveway.", "In an unmarked crosswalk"], "question": "A Vermont license expired over how many days is deemed an invalid license?", "answer": 2, "state": "vt", "type": "permit", "id": 108521}
{"candidates": ["Leave a note on the vehicle.", "Report the accident without delay to the city police or, in unincorporated areas, to the CHP.", "Both of the above."], "question": "The knowledge test has 20 questions. You must answer correctly how many questions in order to pass?", "answer": 2, "state": "vt", "type": "permit", "id": 108547}
{"candidates": ["At least 30 feet but not more than 100 feet from the nearest track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 50 feet from the nearest track", "A maximum of 50 feet and a minimum of 15 feet from the nearest railroad track"], "question": "You should observe more than how many seconds of following distance when following a motorcycle?", "answer": 2, "state": "vt", "type": "permit", "id": 108606}
{"candidates": ["Should drive slower than other traffic for 200 feet.", "Should wait for the first two vehicles to pass, then drive into the lane.", "Need a large enough gap to get up to the speed of traffic."], "question": "Which of the following is not a common vehicle caused collision with bicycles?", "answer": 2, "state": "vt", "type": "permit", "id": 108609}
{"candidates": ["That only vehicles next to the broken line may pass.", "That vehicles next to the solid yellow line may pass.", "That vehicles may pass in all directions."], "question": "Which of the follow should you always do before starting your vehicle at night?", "answer": 0, "state": "vt", "type": "permit", "id": 108611}
{"candidates": ["The other side of the road is a solid line.", "The other side of the road is a broken line.", "Your side of the road is a broken line."], "question": "When are you legally required to obey a flagger directing traffic?", "answer": 2, "state": "vt", "type": "permit", "id": 108727}
{"candidates": ["Within the distance you can see ahead.", "Within the distance lighted by your parking lights.", "Within 5-10 seconds."], "question": "What are the conditions in which the vehicle you are using for the road test must meet?", "answer": 0, "state": "vt", "type": "permit", "id": 108759}
{"candidates": ["The other side of the road is a broken line.", "The other side of the road is a solid line.", "Your side of the road is a broken line."], "question": "During the road test, the examiner may ask you to do which of the following?", "answer": 2, "state": "vt", "type": "permit", "id": 108790}
{"candidates": ["Must merge into the bicycle lane before turning.", "Should only merge into the bicycle lane if you stop before turning.", "May not enter the bicycle lane."], "question": "What are the requirements to obtain a junior driver's license in Vermont?", "answer": 0, "state": "vt", "type": "permit", "id": 108813}
{"candidates": ["The posted speed limit.", "A speed just below the posted speed limit.", "A speed which matches the flow of traffic."], "question": "The course layout for a two-wheel rider skill test is ____ feet long.", "answer": 2, "state": "vt", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 109061}
{"candidates": ["Transporting an unrestrained animal inside the vehicle.", "Adjusting your outside mirrors.", "Listening to music through headphones that cover both ears"], "question": "You are not required to wear face or eye protection if you have ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "vt", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 109091}
{"candidates": ["Unless the vehicle was built before 1978.", "When the vehicle is equipped with seat belts.", "Unless you are in a limousine."], "question": "Deer can bolt up to speeds of ____ mph if they are startled.", "answer": 1, "state": "vt", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 109119}
{"candidates": ["Only if you or the other driver is injured.", "Only if you are at fault.", "If there is property damage in excess of $750 or if there are any injuries."], "question": "Who or what organization is responsible for maintaining a driving record of all convictions received from the court for Virginia residents?", "answer": 2, "state": "va", "type": "permit", "id": 110699}
{"candidates": ["Within 5-10 seconds.", "Within the distance you can see ahead.", "Within the distance lighted by your parking lights."], "question": "How many feet before a turn should you turn on your turn signal?", "answer": 1, "state": "va", "type": "permit", "id": 110731}
{"candidates": ["Any vehicle with 3 or more axles or weighing more than 4,000 pounds.", "Tank trucks marked with hazardous materials placards.", "Motor homes or pickup trucks towing a boat trailer."], "question": "Over-correcting occurs when ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "va", "type": "permit", "id": 110783}
{"candidates": ["Within 5-10 seconds.", "Within the distance you can see ahead.", "Within the distance lighted by your parking lights."], "question": "If you are convicted of driving after illegally consuming alcohol, and your BAC was at least .02 percent and less than .08, the court penalty will include a suspension of your driving privilege for ____ from the date of conviction.", "answer": 1, "state": "va", "type": "permit", "id": 110790}
{"candidates": ["May complete its turn in either of the two lanes.", "May have to swing wide to complete the right turn.", "Must stay in the right lane at all times while turning."], "question": "If you have a school bus driver's license, but not a commercial driver's license, what are the maximum amount of occupants you can carry on the bus?", "answer": 1, "state": "va", "type": "permit", "id": 110817}
{"candidates": ["That only vehicles next to the broken line may pass.", "That vehicles may pass in all directions.", "That vehicles next to the solid yellow line may pass."], "question": "What should you do if stopped by a police officer?", "answer": 0, "state": "va", "type": "permit", "id": 110819}
{"candidates": ["Slow down or stop, only if necessary.", "Stop before entering the intersection and let all other traffic go first.", "Stop, then proceed when safe."], "question": "Which of the following does not hold true for roundabouts?", "answer": 2, "state": "va", "type": "permit", "id": 110879}
{"candidates": ["A sign permits the turn.", "Traffic on the street moves to the left.", "Traffic on the street moves to the right."], "question": "What is the maximum speed limit for passenger vehicles on rural rustic roads?", "answer": 1, "state": "va", "type": "permit", "id": 110908}
{"candidates": ["Under no circumstances.", "During rush hour traffic.", "When you entered the intersection on the green light."], "question": "After you move, how soon must you change your address with the DMV?", "answer": 0, "state": "va", "type": "permit", "id": 110998}
{"candidates": ["50", "75", "100"], "question": "You should never make a U-Turn ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "va", "type": "permit", "id": 111027}
{"candidates": ["Should drive slower than other traffic for 200 feet.", "Should wait for the first two vehicles to pass, then drive into the lane.", "Need a large enough gap to get up to the speed of traffic."], "question": "Which of the following is true regarding a license suspension for child support related requirements?", "answer": 2, "state": "va", "type": "permit", "id": 111085}
{"candidates": ["Required", "Not required if you have had your motorcycle license for more than two years", "Not required, but recommended"], "question": "A helmet is", "answer": 0, "state": "va", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 111098}
{"candidates": ["1 second", "3 seconds", "2 seconds"], "question": "When traveling as a group in a staggered formation, how much distance should there be between the lead rider and the rider directly behind them?", "answer": 1, "state": "va", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 111139}
{"candidates": ["The first rain after a dry spell.", "During a heavy downpour.", "After it has been raining for awhile."], "question": "You can help a friend who has been drinking by ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "va", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 111150}
{"candidates": ["At least 30 feet but not more than 100 feet from the nearest track", "A maximum of 50 feet and a minimum of 15 feet from the nearest railroad track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 50 feet from the nearest track"], "question": "One out of every ____ crashes ends up resulting neck or head injuries.", "answer": 1, "state": "va", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 111236}
{"candidates": ["Not required", "Required", "Only required if the driver is wearing a helmet"], "question": "For a passenger, a helmet is", "answer": 1, "state": "va", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 111244}
{"candidates": ["If the roadway has more than one lane", "If there is little traffic", "If the pavement is slippery from rain or snow"], "question": "What would be a situation where you would want to increase your minimum following distance to 4 seconds?", "answer": 2, "state": "va", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 111266}
{"candidates": ["Your actions cannot result in a traffic citation.", "You help reduce traffic congestion.", "You can frustrate the other drivers and make them angry."], "question": "Someone under the age of 21 with a BAC of no more than ____% will have their license suspended.", "answer": 2, "state": "va", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 111269}
{"candidates": ["A 3-axle vehicle if the Gross Vehicle Weight is less than 6,000 pounds.", "Any 3-axle vehicle regardless of the weight.", "A vehicle pulling two trailers."], "question": "You should position yourself ____ before a curve.", "answer": 0, "state": "va", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 111301}
{"candidates": ["A 3-axle vehicle if the Gross Vehicle Weight is less than 6,000 pounds.", "A vehicle pulling two trailers.", "Any 3-axle vehicle regardless of the weight."], "question": "When turning, you should shift gears ____ you turn if necessary.", "answer": 0, "state": "va", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 111329}
{"candidates": ["Your front wheels must be turned toward the street.", "One of your rear wheels must touch the curb.", "Your wheels must be within 18 inches of the curb."], "question": "Safe riders try to ride less than ____ hours a day.", "answer": 2, "state": "va", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 111389}
{"candidates": ["Carefully drive around the pedestrian.", "Make sure the pedestrian sees you, but continue driving.", "Stop and let the pedestrian cross the street."], "question": "How soon must you notify the Department of Licensing if you change your address or name?", "answer": 2, "state": "wa", "type": "permit", "id": 112821}
{"candidates": ["Yes, it is always safer than driving faster than other traffic.", "No, you can block traffic when you drive too slowly.", "Yes, it is a good defensive driving technique."], "question": "What should you do if you want to parallel park, but vehicles are approaching behind you?", "answer": 1, "state": "wa", "type": "permit", "id": 112848}
{"candidates": ["Listening to music through headphones that cover both ears", "Transporting an unrestrained animal inside the vehicle.", "Adjusting your outside mirrors."], "question": "How many days do you have to comply after receiving a notice of suspension for a failure to appear?", "answer": 0, "state": "wa", "type": "permit", "id": 112850}
{"candidates": ["Loading zone for passengers or mail only.", "Loading zone for freight only.", "Loading zone for freight or passengers."], "question": "If your steering wheel were a clock, where should your left and right hands should, respectively, be positioned?", "answer": 0, "state": "wa", "type": "permit", "id": 112908}
{"candidates": ["Traffic on the street moves to the right.", "Traffic on the street moves to the left.", "A sign permits the turn."], "question": "A probationary license is required for how long if you are convicted of operating a vehicle while under the influence?", "answer": 1, "state": "wa", "type": "permit", "id": 112909}
{"candidates": ["Must stay in the right lane at all times while turning.", "May complete its turn in either of the two lanes.", "May have to swing wide to complete the right turn."], "question": "What is something you should NOT do if your tire blows out?", "answer": 2, "state": "wa", "type": "permit", "id": 112910}
{"candidates": ["May not enter the bicycle lane.", "Should only merge into the bicycle lane if you stop before turning.", "Must merge into the bicycle lane before turning."], "question": "Which of the following is true concerning replacement licenses?", "answer": 2, "state": "wa", "type": "permit", "id": 112995}
{"candidates": ["Help prevent traffic congestion.", "Increase your chances of an accident.", "Get you to your destination much faster and safer."], "question": "Which of the following is a type of driver license in the state of Washington?", "answer": 1, "state": "wa", "type": "permit", "id": 113028}
{"candidates": ["Keep the instrument panel lights bright to be more visible to other\tdrivers.", "Turn on your high beam headlights to better see the vehicles ahead of you.", "Drive slowly enough so you can stop within the area lighted by your headlights."], "question": "Which of the following nonresidents would NOT be allowed to drive in Washington without getting a Washington driver's license?", "answer": 2, "state": "wa", "type": "permit", "id": 113056}
{"candidates": ["Get a new prescription for lenses or contacts.", "Sell or transfer your vehicle.", "Fail a smog test for your vehicle."], "question": "When would you have to receive a restriction on your license for corrective lenses?", "answer": 1, "state": "wa", "type": "permit", "id": 113057}
{"candidates": ["Should drive slower than other traffic for 200 feet.", "Need a large enough gap to get up to the speed of traffic.", "Should wait for the first two vehicles to pass, then drive into the lane."], "question": "What about a traffic sign tells you what type of sign it is?", "answer": 1, "state": "wa", "type": "permit", "id": 113058}
{"candidates": ["Slowly pass vehicles that seem to be stopped for no reason.", "Look to the sides of your vehicle to see what is coming.", "Stop, listen, and proceed cautiously."], "question": "What is a danger of stopping quickly?", "answer": 1, "state": "wa", "type": "permit", "id": 113059}
{"candidates": ["25 mph", "20 mph", "30 mph"], "question": "When entering traffic you need to allow yourself enough space to do what?", "answer": 0, "state": "wa", "type": "permit", "id": 113087}
{"candidates": ["Stop before entering the right lane and let all other traffic go first.", "Slow down or stop, if necessary, and then make the turn.", "Signal and turn immediately."], "question": "Which statement about pavement markings is NOT correct?", "answer": 1, "state": "wa", "type": "permit", "id": 113151}
{"candidates": ["Traffic on the street moves to the left.", "Traffic on the street moves to the right.", "A sign permits the turn."], "question": "About how many bicyclists are killed annually in the United States?", "answer": 0, "state": "wa", "type": "permit", "id": 113178}
{"candidates": ["You have already passed.", "You are approaching from behind.", "Approaching you from behind."], "question": "Before heading out with passengers or cargo, you should check your ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "wa", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 113240}
{"candidates": ["75", "100", "50"], "question": "A permit is valid for ____ days.", "answer": 1, "state": "wa", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 113269}
{"candidates": ["15 to 20 seconds", "5 to 10 seconds", "10 to 15 seconds"], "question": "The intermediate rider course is ____ hours long.", "answer": 2, "state": "wa", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 113297}
{"candidates": ["Only if you or the other driver is injured.", "If there is property damage in excess of $750 or if there are any injuries.", "Only if you are at fault."], "question": "Your horn must be able to be heard from ____ feet away.", "answer": 1, "state": "wa", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 113450}
{"candidates": ["Other drivers when merging onto a freeway.", "Other drivers when they want to slow down.", "The truck driver to stop the vehicle."], "question": "To get your first time endorsement, the fee is ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "wa", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 113479}
{"candidates": ["Loading zone for freight only.", "Loading zone for passengers or mail only.", "Loading zone for freight or passengers."], "question": "How old do you have to be to obtain a Level 1 GDL driver's license?", "answer": 1, "state": "wv", "type": "permit", "id": 114937}
{"candidates": ["Always put one car length between you and the car ahead.", "Look only at the car in front of you while driving.", "Keep your eyes moving to look for possible hazards."], "question": "If the Commissioner of Motor Vehicles has good cause to believe you are incompetent or otherwise not qualified to be licensed, what type of examination may you be required to take?", "answer": 2, "state": "wv", "type": "permit", "id": 114940}
{"candidates": ["Any vehicle with 3 or more axles or weighing more than 4,000 pounds.", "Tank trucks marked with hazardous materials placards.", "Motor homes or pickup trucks towing a boat trailer."], "question": "A school driver eligibility certificate requires that an applicant's parent or legal guardian must submit ____ proofs of WV residency.", "answer": 1, "state": "wv", "type": "permit", "id": 114965}
{"candidates": ["You help reduce traffic congestion.", "Your actions cannot result in a traffic citation.", "You can frustrate the other drivers and make them angry."], "question": "What is one document you do not need if you are a first-time driver's license applicant?", "answer": 2, "state": "wv", "type": "permit", "id": 114968}
{"candidates": ["Stop, then proceed when you think all of the children have exited the bus.", "Slow to 25 MPH and pass cautiously.", "Stop as long as the red lights are flashing."], "question": "What should you include in a basic first aid kit?", "answer": 2, "state": "wv", "type": "permit", "id": 114969}
{"candidates": ["May have to swing wide to complete the right turn.", "Must stay in the right lane at all times while turning.", "May complete its turn in either of the two lanes."], "question": "All the following documents must be brought to the road test except:", "answer": 0, "state": "wv", "type": "permit", "id": 114996}
{"candidates": ["10", "15", "5"], "question": "When should you carry your driver's license?", "answer": 2, "state": "wv", "type": "permit", "id": 114998}
{"candidates": ["During rush hour traffic if there are no bicyclists in the bike lane.", "When you want to pass a driver ahead of you who is turning right.", "When you are within 200 feet of a cross street where you plan to turn right."], "question": "Which of the following is not a valid proof of WV residency for the driver's license application?", "answer": 2, "state": "wv", "type": "permit", "id": 115031}
{"candidates": ["Stay out of the intersection until traffic clears.", "Enter the intersection and wait until traffic clears.", "Merge into another lane and try to go around the traffic."], "question": "What should you do in regards to speed when approaching and crossing an intersection?", "answer": 0, "state": "wv", "type": "permit", "id": 115087}
{"candidates": ["Within 5-10 seconds.", "Within the distance you can see ahead.", "Within the distance lighted by your parking lights."], "question": "What is one driver's license or ID card designation that you cannot get?", "answer": 1, "state": "wv", "type": "permit", "id": 115142}
{"candidates": ["Any lane (as long as it is safe)", "The lane in the center of the road.", "The lane closest to the left curb"], "question": "When is parking on the shoulder of an interstate permitted?", "answer": 2, "state": "wv", "type": "permit", "id": 115143}
{"candidates": ["5", "10", "15"], "question": "When parallel parking, how far from the curb should your wheels be?", "answer": 0, "state": "wv", "type": "permit", "id": 115211}
{"candidates": ["Interior lights", "Parking lights", "Headlights."], "question": "A driver who gets his first license at 23 will be what age when his license needs to be renewed?", "answer": 2, "state": "wv", "type": "permit", "id": 115239}
{"candidates": ["Between 65 mph and 70 mph.", "70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic.", "No faster than 65 mph."], "question": "When is it permissible to not stop at a red light or stop sign?", "answer": 2, "state": "wv", "type": "permit", "id": 115240}
{"candidates": ["Adjusting your outside mirrors.", "Transporting an unrestrained animal inside the vehicle.", "Listening to music through headphones that cover both ears"], "question": "What is one action you should take if you suddenly lose steering control?", "answer": 2, "state": "wv", "type": "permit", "id": 115298}
{"candidates": ["Stop, then proceed when safe.", "Slow down or stop, only if necessary.", "Stop before entering the intersection and let all other traffic go first."], "question": "What should you do if your oil pressure light comes on?", "answer": 0, "state": "wv", "type": "permit", "id": 115299}
{"candidates": ["Stay out of the intersection until traffic clears.", "Merge into another lane and try to go around the traffic.", "Enter the intersection and wait until traffic clears."], "question": "Who is eligible for a Level 3 GDL?", "answer": 0, "state": "wv", "type": "permit", "id": 115300}
{"candidates": ["Yield to pedestrians only in the intersection.", "Wait four seconds before proceeding.", "Yield to any vehicle, bicycle, or pedestrian in the intersection."], "question": "What is the purpose of the Problem Driver Point System?", "answer": 2, "state": "wv", "type": "permit", "id": 115326}
{"candidates": ["Slow down because the lane ends ahead.", "Change lanes and maintain your current speed.", "Be prepared for workers and equipment ahead."], "question": "If headlights fail, all the following are acceptable means of alerting your presence to other drivers except:", "answer": 2, "state": "wv", "type": "permit", "id": 115417}
{"candidates": ["70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic.", "Between 65 mph and 70 mph.", "No faster than 65 mph."], "question": "Which of the following is true of the driver's test?", "answer": 2, "state": "wv", "type": "permit", "id": 115448}
{"candidates": ["Must stay in the right lane at all times while turning.", "May complete its turn in either of the two lanes.", "May have to swing wide to complete the right turn."], "question": "You should be prepared to be testing on ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "wv", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 115750}
{"candidates": ["After you stop", "Never, unless there is a sign saying you can", "the traffic with the green light is clear"], "question": "If the traffic light is red and you want to turn right, you can turn when:", "answer": 2, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117272}
{"candidates": ["10 to 15 seconds", "100 to 150 yards", "1 to 1.5 blocks"], "question": "How far down the road you should look when driving", "answer": 0, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117307}
{"candidates": ["Yes, it is always safer than driving faster than other traffic.", "No, you can block traffic when you drive too slowly.", "Yes, it is a good defensive driving technique."], "question": "Talking on a cell phone while driving can increase your risk for an accident by how much?", "answer": 1, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117330}
{"candidates": ["In a bicycle lane.", "In an unmarked crosswalk", "Within three feet of a private driveway."], "question": "If involved in a crash, when is it okay to move an injured person?", "answer": 1, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117359}
{"candidates": ["Under no circumstances", "If the shoulder is wide enough to accommodate your vehicle", "If the vehicle ahead of you is turning left."], "question": "If your brakes stop working, you should:", "answer": 0, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117361}
{"candidates": ["May not enter the bicycle lane.", "Must merge into the bicycle lane before turning.", "Should only merge into the bicycle lane if you stop before turning."], "question": "It's the duty of ____ to make sure the vehicle is safe to drive.", "answer": 1, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117391}
{"candidates": ["That only vehicles next to the broken line may pass.", "That vehicles may pass in all directions.", "That vehicles next to the solid yellow line may pass."], "question": "Always try to avoid being hit head on if you can, but if you can not and you are about to be hit from the front, you should try to ____.", "answer": 0, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117420}
{"candidates": ["You cannot cross the line to pass", "You may cross the line to change lanes", "You may only change lanes if you are in the left lane"], "question": "If you are driving on a highway with a single broken white line marking", "answer": 1, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117454}
{"candidates": ["The reasons you can drive between midnight and 5am", "Both", "The type and number of passengers that can be in your car"], "question": "If you are under 18 you have additional license restrictions for the first 9 months for", "answer": 1, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117471}
{"candidates": ["Slow down because the lane ends ahead.", "Change lanes and maintain your current speed.", "Be prepared for workers and equipment ahead."], "question": "When can your driver's license be reinstated?", "answer": 2, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117481}
{"candidates": ["When there are no vehicles approaching nearby.", "On a one-way street on a green arrow.", "Across two sets of solid double, yellow lines."], "question": "Pedestrians must be yielded to when:", "answer": 0, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117507}
{"candidates": ["High beams.", "Fog lights only.", "Low beams."], "question": "How many seconds of space should you keep between your vehicle and the one in front of you?", "answer": 2, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117510}
{"candidates": ["Going straight through the roundabout", "Is already in the roundabout", "Going to the 1st right out of the roundabout"], "question": "In a roundabout, the driver who shouldn't have to stop is", "answer": 1, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117528}
{"candidates": ["Never", "If you haven't been drinking", "if you think you will fail"], "question": "If you are stopped and the officer suspects you have been drinking, you can refuse the BAC test", "answer": 0, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117574}
{"candidates": ["Only if you or the other driver is injured.", "Only if you are at fault.", "If there is property damage in excess of $750 or if there are any injuries."], "question": "If the DMV declares you a habitual offender in Wisconsin, your driving privilege will be revoked for a period of:", "answer": 2, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117599}
{"candidates": ["Any 3-axle vehicle regardless of the weight.", "A vehicle pulling two trailers.", "A 3-axle vehicle if the Gross Vehicle Weight is less than 6,000 pounds."], "question": "The law requires a distance of at least ____ feet behind a snowplow when it's red or amber lights are on.", "answer": 2, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117600}
{"candidates": ["Everyone in the vehicle", "Only for children under 16 years old", "Only for the driver"], "question": "Seat belts are required by", "answer": 0, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117644}
{"candidates": ["Cannot see the vehicle directly to your right.", "Have passed the other vehicle\u2019s front bumper.", "See the vehicle\u2019s headlights in your rear view mirror."], "question": "You get pulled over and the officer suspects you have been using a restricted controlled substance. He requests you take a blood test and you refuse. What are the consequences?", "answer": 2, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117747}
{"candidates": ["May have to swing wide to complete the right turn.", "Must stay in the right lane at all times while turning.", "May complete its turn in either of the two lanes."], "question": "If you are involved in a crash, be sure to:", "answer": 0, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117809}
{"candidates": ["Oncoming cars moving straight ahead or turning right", "Passing cars", "No one in particular"], "question": "Drivers turning left must yield to", "answer": 0, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117816}
{"candidates": ["Turn on your emergency flashers and stay in your vehicle you can", "Blow your horn at passing cars to let them know you have stopped", "Get out of the vehicle once you have stopped"], "question": "It is necessary for you to make an emergency stop. You should:", "answer": 0, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117854}
{"candidates": ["Either A or B", "The damage is more than $1,000", "Someone is hurt"], "question": "You have to report a crash to law enforcement when:", "answer": 0, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117904}
{"candidates": ["Stop before crossing through", "Wait for a green light", "Slow down and proceed with caution"], "question": "As you approach an intersection with a flashing yellow light:", "answer": 2, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117909}
{"candidates": ["Headlights.", "Interior lights", "Parking lights"], "question": "How many points in a 12 month period will get your license revoked?", "answer": 0, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117959}
{"candidates": ["5", "15", "10"], "question": "Which of the following does not help you reduce fatigue on long trips?", "answer": 0, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 117987}
{"candidates": ["Quickly tap the brake pedal several times", "Blow horn constantly", "Wave left arm out the window"], "question": "If you are going to stop or slow down where another driver does not expect you to:", "answer": 0, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 118067}
{"candidates": ["At least 30 feet but not more than 100 feet from the nearest track", "A maximum of 50 feet and a minimum of 15 feet from the nearest railroad track", "At least 30 feet but not more than 50 feet from the nearest track"], "question": "Which vehicle(s) in a funeral procession must obey traffic signs and signals?", "answer": 1, "state": "wi", "type": "permit", "id": 118079}
{"candidates": ["It is OK for small children to ride in the front passenger seat of your car.", "Use the rear-facing child restraint system in the front passenger seat.", "Small children should ride in the back seat."], "question": "It's your choice is your want to provide your own ____.", "answer": 2, "state": "wi", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 118114}
{"candidates": ["Look to the sides of your vehicle to see what is coming.", "Slowly pass vehicles that seem to be stopped for no reason.", "Stop, listen, and proceed cautiously."], "question": "What is it called when two vehicles are on either sides of your vehicle?", "answer": 0, "state": "wy", "type": "permit", "id": 119657}
{"candidates": ["Decrease your following distance.", "Slow down to watch the workers.", "Pass the construction zone carefully and not rubberneck."], "question": "When do most accidents involving wildlife occur?", "answer": 2, "state": "wy", "type": "permit", "id": 119743}
{"candidates": ["No faster than 65 mph.", "Between 65 mph and 70 mph.", "70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic."], "question": "Your driving record contains:", "answer": 0, "state": "wy", "type": "permit", "id": 119749}
{"candidates": ["On the side of the freeway in an emergency.", "Within 100 feet of an elementary school.", "Next to a red painted curb."], "question": "A \"B\" restriction on your license means which of the following?", "answer": 2, "state": "wy", "type": "permit", "id": 119987}
{"candidates": ["See the vehicle\u2019s headlights in your rear view mirror.", "Cannot see the vehicle directly to your right.", "Have passed the other vehicle\u2019s front bumper."], "question": "If you buy a used vehicle, what should you get from the previous owner?", "answer": 0, "state": "wy", "type": "permit", "id": 120018}
{"candidates": ["No faster than 65 mph.", "Between 65 mph and 70 mph.", "70 mph or faster to keep up with the speed of traffic."], "question": "What vehicle(s) can you operate when you are issued a Class M license?", "answer": 0, "state": "wy", "type": "permit", "id": 120138}
{"candidates": ["10", "5", "15"], "question": "What test do you not have to pass in order to receive an instruction permit?", "answer": 1, "state": "wy", "type": "permit", "id": 120140}
{"candidates": ["Decrease the distance you look ahead of your vehicle.", "Test your tires\u2019 traction while going uphill.", "Avoid making fast turns and fast stops."], "question": "How long does it normally take to move your foot from the accelerator to the brake?", "answer": 2, "state": "wy", "type": "permit", "id": 120259}
{"candidates": ["Adjusting your outside mirrors.", "Listening to music through headphones that cover both ears", "Transporting an unrestrained animal inside the vehicle."], "question": "When should you turn your key to the lock position when in motion in a vehicle with a steering-lock device?", "answer": 1, "state": "wy", "type": "permit", "id": 120287}
{"candidates": ["Any vehicle with 3 or more axles or weighing more than 4,000 pounds.", "Tank trucks marked with hazardous materials placards.", "Motor homes or pickup trucks towing a boat trailer."], "question": "A leading cause of single vehicle crashes is caused by ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "wy", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 120348}
{"candidates": ["Slow down or stop, only if necessary.", "Stop before entering the intersection and let all other traffic go first.", "Stop, then proceed when safe."], "question": "How much is a renewal for a non-commercial driver's license?", "answer": 2, "state": "wy", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 120349}
{"candidates": ["The railroad crossing is located in a city or town that has frequent train traffic.", "You do not have room on the other side to completely cross the tracks.", "You transport two or more young children in a passenger vehicle."], "question": "Before you head out on the road, make sure you ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "wy", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 120350}
{"candidates": ["Four yellow rear reflectors", "One brake light", "One headlight"], "question": "A motorcycle is required to have all of the following except:", "answer": 0, "state": "wy", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 120364}
{"candidates": ["Swerve", "Sleep", "Scan"], "question": "A five-step process to help drivers make appropriate judgments is known as SIPDE. What does the S stand for?", "answer": 2, "state": "wy", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 120370}
{"candidates": ["Avoid driving in the bicycle lane.", "Signal for 100 feet before turning.", "Move toward the left side of your lane."], "question": "Most crashes happen ____.", "answer": 1, "state": "wy", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 120409}
{"candidates": ["Provide an escape route", "Invite others to use your lane", "Decrease your visibility to others"], "question": "The proper lane position should:", "answer": 0, "state": "wy", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 120424}
{"candidates": ["16", "14", "18"], "question": "What is the minimum age for a motorcycle license?", "answer": 0, "state": "wy", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 120458}
{"candidates": ["Personal injury", "Liability", "Collision"], "question": "What type of insurance do you need to legally drive a motor vehicle?", "answer": 1, "state": "wy", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 120488}
{"candidates": ["Time", "Drinking coffee", "Exercise"], "question": "What\u2019s the only way to reduce Blood Alcohol Content levels?", "answer": 0, "state": "wy", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 120489}
{"candidates": ["Ride in a staggered formation", "Ride in large groups \u2013 the larger the better", "Place beginning riders just behind the lead riders"], "question": "When riding in a group, which of the following should not be done?", "answer": 1, "state": "wy", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 120548}
{"candidates": ["You help reduce traffic congestion.", "Your actions cannot result in a traffic citation.", "You can frustrate the other drivers and make them angry."], "question": "What license is required for motorcycles and mopeds?", "answer": 2, "state": "wy", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 120558}
{"candidates": ["0.08", "0.02", "0.04"], "question": "A driver of a motorcycle who is under 21 can have their license suspended for DWUI with an alcohol concentration of ____ or more.", "answer": 1, "state": "wy", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 120584}
{"candidates": ["Interfere", "Identify", "Impact"], "question": "A five-step process to help drivers make appropriate judgments is known as SIPDE. What does the I stand for?", "answer": 1, "state": "wy", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 120601}
{"candidates": ["Separate lanes of traffic in the same direction", "A no passing zone", "Separate traffic flowing in opposite directions"], "question": "On a roadway, what do white lines indicate?", "answer": 0, "state": "wy", "type": "motorcycle", "id": 120674}
